<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v107 on mysterium</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v107/</link><description>Recent content in v107 on mysterium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v107/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2021.06.23 patch notes (v107.02.02) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-02-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-02-02/</guid><description>Update 1. Service stabilization Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability 2. Item Changed to be able to discard 1-day Summer Festival style cosmetic 3. Services (TERA KR exclusive) 테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. (TERA KR exclusive additional sale listing)
6/30(수) 점검 이후부터 7/28(수) 점검 전까지 테라 샵에서 아래 상품들이 여름 특별 할인으로 가격이 일시 조정될 예정입니다. (TERA KR exclusive discount sale listing)
6/30(수) 점검 이후 테라샵에서 일부 상품의 판매 방향 및 정책 변경으로 가격이 영구 조정될 예정입니다.</description></item><item><title>2021.06.16 patch notes (v107.02.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-02-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-02-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Service stabilization Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability 2. Event (TERA KR exclusive) 던전 드랍 확률 1.5배 증가 이벤트가 진행됩니다. 기간: 2021년 6월 16일 점검 이후 ~ 2021년 6월 23일 점검 전까지 강화 성공 확률 2배 증가 이벤트가 진행됩니다. 기간: 2021년 6월 16일 점검 이후 ~ 2021년 6월 20일 23:59까지 3. Homepage (TERA KR exclusive) Activated ranking system on main website 홈페이지 -&amp;gt; 순위 메뉴를 통해 확인해 보실 수 있습니다.</description></item><item><title>2021.06.09 patch notes (v107.02) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-02/</guid><description>Update 1. Summer Festival Summer Festival begins Completing guide quests per festival unlocks daily quests to obtain [Summer Festival Coin] Beach Party Guide quest [Event] Life&amp;rsquo;s a Beach Quest level requirement Lv.48 Festival location Serpentis Isle - Boan Strand region Daily quests Splash Cannon Mini-Game, Melon Bash Mini-Game, Sand Castles in The Sand, The Horn Carver&amp;rsquo;s Concerns, Beauty at the Beach, Ramsay&amp;rsquo;s New Hobby Item obtained 2021 Summer Festival Coin 15 [2021 Summer Festival Coin] can be obtained per character via Beach Party festival Festival of the Sun Guide quest [태양의 축제] 지혜의 나무로 Quest level requirement Lv.</description></item><item><title>2021.06.02 patch notes (v107.01.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-01-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-01-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Server stabilization Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability 2. Services 테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. 아이템명 가격(블루) 판매 시작일 판매 종료일 [랜덤] 돌아온 밀리터리 코스튬x연합 의장복 상자 40 2021-06-02 점검 후 2021-06-23 점검 전 [랜덤] 돌아온 핫! 토끼 스타일 상자 40 2021-06-02 점검 후 2021-06-23 점검 전 [랜덤] 신비한 파트너 상자 55 2021-06-02 점검 후 상시 판매</description></item><item><title>2021.05.26 patch notes (v107.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v107-01/</guid><description>Developer comment Addition update on new gear release together with a class balance is in preparation. key detail in preparation is, for each class, stat-related passive revision, skill damage and effect adjustment, and select skill revision and addition. through these changes, we hope to match the necessary balance between classes that were not applied in this balance update, so please stay tuned for more information. Update 1. Combat balance Berserker Unleash Unleashed: Sinister, Unleashed: Dexter Increase skill damage by 20% Changed 폭주 : 강화 효과 stack limit to 7 Changed damage increase per 폭주 : 강화 효과 stack from 5~10% -&amp;gt; 8~14% Unleashed: Rampage Changed 야수의 돌진 강화 효과 stack limit to 7 Changed damage increase per 야수의 돌진 강화 효과 stack from 5~10% -&amp;gt; 8~14% Unleashed: Beast Fury Changed cooldown duration from 10s -&amp;gt; 8s Unleash Increased skill damage by 30% Cyclone Changed stagger effect to players to apply on 1st, 2nd, 3rd hit Bloodlust Skill level 1 Increased skill damage increase upon successful hit on monsters from 10% -&amp;gt; 12% Skill level 2 Increased skill damage increase upon successful hit on monsters from 10% -&amp;gt; 15% Flatten Increased skill damage by 15% Vampiric Blow Increased skill damage by 15% Tackle Increased skill damage by 20% Developer comment Unleash-related skill and Bloodlust skill adjustments - Regarding the Berserker class, we realized there was a risk due to the lack of utility while using Unleash, especially in the current meta where frequency repositioning is necessary.</description></item></channel></rss>