<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2016 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/2016/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2016 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 patch summary</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/summary/</guid>
      <description>January   v42.01
 New class : Ninja New Flight system New dungeon : Demokron Factory New dungeon : Celestial Arena Dungeon : Reopened Wonderholme Dungeon : Reopened Abscess (hard) Dungeon : Reopened Abscess Dungeon : Removed select solo instances Dungeon : Removed Dreadspire Dungeon : Removed Timescape (hard) Dungeon : Removed Kalivan&amp;rsquo;s Dreadnaught Dungeon : Removed Forsaken Island (hard) Dungeon : Removed Bathysmal Rise Dungeon : Removed Bathysmal Rise (hard) Dungeon : Removed Sky Cruiser Endeavor (hard) Open world : Level progression revision Class balance (Archer) : CHanged to hide trap effect to enemies    v42.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.12.22 patch notes (v54.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v54-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v54-01/</guid>
      <description>Translated patch notes by Loriri (idi0ticgenius#4869) and seraphinush (seraphinush#5417) with the help of Sam (sam202s)
Update 1. New class : Valkyrie  Added new class Valkyrie  Valkyrie is currently only available for Castanic Female Active skills     Passive skills   Glyph  2. Level progression open world difficulty revision  성장구간 사냥터에 배치된 몬스터들의 난이도 체감이 점진적으로 증가되도록 개선되었습니다. 성장구간 사냥터에서 중형 몬스터 분노 시 공격력과 공격 속도가 상승하도록 수정했습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.12.08 patch notes (v53.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v53-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v53-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill  Berserker  Vampiric Strike, Lethal Strike  Revised issue where damage was significantly low at high HP The following is the HP and damage ratio:  HP 100-90%: 1.0 times, HP 90-80%: 1.1 times Damage onward will increase by 1.1 times per 10% HP (Max at HP 10-0%: 2.0 times)       Slayer  Knockdown Strike  Changed so that Knockdown Strike can be chained from the 1st and 2nd hit of Distant Blade as well Fixed issue where casting speed of Knockdown Strike was significant faster than intended     Lancer  Backstep  Changed animation to take effect from Attack Speed, while making the iframe last just before the end of the animation static      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.12.01 patch notes (v53.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v53-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v53-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill  Berserker  Thunder Strike  Increase PvE damage by 15% Slightly decrease PvP damage Changed glyph point for Glyph of the Slick (common) from 7 to 6 Changed glyph point for Glyph of the Slick (uncommon) from 6 to 5 Changed glyph point for Glyph of the Slick (rare) from 5 to 4 Added different skill display per charge, and increased visibility of hit radius       Fiery Rage  Changed to be able to move while casting in [normal] stance   Triumphant Shout  Removed skill, and added skill effect to Tenacity   Cyclone  Patch notes do not comment on pulling effect on enemies Changed glyph effect to increase damage from 12% to 24% from overcharging   Changed skill display hues   Tenacity  Added Triumphant Shout skill effect Increased MP regen   Bloodlust  Added Flurry of Blows effect for 10 seconds upon casting   Lethal Strike  Changed to increased damage as HP decreases Added passive to increase crit chance when below 50% HP Changed glyph point for Glyph of the Slick (common) from 6 to 5   Vampiric Blow  Changed to increased damage as HP decreases Added passive to increase crit chance when below 50% HP       Reduced post-skill display delay Changed glyph point for Glyph of Power (common) from 5 to 4 Added glyph to increase skill damage of Lethal Strike by 20%   Slayer  Knockdown Strike  Increased PvE damage by 20% Increased casting speed after 3rd hit of Distant Blade Added Glyph (common) to decrease damage by 50% while casting   Backstab  Decreased cooldown by 3 seconds Readjusted grounding effect after using skill Changed to not take cooldown in case it fails to move   Triumphant Shout  Removed skill, and added skill effect and glyphs to Tenacity   Overhand Strike  Adjusted level requirement and base damage for skill when under level 52 Removed knockdown to monsters (knockdown still exists for Ultimate Overhand Strike) Increased casting speed after 3rd hit of Distant Blade and Fury Strike   Heart Thrust  Increased PvE damage by 10%   Startling Kick  Changed to ignore collision during casting   Overpower  Changed to be able to stop animation during casting   Tenacity  Added Triumphant Shout skill effect upon casting Increased MP regen   Eviscerate  Increased damage by 10% Increased crit chance by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.10.27 patch notes (v52.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v52-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v52-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill  Warrior  Revised Edge system  Edge will stack on the player instead of the monster      - Stack UI will be display beneath the HP/MP bar   - Choosing the option shown above will display stack under the HP bar - Scythe - Changed Glyph of Carving from increase crit chance by 2 times to 3 times against monsters - Increased PvE damage by 10% - Smoke Aggressor - Changed to instantiate instantly - While Shadow is summoned, it will take 50% (PvP 20%) of the damage - Traverse Cut - Removed endurance debuff - Added 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.10.13 patch notes (v51.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Festival  Started Halloween Festival  할로윈 축제는 10월 13일부터 11월 10일까지 시행됩니다. 축제 기간 동안 각 마을 및 대도시에 [마녀의 성 지상 1층]으로 순간이동 시켜주는 &amp;lsquo;꼬마 마녀&#39;들이 등장합니다. 마녀의 성 지상 1층에서 &amp;lsquo;마녀탐정 티티아나&amp;rsquo; NPC와 대화하여 할로윈 퀘스트를 받을 수 있습니다.     마녀의 성 연회장  할로윈 호박 대포에 탑승하여 몰려오는 몬스터를 처치하는 디펜스 형태의 던전입니다. 마녀의 성 연회장에서 &amp;lsquo;하르니아&amp;rsquo; NPC와 대화하여 게임을 시작할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.09.29 patch notes (v51.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Added new dungeon [Broken Prison] Broken Prison is a 5man party dungeon  Can be entered through teleportal in Arcadia &amp;gt; Oblivion Woods &amp;gt; Deva Silva, and requires iLvl 417 to enter via IMS Rewards are Tier 2 Demense earring/ring, Imperator Belt, Cleansing Brooch, Goldfinger Token, Eau d&amp;rsquo;Fascination, Lachelith&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Box, Imperator designs, Ambush designs, Rare innerwear, Dyad Niveot Structure, and etc Added [Broken Prison] to guild quest   Harrowhold  Adjusted balance per phase  Phase 1  Decreased Agalith damage by 15% Decreased Agalith HP by 10%   Phase 2  Increased Balista skill damage by 20%   Phase 3  Decreased Vergoth defense by 5%   Phase 4  Increased attack speed of aerial breathe by 10% Increased attack speed of stoning attack due to close-range explosion by 15%     Decreased gold drop per phase  Gold Hunter Boost/Internet Cafe/Elite related bonus gold will no longer apply Increased the upper limit of gold given, and decreased lower limit Decreased the number of gold item dropped   Exchanged the loot table between Phase 1 and Phase 2  Clearing Phase 2 gives Phase 1 loot, and clearing Phase 1 gives Phase 2 loot   Changed loot table and loot probability of Vergoth&amp;rsquo;s Bronze/Silver/Gold Treasure Box  Removed Diamond Added Goddess&amp;rsquo;s Tear and Superior Etching Box   각 페이즈의 기본보상인 베르고스의 전투 주머니에 강화석이 추가로 구성됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.09.22 patch notes (v50.01.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v50-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v50-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Civil Unrest  Reopened Civil Unrest  Some comment   Some comment Changed loot table for bams in CU  Increased the number of Diamond and Emerald Changed Imperator gear box to Ambush gear box   Added message upon kill or death during CU Added 5 contribution points upon kill or death during CU  Can only be obtained while Guild Tower exists   Added Guild XP to CU rank 1-10     Rank Guild XP     1 340   2 145   3 97   4 82   5 82   6 75   7 75   8 75   9 75   10 75    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.09.13 patch notes (v50.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v50-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v50-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill  Archer  Removed Bloodlust effect (additional damage as HP of monster decreases) from Thunderbolt Adjusted the excessive PvP damage of Thunderbolt Changed Rapid Fire - Glyph of Power from increase skill damage by 50% to 20% Changed Rapid Fire - Glyph of Persistence from eliminate cooldown by 30% to 15%    2. Item (TERA KR exclusive)  테라 코인상점 아이템 추가  스페셜탭에 특성 초기화 물약이 추가되었습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.09.08 patch notes (v50.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v50-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v50-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill  Archer  Added new skill [Chase]  Skill description   Added new skill [Find Weakness]  Skill description   Increased damage of Thunderbolt by 100%  Changed skill display Added Noctenium effect  Consumes 2 Noctenium Infusion, increases damage by 9-13%     Increased damage of Radiant Arrow by 25%  Changed skill display   Increased damage of Penetrating Arrow by 25%  Changed skill display   Increased damage of Rain of Arrows by 10%  First hit positioning will determine the positioning of the entire skill Changed skill display   Changed Backstep to be directional input Changed Breakaway Bolt to be directional input Increased damage of Rapid Fire  Increased damage of first hit by 3 times Increased damage of 2~7 hit by 10% Focus Preparation stacks per hit   Increased casting speed of Poison Arrow Increased maximum poison stack to 3 Changed Ensnaring Trap from 1 hit to 2 hit  Re-clicking the skill will trigger the second hit of the trap Second hit of skill will apply decrease movement speed by 90% effect Movement speed debuff will be halved in PvP Time limit to trigger the second hit is 3 seconds Changed skill sound and display   Changed Eagle&amp;rsquo;s Eye effect  Before: Increase damage against bams by 5% After: Increase damage against monsters by 7%   Removed Sniper&amp;rsquo;s Eye Renamed Final Salvo to Sequential Fire  Combined 5 hits to a single hit Increased the damage to be 40% more than the sum damage of the original 5 hits Changed skill display   Broadened the skills that applies Focus Preparation  Changed the skill effect from using Arrow to Focus Preparation Focus Preparation will stack from Arrow, Sequential Fire, and Rapid Fire, and upon 10 stacks Focus effect will apply increasing the charging speed of all charge skills   Changed and added glyphs       Rank Skill Glyph Effect Level obtained Cost     Common Rapid Fire Glyph of Persistence Chance to eliminate cooldown by 30% 20 4   Common Sequential Fire Glyphs of Energy Decrease cooldown by 25% 24 4   Uncommon Sequential Fire Glyphs of Energy Decrease cooldown by 35% 65 3   Uncommon Thunderbolt Glyphs of Carving Increase crit chance by 2 times 63 4   Rare Thunderbolt Glyphs of Carving Increase crit chance by 3 times 65 3   Rare Radiant Arrow Glyphs of Carving Increased crit chance by 3 times 65 4     Berserker  Applies both Fiery Rage effect and Flurry of Blows effect upon using Fiery Rage Decreased Evasive Roll cooldown by 1 second Increased Evasive Smash cooldown by 2 seconds Added a new passive skill which increases crit chance of the next Thunder Strike if the previous Thunder Strike fails to crit  This passive will only apply in PvE situations   Changed glyph effects  Changed Flurry of Blows - Glyph of Lingering (common) to Fiery Rage – Glyph of Lingering (increase effect duration by 30%) Changed Flurry of Blows – Glyph of Lingering (uncommon) to Fiery Rage – Glyph of Lingering (increase effect duration by 35%) Changed Evasive Roll – Glyph of Energy to Thunder Strike – Glyph of Energy (decrease cooldown by 20%)     Reaper  Increased damage to dungeon monsters Increased damage to bams   Gunner  Increased damage to dungeon monsters Increased damage to bams   Priest  (Fixed) Blessing of Arun, Blessing of Shara, and Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Shield does not lose effect when teleporting within the same area (dungeon to dungeon, field to field)   Mystic  (Fixed) Vow does not lose effect when teleporting within the same area (dungeon to dungeon, field to field)    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.09.01 patch notes (v49.01.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v49-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v49-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Adjusted Harrowhold balance.  Phase 3  Increased Vergoth defense Increased center breathe damage Increased HP of attribute sphere Increased attribute sphere explosion damage Increased HP of shield for all body parts Increased periodic damage of lava puddle Increased defense upon burn phase      Developer&#39;s comment - We have confirmed that phase 3 severely lacks difficulty. Because of this, clearing phase 3 has become meaningless, and it does not accomplish its role as a bridge to phase 4, and thus the difficulty of the phase was significantly increased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.08.30 patch notes (v49.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v49-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v49-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Bug fixes  Dungeon   Fixed issue allowing players to enter cleared phases in Harrowhold. Fixed issue where players could iframe the sphere explosion in phase 3 of Harrowhold. Fixed issue where Vergoth&amp;rsquo;s target pattern would intermittently be stacked twice. Fixed issue where Breathe attack could be blocked in phase 4 of Harrowhold. Fixed issue where players could potentially die from spawning rock pillars in phase 4 of Harrowhold. Fixed issue where Rock pillar intermittently be located differently than the spawned located in phase 4 of Harrowhold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.08.25 patch notes (v49.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v49-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v49-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  New dungeon &amp;lsquo;Harrowhold&amp;rsquo; added (referred to as Harrowhold from here on)  30 man level 65 raid Can be entered through teleportal located at Velika Outskirts. Harrowhold does not support cross-server instance party matching system. Harrowhold holds 4 stages/phases, and each stage/phase will give rewards. (Rewards can be looted by breaking instantiated reward box upon clearing, and reward will not be given unless player is located within 100m when the reward box is broken).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.08.11 patch notes (v48.03) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v48-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v48-03/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill  Berserker  Increased damage against dungeon monsters/BAMs   Sorcerer  Increased casting speed of the following skills  Glacial Retreat by 20% Painblast by 20% Nova by 25% Lightning Bolt by 15%   Increased PvP damage of the following skills  Meteor Fall / Overchanneled Meteor Fall Void Pulse Flame Pillar   Lightning Bolt  Decreased damage by 15%   Warp Barrier  Changed MP cost to 0 Recover a maximum of 5% MP upon casting Recover a maximum of 5% MP upon taking damage no longer works Overchanneling does not apply when Warp Barrier is in effect   Ice Sphere  Decreased skill AoE   Meteor Fall / Overchanneled Meteor Fall  Able to use Backstep while casting     Reference: Slayer balance patch will be on the 08/25 update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.07.21 patch notes (v48.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v48-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v48-01/</guid>
      <description>Update: 2016.07.26 - additional sorcerer pve/pvp buffs
1. Class renewal : Sorcerer  Removed Skills  Removed Ice Needle Removed Fireblast Removed Magma Bomb Removed Overchannel   Burst of Celerity  Changed into passive skill Changed to increase attack speed by 30% -Arcane Pulse Decreased charge by 1 bar, and blast 2 pulses are full charge Increased number of pulses with Overchanneling effect Increased speed of pulse Changed to immediately fire at full charge Increased damage Decreased glyph point for Glyph of Power (common) from 4 to 3 Decreased glyph point for Glyph of Carving (common, uncommon) from 4 to 3   Mana infusion  Increased mana regeneration to 400-700mp/s at a max of 2000-3500mp over a duration of 5 seconds Added Glyph of Energy (common)  4 points Decrease cooldown by 30%     Frost Sphere  Replaces Ice Needle Fires Frost Sphere towards the front.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>