<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v113 on tera-mysterium</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v113/</link><description>Recent content in v113 on tera-mysterium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v113/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2021.12.15 patch notes (v113.02.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-02-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-02-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Service stabilization 서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다. Bug fixes Fixed issue where Bandit Santa Caiman spawn in Wintera Snowfield event battleground</description></item><item><title>2021.12.08 patch notes (v113.02) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-02/</guid><description>Update 1. Service stabilization 서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다. 2. Services (TERA KR exclusive) 테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. Image not available
Bug fixes Fixed issue where 태고의 유적지 on Island of Glowing Dawn is displayed as 로크 추종자 기지 Fixed issue where HP bar does not display for select NPCs in combat on Island of Glowing Dawn Fixed issue where Supernatural Power effect does not apply upon learning Mighty Empyrean Gryphon (rare, legendary) Fixed issue where pop-up upon death does not display properly on Island of Glowing Dawn Fixed issue in Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold where logging out while capturing pyre maintains capturing process Fixed issue where NPC Agrakan dialogue is awkward</description></item><item><title>2021.12.01 patch notes (v113.01.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-01-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-01-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Open world Island of Glowing Dawn Changed to be able to teleport to Island of Glowing Dawn through NPC Barem at North Dock Removed &amp;lsquo;Island of Glowing Dawn Teleportal Scroll&amp;rsquo; from Island of Dawn North Dock&amp;rsquo;s merchant 2. Services (TERA KR exclusive) 테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. Image not available
3. Event (TERA KR exclusive) 다음의 이벤트 아이템이 제거됩니다. 할로윈 사탕, [이벤트] 할로윈 축제 상자, [이벤트] 할로윈 스타일 상자 Bug fixes Fixed issue at Island of Glowing Dawn where background music does not play Fixed issue at Island of Glowing Dawn where dropping party teleport players out Fixed issue at Island of Glowing Dawn where there is no sound on interacting with NPC Jenny Fixed issue at Island of Glowing Dawn where players cannot enter Battleground upon matching Fixed issue where Priest&amp;rsquo;s Holy Burst range does not align with tooltip Fixed issue where Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold opens everyday even after the end of its event Fixed issue where there is no delay entering character selection screen</description></item><item><title>2021.11.24 patch notes (v113.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v113-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon Resonance Added Pure Resonance Gate Entry Entry is available through Pure Resonance Gate located in Baldera &amp;gt; Balderon Entry requires Weak AWAKE Resonance Stone (consumed per party member) Pure Resonance Gate Entry level 70 Item level 504 Either Stormed Citadel, Fusion Laboratory, or Grotto of Lost Souls (hard) is chosen automatically upon entering Pure Resonance Gate Highest resonance level of each dungeon is level 1 Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) Changed unleash time limit to 20 minutes Changed orb mechanic method to be the same as before, and changed to be able to destroy by close range attacks Increased damage of pulse mechanic Reward Added Adventure Coin reward upon clearing Dungeon Resonance Dungeon Resonance Reward Pure Resonance Gate Adventure Coin (50, 1 Day) Resonance Gate '' Bloody Resonance Gate Adventure Coin (150, 1 Day) Adventure Coin obtained from Dungeon Resonance is of equal distribution and is distributed to all party members 2.</description></item></channel></rss>