<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v110 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v110/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v110 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v110/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.09.15 patch notes (v110.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-02/</guid>
      <description>*9/10 15:55 - 던전 항목이 업데이트 되었습니다. *9/10 14:29 - 길드대전 항목이 업데이트 되었습니다. Update 1. Dungeon  Increased Sky Cruiser Endeavor (hard) reward  Added 정제된 돌 재료 상자 (pl.) as additional reward  1 Essence is guaranteed with full Joy of Partying buff, and additional can be obtained at chance The following items can be obtained from 정제된 돌 재료 상자 (pl.) with equal chance         Listing Amount     Solar Essence 1   Lava Essence 1   Glacial Essence 1   Frost Essence 1   Lightning Essence 1    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.09.08 patch notes (v110.01.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-02/</guid>
      <description>*09/06 15:30 - 버그 수정 사항이 업데이트 되었습니다. Update 1. Service stabilization  서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다.  2. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.     아이템명 가격(블루) 판매 시작일 판매 종료일     [랜덤] 이세계의 퇴마사 의상 상자 40 2021-09-08 점검 후 2021-09-29 점검 전    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where unclaimed rewards from previous TERA Pass season is not parcelled Fixed issue where logging out while Manage Effect UI is open resets Manage Effect settings Fixed issue in Resonance Dungeon where damage is inflicted despite destroying tentacle cage within time limit  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.09.01 patch notes (v110.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilization  서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다.  2. Dungeon Resonance  Adjusted to decrease reflect damage amount Fixed to no longer apply reflect effect on Argon Solder in Corrupted Skynest (hard) Fixed issue where select mechanics activate abnormally when level 31 and above effect is applied in Corrupted Skynest (hard)  3. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.  Image not available</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.08.25 patch notes (v110.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01/</guid>
      <description>*08/25 11:56 - 버그 수정 내역이 업데이트 되었습니다. *08/25 10:40 - 승리자의 증표 상점 보상 내역이 업데이트 되었습니다. *08/24 20:18 - 버그 수정 내역이 업데이트 되었습니다. *08/23 17:37 - 발키온 연합 지령서 추가 보상, 신규 악세서리 랜덤 옵션, 클래스 밸런스, T-cat 상점 신규 판매 상품 목록이 업데이트 되었습니다. Update 1. Resonance Dungeon  Resonance Dungeon phenomenon has occurred in Balderon  Resonated dungeons can only be entered through the Resonance Gate located in Balderon, Baldera       Resonance Dungeon content becomes available after completing &amp;lsquo;[중요] 던전 공명 현상 탐구&amp;rsquo; quest available at level 70         Two types of gates exist : Resonance Gate (left) and Bloody Resonance Gate (right) (instances available differ between the two gates) &amp;lsquo;Bloody Resonance Gate&amp;rsquo; offers content above higher difficulty (offers exclusive reward not available through the &amp;lsquo;Resonance Gate&#39;) Each gate differs in the available dungeons, maximum tier, and recommended item level         Gate Resonance Gate Bloody Resonance Gate     Tier 1~3 1~n   Dungeon Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum, Fusion Laboratory (hard) Corrupted Skynest (hard)   Recommended ilvl 504 510       Players can interact with the Resonance Gate (default : F) to enter         Players can enter Resonance Dungeon by clicking Teleport (can enter as a 5-Person Party) Successfully completing the challenge opens higher levels to challenge inBloody Resonance Gate Players require an entrance item to enter (consumed per Party Member)         Resonance Gate entrance item Bloody Resonance Gate entrance item               Resonance Stone can be obtained from level 65 and above instances Resonance Stone is only usable during its appropriate season (AWAKE Resonance Stone can only be used during AWAKE season)   Entering a Resonance Dungeon starts a timer         Reward is distributed by clearing the instance within the time limit, nevertheless the minimum reward is distributed by defeating the boss monster after exceeding the time limit  Resonance Dungeon does not distribute loot reward, but distributes either success reward or fail reward   Resonance Effect (pl.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>