<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v84 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/tags/v84/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v84 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/tags/v84/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.23 patch notes (v84.05) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-05/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Demon&amp;rsquo;s Wheel (5-man)  Open until maintenance on 6/27 Requires level 65, and item level 446 to use instance matching system Consumes 145 Adventure Coins upon entry, with up to 40 entries per week (80 enrties for VIP) Teleportal is located at Allementheia Outskirts   Loot table includes Gold/Silver Plate, Otherworldly Shard, Archdevan Formula, Scavenged Supplies, Devil&amp;rsquo;s Claws, Dragon Skull, and [Event] Demoros&amp;rsquo; Supply Box. Mysterious Intel pieces and Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 23일 업데이트 안내 (v84.05)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-05/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  데모로스의 룰렛(5인)  6/27(목) 점검 전까지 기간 한정으로 오픈됩니다. 65레벨, 장비 레벨 446 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 입장 시 모험의 주화가 145 소모되며, 주간 40회(VIP/월간패스 80회)까지 입장 가능합니다. 알레만시아 인근 &amp;lsquo;산 알레마 마을&#39;의 차원의 게이트를 통해 던전에 입장할 수 있습니다. 아르보레아의 금/은빛 판금, 이공간의 파편, 불길한 마법 스크롤, 낡은 보급품, 악마의 발톱, 용의 두개골, [이벤트] 데모로스의 낡은 상자 등의 보상을 획득할 수 있습니다. (기간 한정 이벤트 던전에서는 첩보 지도 조각, 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각이 드랍되지 않습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.16 patch notes (v84.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-04/</guid>
      <description>1. Other  Leaderboard  Extended current season by 7 days (5/9~6/13)    Bug fixes  Fixed issue in Gossamer Vault (hard) where certain last boss mechanics prevented voice lines from playing Fixed issue in Argaff Hatchery where a certain enemy pushed Brawlers that are blocking Fixed issue in Argaff Hatchery where players could move inside of a certain enemy Fixed issue where event gear that maxes at +7 could be registered in enchant UI Fixed issue where registering pet bank skill to skillslot UI and moving the skill to another slot displayed a default skill icon Fixed issue where players could go through certain objectives using Priest&amp;rsquo;s Divine Charge Fixed issue where premium slot items did not rest occasionally Fixed issue where certain items could be stored in bank and guild bank Fixed issue where rested XP stacked differently than intended (수정) 휴식 경험치 획득 방식이 몬스터 처치 시 획득 경험치를 기준으로 적용되지 않고 있던 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 16일 업데이트 안내 (v84.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-04/</guid>
      <description>1. 기타  던전/전장 순위표  5시즌 진행 기간이 7일 연장됩니다. (5/9 ~ 6/13)    [버그수정]  찬란한 파르퀴나의 둥지 던전에서 2네임드가 특정 패턴 사용 시 대사가 출력되지 않는 문제 아르가프 부화장의 황금 유충이 방어 중인 권술사를 밀어내는 문제 아르가프 부화장의 황금 유충의 배에 캐릭터가 묻히는 문제 7강화 몽환의 장갑, 신발 아이템을 강화 UI에 등록할 수 있는 문제 펫 보관함을 스킬 슬롯에 등록 후 슬롯 변경 시 더미 이미지가 출력되는 문제 사제 혼신의 주문 사용 시 일부 오브젝트를 뚫고 이동할 수 있는 문제 66레벨 이상부터 특성 공격력 증가 효과가 적용되지 않는 문제 간헐적으로 프리미엄 슬롯 아이템이 초기화되지 않는 문제 길드 창고 보관 가능, 계정 창고 보관 불가 속성의 아이템을 길드 창고에 보관할 수 없는 문제 휴식 경험치 중첩 방식이 사양과 다르게 적용되고 있던 문제 (수정) 휴식 경험치 획득 방식이 몬스터 처치 시 획득 경험치를 기준으로 적용되지 않고 있던 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.09 patch notes (v84.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Balance  Slayer  Overhand Strike: Focus  Adjusted to increased skill damage increase per stack from 1% to 2% (max stack from 15% to 30%)   Propulsion  Changed requirement to decrease cooldown of Measured Slice from &amp;lsquo;upon critical hit&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;upon hit&amp;rsquo; with Whirlwind   Punishing Blow  Increased skill damage by 10%      2. Content  Nomadic Caiman &amp;amp; Argaff Hatchery  Adjusted to increase chance to spawn Nomadic Caiman or Dimensional Door by 4 times Adjusted to decrease XP gained from defeating Nomadic Caiman Adjusted to decrease XP and skill advancement XP gained from defeating Hatchery monsters   Argaff Scout Intel  Changed Doubtful Intel piece to drop in the following dungeons  From Doubtful Intel (Left) to Doubtful Intel (Right)  Red Refuge RK9-Kennel Dark Reach Citadel Velik&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary Shadow Sanguinary Grotto of Lost Souls Ruinous Manor Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss     Changed Doubtful Intel piece to drop from the following monsters  From Doubtful Intel (Left) to either Doubtful Intel (Left) or Doubtful Intel (Right) (by chance)  List of 28 level 65-70 monsters  그림자 경계병 철갑가시 오칸 병든 롱터스크 불타는 유적 길리두 성역의 파수꾼 오염된 롱터스크 오염된 뿌리약탈자 폐허 파괴자 알쿠스 부활의 나무 오염된 볼칸 야수의 숲 볼칸 폐허를 방황하는 악마 시간의 수호자 오염된 뿌리약탈자 아둔한 장물꾼 사막 바실리스크 푸른이끼부족 예언가 파르프 비열한 도굴꾼 폐허 하이에나 푸른이끼부족 주술사 파르폰 둥근 부리 파수꾼 검은불꽃 알쿠스 푸른이끼부족 전사 폭주한 황금 정원사 낡은 거인의 하수꾼 고블린 도둑          3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 09일 업데이트 안내 (v84.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-03/</guid>
      <description>###1. 밸런스
 무사  일도양단: 집중  일도양단: 집중 중첩 당 상승되는 모든 스킬의 위력이 1%에서 2%로 상향 조정됩니다. (최대 중첩 시 15% -&amp;gt; 30%)   추진력  일섬 스킬의 재사용 대기시간 감소 조건이 회전 베기 &amp;lsquo;치명타 적중 시&#39;에서 &amp;lsquo;적중 시&#39;로 변경됩니다.   참격  스킬 위력이 기존대비 10% 상향됩니다.      [개발자 코멘트]
 추진력 패시브 변경을 통해 치명타 의존도를 감소시켰습니다. 이를 통해 회전 베기 치명타 여부에 따라 딜사이클이 자주 변경되어 무사의 난이도가 높아지는 문제를 완화하고자 하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.02 patch notes (v84.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Other  Changed path guide in Necromancer&amp;rsquo;s Tomb (1-man) Changed certain level progression instances to reset automatically upon re-entering the instance for convenience  Quest progression is adjusted accordingly Instances of the following quest are reset automatically :  Quest  1507 ???? (전염병의 원인을 찾아서) 2501 Secrets Not Meant to Be Known 2801 Vision of Destiny 3901 Unveil the Mask 401 Rescue the Core 5601 Drowned In Blood 5602 Sikander&amp;rsquo;s Bane 3702 Fragment of Hope 5201 Into the Furnace 17207 The Battle for Intrepid       Decreased chance of getting Banana Peel from Weird Sack (placeholder) from 50% to 20% for Stolen Cure quest  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 02일 업데이트 안내 (v84.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 기타  사령술 연구소(1인) 던전 길찾기 가이드가 변경됩니다. 성장구간 퀘스트 진행 중 초기화되지 않으면 진행이 어려운 특수 공간들에 대해 재입장 시 자동으로 초기화되도록 변경됩니다.  특수공간 초기화에 맞춰 퀘스트도 진행하기 좋은 단계로 재설정됩니다. 특수공간 리스트는 아래와 같습니다.  퀘스트명 | 지역명  전염병의 원인을 찾아서 | 호송대 습격지 잊혀져야 하는 힘 | 고통의 전당 태고신의 파편 | 생명의 샘 가면을 벗겨라 | [툴사의 군단 지휘소, 말라키의 실험실] 코어 구출 작전 | 폭염의 산맥 심층부 피의 기둥을 파괴하라 | 칠흑의 제단 켈사이크 부활 저지 | 부활의 성소 희망의 조각 | 광대의 별장 용광로 속으로 | 용암의 홀 초대하지 않은 손님 | 엘카이아호       &amp;lsquo;도둑맞은 치료제&amp;rsquo; 퀘스트의 수상한 자루에서 바나나 껍질이 등장할 확률이 감소됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.04.25 patch notes (v84.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  New: Azart Hatchery (1-man)  Can be entered through a warp hole randomly generated by defeating Nomadic Caiman and/or level 65 and/or above monsters/BAMs Loot table includes Skill Advancement XP and Naga Guard Chest (placeholder) (Blightoath gear, rare Halidom/Relic)  Nomadic Caiman     Nomadic Caiman spawns by defeating level 65 and/or above monsters from the following zones Loot table includes Skill Advancement XP and Worldly Crystal :  Location  Celestial Hills Essenian Crest Timeless Woods Balder&amp;rsquo;s Refuge Ex Prima Sienna Canyon Progression dungeon   Changed Relic Weapon drop to be class-relevant to the classes within party    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 04월 25일 업데이트 안내 (v84.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  신규: 아르가프 부화장(1인)  떠돌이 시누스 혹은 65레벨 이상 일반/중형 몬스터를 처치 시 확률적으로 차원문이 등장하며, 해당 차원문을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. [아르가프 부화장 컨텐츠 소개 GM노트] 던전 보상으로 스킬 연마 경험치, 나가 경비병의 소지품(녹슨 맹세의 장비, 희귀 성물/유물)을 획득할 수 있습니다.  떠돌이 시누스     아래 지역의 65레벨 이상 몬스터 처치 시 확률적으로 &amp;lsquo;떠돌이 시누스&#39;가 등장합니다. 보상으로 스킬 연마 경험치, 세계의 결정을 획득할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>