<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v58 on mysterium</title>
    <link>/mysterium/tags/v58/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v58 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/mysterium/tags/v58/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 04월 20일 업데이트 안내 (v58.02.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-02-01/</guid>
      <description>null  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017.04.13 patch notes (v58.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v58-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v58-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Akeron&#39;s Inferno (hard) - Significantly decreased the HP of 1/2/3/4th boss - Significantly decreased the HP of the mobs spawned at 2nd boss ### Bug fixes - Skill - Sorcerer : Fixed issue where changing certain chain skills in the skill UI did not apply - Berserker : Fixed issue where overcharging Thunderstrike and Cyclone resulted in collision with party members - Berserker : Talent fix - Dungeon - Fixed issue in Ruinous Velik&#39;s Temple where Joy of Partying was affected if a member of the party was dead when the 3rd boss was defeated - Cash shop - Fixed issue where Knight set box for Castanics was shown as Cestanics - Character - Fixed issue where the hair of Elin&#39;s 11th hairstyle would slightly fall off while walking or using a teleport scroll  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 04월 13일 업데이트 안내 (v58.02)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 오만한 아케론의 염옥 - 1/2/3/4 네임드의 HP가 대폭 하향됩니다. - 2 네임드와 전투 중 소환되는 부하 몬스터의 HP가 대폭 하향됩니다. ### [버그수정] - 스킬 - 마법사 일부 스킬의 이어지는 스킬의 옵션 설정 후 스킬UI 재 오픈 시 설정된 사항이 유지되지 않는 문제 - 광전사의 소용돌이, 모아치기 스킬을 자동 사용할 때까지 오버차징 후 사용 시 파티원과 충돌하는 문제 - 광전사의 소용돌이 스킬 사용 중 늑골 부수기를 2타까지 사용 시 소용돌기 [가속] 특성이 해제되지 않는 문제 - 던전 - 함락된 벨릭의 신전 3네임드를 일부 파티원이 사망한 상황에서 처치 시 확정 보상이 확정 드랍되지 않는 문제 - 부가서비스 - 나이츠 세트 박스의 구성품 중 케스타닉 전용 아이템 이름이 캐스타닉으로 출력되는 문제 - 캐릭터 - 엘린 종족 11번 프리셋 헤어로 걷기, 이동 주문서 사용 시 머리카락이 떨어져 보이는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 04월 06일 업데이트 안내 (v58.01.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-01-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 길드전 - 리카노르 투기장 내에서 길드전 전투를 할 수 없도록 변경됩니다. ### [버그수정] - 몬스터 - 일부 몬스터가 사망할 때 본래 위치보다 뒤쪽으로 순간이동하며 사망하는 문제 - UI - 파티 후 아이템 획득 시 주사위 굴림 UI에서 장비의 랜덤 옵션이 항상 동일한 옵션으로 출력되는 문제 - 프리셋을 저장하고 캐릭터 선택화면/접속종료 후 재접속 시 저장해둔 프리셋이 사라지는 문제 - 부가서비스 - 비치웨어 다이아몬드 컬렉션에서 획득 가능한 유니크 화이트 니삭스 스쿨린에 이름 변경권 사용이 불가능한 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017.03.30 patch notes (v58.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v58-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v58-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Manglemire reopened - 5 man party instance, with Instance Matching System available from ilvl 423 - Teleportal is located in Pora Elinu - Manglemire Teleport Scroll can be purchased from the Specialty Store - Tier 2 Lakan&#39;s jewelry, Visionmaker Rutheless (VM9) material, Dyad Niveot Structure, Tier 11 Feedstock, Masterwork/Personal Premium Alkahest, Goddess&#39; Tear, Diamond, etc can be obtained ### 2. Skill - Slayer - Combo Attack (1st hit) - Changed hit point to be race-equivalent - Slightly increased casting speed - Knockdown Strike - Changed hit point to be race-equivalent - Slightly increased casting speed - Cahnged to be queue-able before the end of the other [previous] skills - Increased skill damage by 10% - Whirlwind - Changed hit point to be race-equivalent - Slightly increased casting speed - Increased skill damage by 10% - Heart Thrust - Slightly increased skill radius - Changed skill to no longer collide with party members - Measured Slice - Changed skill to no longer collide with party members - Increased skill&#39;s base crit chance from 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 03월 30일 업데이트 안내 (v58.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v58-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 거짓말쟁이 타르스키의 놀이터가 재오픈 됩니다. - 5인 파티 던전이며, 장비 레벨 423 도달 시 서버간 파티매칭을 시도할 수 있습니다. - 입장용 차원의 마법석은 [포포리아 가드 &amp;gt; 포라 엘리누 &amp;gt; 마녀의 성]에 위치하고 있습니다. - 명품관에서 거짓말쟁이 타르스키의 놀이터 이동주문서를 구입하실 수 있습니다. - 탐욕스러운 라칸의 액세서리, 철기장 재료(냉혈), 아티팩트 원석 VII, 11단계 강화 재료, 완전한/진귀한 단련의 가루, 빛나는 여신의 눈물, 다이아몬드 등을 획득할 수 있습니다. ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>