<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Equipment on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Equipment on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>v108 : Mahtnan Gear</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v108-mahtnan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v108-mahtnan/</guid>
      <description>Mahtnan gear is the new gear set added v108, as part of a new season of TERA, namedly TERA : AWAKE.
Mahtnan gear differentiates itself from the previous Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul gear set by removing damage on enchant, and Infusion options. This makes it one of the easiest gear set to enchant due to the removal of artificial enchanting difficulty, but other factors have been added to make Mahtnan gear just as problematic as it was before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>v102 : Kaia&#39;s Soul Gear</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v102-kaiassoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v102-kaiassoul/</guid>
      <description>Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul gear is the retool for Kaia&amp;rsquo;s gear, added v102. It is available to upgrade from +15, and enchantment is available up to +9.
Upgrading Kaia&amp;rsquo;s gear (Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Fury / Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Wisdom) requires either Lumikan&amp;rsquo;s Wing Fragment or Tyrant&amp;rsquo;s Belt, obtained from Catalepticon and Killing Grounds, respectively. Random options, Infusion options, and Etchings are not inherited upon upgrading. Specifically, Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul gear upon upgrading starts with 0 Random options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>v91 : Kaia&#39;s Gear</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v91-kaia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v91-kaia/</guid>
      <description>Kaia&amp;rsquo;s gear is the retool for Annihilation / Dark Light gear, added v91. It is the first of the Mythical rarity gear, which therefore termed itself to be generally known as Mythical gear. It is available at all enchantment levels of Annihilation / Dark Light gear, and enchanting is still available after upgrading to Mythical gear.
One core equipment is necessary to retool superior Exodor gear into Mythical gear, which can be either a Black Core Essence, or Heroic Oath gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>v68 : Heroic Oath Gear (wip)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v69-heroicoath/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/equipment/v69-heroicoath/</guid>
      <description>Heroic Oath gear is the new gear set added v69, as a retool for Stormcry gear. It is available to upgrade at +9, and enchantment is available up to +3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>