<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 patch summary</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/summary/</guid>
      <description>January   v103.01
 New dungeon : Killing Grounds, Killing Grounds (hard) New dungeon : Catalepticon Trial Leaderboard : Removed Forbidden Arena Exodor : Removed restriction from using flight and jump platform Quest : Added quest skip function Partner : Revised to guarantee (100%) obtaining a Partner upon using an Evolution Core Partner : Revised Partner Fellowship increase rate and amount Battleground : Revised Gridiron Card Collection : Increase Card Fragment drop rate in all instances Card Collection : Decreased cost of Card Fragment Boxes in Specialty Merchant Card Collection : Significantly increased Selective Card Fusion rate Vanguard Initiative : Added level 70 [Daily] Vanguard Request Item : Added +9 passive effect to Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Armor / Hand Armor / Foot Armor Item : Changed Frost Monarch dragon-type mount active skill    v103.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.09.15 patch notes (v110.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-02/</guid>
      <description>*9/10 15:55 - 던전 항목이 업데이트 되었습니다. *9/10 14:29 - 길드대전 항목이 업데이트 되었습니다. Update 1. Dungeon  Increased Sky Cruiser Endeavor (hard) reward  Added 정제된 돌 재료 상자 (pl.) as additional reward  1 Essence is guaranteed with full Joy of Partying buff, and additional can be obtained at chance The following items can be obtained from 정제된 돌 재료 상자 (pl.) with equal chance         Listing Amount     Solar Essence 1   Lava Essence 1   Glacial Essence 1   Frost Essence 1   Lightning Essence 1    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.09.08 patch notes (v110.01.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-02/</guid>
      <description>*09/06 15:30 - 버그 수정 사항이 업데이트 되었습니다. Update 1. Service stabilization  서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다.  2. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.     아이템명 가격(블루) 판매 시작일 판매 종료일     [랜덤] 이세계의 퇴마사 의상 상자 40 2021-09-08 점검 후 2021-09-29 점검 전    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where unclaimed rewards from previous TERA Pass season is not parcelled Fixed issue where logging out while Manage Effect UI is open resets Manage Effect settings Fixed issue in Resonance Dungeon where damage is inflicted despite destroying tentacle cage within time limit  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.09.01 patch notes (v110.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilization  서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다.  2. Dungeon Resonance  Adjusted to decrease reflect damage amount Fixed to no longer apply reflect effect on Argon Solder in Corrupted Skynest (hard) Fixed issue where select mechanics activate abnormally when level 31 and above effect is applied in Corrupted Skynest (hard)  3. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.  Image not available</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.08.25 patch notes (v110.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v110-01/</guid>
      <description>*08/25 11:56 - 버그 수정 내역이 업데이트 되었습니다. *08/25 10:40 - 승리자의 증표 상점 보상 내역이 업데이트 되었습니다. *08/24 20:18 - 버그 수정 내역이 업데이트 되었습니다. *08/23 17:37 - 발키온 연합 지령서 추가 보상, 신규 악세서리 랜덤 옵션, 클래스 밸런스, T-cat 상점 신규 판매 상품 목록이 업데이트 되었습니다. Update 1. Resonance Dungeon  Resonance Dungeon phenomenon has occurred in Balderon  Resonated dungeons can only be entered through the Resonance Gate located in Balderon, Baldera       Resonance Dungeon content becomes available after completing &amp;lsquo;[중요] 던전 공명 현상 탐구&amp;rsquo; quest available at level 70         Two types of gates exist : Resonance Gate (left) and Bloody Resonance Gate (right) (instances available differ between the two gates) &amp;lsquo;Bloody Resonance Gate&amp;rsquo; offers content above higher difficulty (offers exclusive reward not available through the &amp;lsquo;Resonance Gate&#39;) Each gate differs in the available dungeons, maximum tier, and recommended item level         Gate Resonance Gate Bloody Resonance Gate     Tier 1~3 1~n   Dungeon Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum, Fusion Laboratory (hard) Corrupted Skynest (hard)   Recommended ilvl 504 510       Players can interact with the Resonance Gate (default : F) to enter         Players can enter Resonance Dungeon by clicking Teleport (can enter as a 5-Person Party) Successfully completing the challenge opens higher levels to challenge inBloody Resonance Gate Players require an entrance item to enter (consumed per Party Member)         Resonance Gate entrance item Bloody Resonance Gate entrance item               Resonance Stone can be obtained from level 65 and above instances Resonance Stone is only usable during its appropriate season (AWAKE Resonance Stone can only be used during AWAKE season)   Entering a Resonance Dungeon starts a timer         Reward is distributed by clearing the instance within the time limit, nevertheless the minimum reward is distributed by defeating the boss monster after exceeding the time limit  Resonance Dungeon does not distribute loot reward, but distributes either success reward or fail reward   Resonance Effect (pl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.08.18 patch notes (v109.02.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Increased Forge Fragment drop amount upon defeating boss monster in Damned Citadel by 1.5 times Increased Power Fragment drop amount upon defeating boss monster in Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold by 1.5 times  2. Vanguard Request  Changed AWAKE Token distribution upon completing Vanguard Request of select dungeons     Vanguard Request AWAKE Token (before) AWAKE Token (after)     Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum 17 25   Fusion Laboratory (hard) 17 25   Sky Cruiser Endeavor 17 25   Stormed Citadel 9 10   Fusion Laboratory 9 10   Grotto of Lost Souls (hard) 9 10   Catalepticon 9 4   Draakon Arena 5 4   Damned Citadel 3 4   Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold 3 4    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.08.11 patch notes (v109.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-02/</guid>
      <description>* 2021/08/09 16:58 - 던전 공명 업데이트 일정이 조정되었습니다. Update 1. Resonance Dungeon  던전 공명 업데이트가 시스템의 안정성 확보를 위해 8월 25일로 연기되었습니다. 더욱 원활한 플레이 환경과 완성된 모습으로 선보일 수 있도록 노력하겠습니다. Resonance Dungeon phenomenon has occurred in Balderon  Resonated dungeons can only be entered through the Resonance Gate located in Balderon, Baldera       Resonance Dungeon content becomes available after completing &amp;lsquo;[중요] 던전 공명 현상 탐구&amp;rsquo; quest available at level 70         Two types of gates exist : Resonance Gate (left) and Bloody Resonance Gate (right) (instances available differ between the two gates) &amp;lsquo;Crimson Resonance Gate&amp;rsquo; offers content above highest difficulty (offers exclusive reward not available through the &amp;lsquo;Resonance Gate&amp;rsquo;) Each gate differs in the available dungeons, maximum tier, and recommended item level         Gate Resonance Gate Bloody Resonance Gate     Tier 1~3 1~n   Dungeon Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum, Fusion Laboratory (hard) Corrupted Skynest (hard)   Recommended ilvl 504 510       Players can interact with the Resonance Gate (default : F) to enter         Players can enter Resonance Dungeon by clicking Teleport (can enter as a 5-Person Party) Successfully completing the challenge opens higher levels to challenge Players require an entrance item to enter (consumed per Party Member)         Resonance Gate entrance item Bloody Resonance Gate entrance item               Resonance Stone can be obtained from level 65 and above instances Resonance Stone is only usable during its appropriate season (AWAKE Resonance Stone can only be used during AWAKE season)   Entering a Resonance Dungeon starts a timer         Reward is distributed by clearing the instance within the time limit, nevertheless the minimum reward is distributed by defeating the boss monster after exceeding the time limit  Resonance Dungeon does not distribute loot reward, but distributes either success reward or fail reward   Resonance Effect (pl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.08.04 patch notes (v190.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilization  서버 렉 현상 완화를 위한 안정화 작업이 진행되었습니다.  2. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.  Image not available
Bug fixes  Fixed issue where &amp;lsquo;Lucidity&amp;rsquo; Unique Option on Mahtnan gear does not apply Fixed issue where Reaper&amp;rsquo;s Shadow Reaping Glyph and Skill Option effect does not apply Fixed issue where dungeon boss monster&amp;rsquo;s damage range and system damage range does not match Fixed issue where graphics downgrade in select location in Spring Valley Fixed issue where Vanguard Request for Sky Cruiser Endeavor (hard) is available at lower item level Fixed issue where unachievable Achievement is in Achievements Fixed issue where leaving Ace Dungeons after entering in Baldera spawns player in Highwatch 아룬의샘 중요 퀘스트 중 슈리안 안내자 관련 퀘스트를 여러 명이 동시에 진행할 수 없는 문제 Fixed issue where skill and chat occasionally are not available while playing Mystic  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.07.28 patch notes (v109.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v109-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 공명 던전 업데이트가 시스템의 안정성 확보를 위해 8월 11일로 연기되었습니다. 더욱 원활한 플레이 환경과 완성된 모습으로 선보일 수 있도록 노력하겠습니다. 1. Open world  Opened Undiscovered region - Baldera  Baldera can be accessed through &amp;lsquo;Ruinweald&amp;rsquo; located North of Arcadia &amp;gt; Oblivion Woods       Activity level is set to level 71 in Baldera and level 70 is recommended A town called Balderon exists in Baldera, and new achievements, adventure, and story can begin       Baldera              Balderon           2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.07.21 patch notes (v108.02.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Increased enchanting material drop amount in select instances  Damned Citadel  1 Forge Fragment -&amp;gt; 2 Forge Fragment   Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold  1 Power Fragment -&amp;gt; 2 Power Fragment      2. Achievement  Changed select achievements to Legacy Achievements  Moved to Legacy Achievements       Content Achievement name Achievement category     Stormed Citadel Call this Work-Life Balance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.07.14 patch notes (v108.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Reopened dungeon : Draakon Arena (5-Person instance)     Draakon Arena      Entry limit 2 entries daily (4 entries with VIP)   Adventure Coin 400   Entry level 69   Matching level 501       Adjusted to decrease HP and attack balance overall appropriate to medium-tier difficulty, adjusted the following mechanics  Tonfa throwing mechanic no longer applies Silence abnormality upon hit Decreased stun duration of Leaping Strike skill upon getting hit Significantly decreased damage of key mechanics that dealt enough damage to kill on 1 hit   Difficulty and key reward :       Difficulty Dungeon Entry limit Adventure Coin Key reward     Medium Draakon Arena ilvl 501 400 Rare Halidom / Relic II Token       Skill Advancement Scroll       Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare)       Mahtnan Gear Crate (Legendary)       Murky Mahtnan Powder Chest       Mahtnan Option Change Scroll       Warlord&amp;rsquo;s Earring / Circlet       Weapon Etching : Energetic IV       Armor Etching : Grounded IV       Mahtnan Gear Design Box (Mythical)         *Key reward : only a select few key rewards are listed, and not all reward items are listed   Vanguard Initiative Request       Vanguard Request Reward (up to 16 times daily) Additional reward (once daily)     Complete Draakon Arena XP : 33,000,000 Mahtnan Ash : 2    Gold : 2,250     Vanguard Initiative credit : 40     EP XP : 1,518     Dragonscale : 1     Noctenium Infusion : 25     Skill Advancement Stone : 4     AWAKE Token : 3        Entry  Teleportal is located at Verrak Fortress Abyss of Verrak Fortress, with access via Dungeon Teleportal Scroll from Exodor Specialty Store, Vanguard Request dungeon entrance teleport, or through Instance Matching   Added new achievements to match reopening of the dungeon, and re-categorized select existing achievements and changed to Legacy Achievement   Adjusted Fusion Laboratory (hard) balance and reward  Increased laser attack damage from exterior drones to secondary aggro target  Displays a message before the attack to give 2 seconds time to evade (both normal / hard mode)   Increase exterior &amp;lsquo;터져라&amp;rsquo; AoE mechanic range Adjusted attack range of the 4 second-duration red laser mechanic Changed lightning mechanic and red laser mechanic to chain Increased damage of in-out / out-in pulse AoE mechanic Added &amp;lsquo;Murky Mahtnan Powder&amp;rsquo; to drop table upon defeating boss monster   Revised Fusion Laboratory effect (both normal / hard mode)  Fixed select effects to resolve issues of eyestrain from effects and mechanics that were difficult to recognize  Changed laser color and effect from drones Changed border-side color and effect Changed boss monster&amp;rsquo;s AoE color and effect Reinforced visibility of other boss monster skill and effect     Changed drop item of select dungeons :     Dungeon Before After     Abscess Mahtnan Hand Armor Crate (Rare) Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare)   Akalath Quarantine Mahtnan Foot Armor Crate (Rare) Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare)   Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold Mahtnan Armor Crate (Rare) Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare)   Damned Citadel Mahtnan Weapon Crate (Rare) Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare)     Adjusted to decrease boss monster difficulty in Stormed Citadel  Adjusted to decrease casting speed of select skills Adjusted to decrease attack of jump-in-spot attack Decreased duration of 정신착란 및 혼란 이상상태의 지속시간이 짧아집니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.07.07 patch notes (v108.01.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Added new instance : Fusion Laboratory (hard) (5-person dungeon)  Difficulty and key reward       Difficulty Dungeon Entry limit Adventure Coin Key reward     Higher Fusion Laboratory (hard) ilvl 510 400 Superior Halidom / Relic II Token       Mahtnan Gear Create (Legendary)       Mahtnan Gear Create (Mythical)       Etching IV (earring, brooch)       Greedy Mahtnan Option Change Scroll       Greedhead&amp;rsquo;s Option Change Scroll (Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Mask / Belt / Brooch)       Wind Earring Resizing Stone       Earth Circlet Resizing Stone       Mahtnan Jewel       Mahtnan Ash       Hero&amp;rsquo;s Crystal       Vanguard Initiative Request       Dungeon Vanguard reward (up to 16 times daily) Additional reward (daily)     Fusion Laboratory (hard) XP : 100,000,000 Mahtnan Ash : 4    Gold : 6,000 AWAKE Token : 3    VG credit : 100     EP XP : 1,518     Dragonscale : 1     Noctenium Infusion : 100     AWAKE Token : 17        Entry  Teleportal is located at Verrak Fortress, with access via Dungeon Teleportal Scroll sold from Exodor Specialty Store, Vanguard Request dungeon entrance teleport, or through Instance Matching     Fusion Laboratory  Fixed select effect to settle eyestraining effects and mechanics difficult to perceive  A second revision is scheduled on 7/14 patch update     Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum (added 7/6)  Adjusted balance of phase 2 of Bahaar  Changed to be able to resist knockback when a shield effect is applied to character during [Feel my wrath] mechanic Increased damage of fury wave mechanic      Developer comment 핵심 패턴의 탱커 클래스 간 형평성 문제 바하르 2페이즈에서, [내 분노는 지금부터 시작이다!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.07.02 patch notes (v108.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Item and gear  Adjusted to increase Mahtnan gear performance     Rarity Crit Factor Additional damage when attacking monsters Amplification and resistance increase upon enchanting PVP defense increase MP recovery option Maximum HP increase Maximum MP increase     Rare 10 per part Weapon : 10% 3% -&amp;gt; 6% Armor 35, Hand / Foot Armor 25 Armor : Recover 400 MP every 5 seconds Foot Armor : max HP +46141 (+18000 relatively) Hand armor : max MP +500   Superior 20 per part Weapon : 15% 3% -&amp;gt; 6% Armor 35, Hand / Foot Armor 25 Armor : Recover 400 MP every 5 seconds Foot Armor : max HP +46141 (+18000 relatively) Hand armor : max MP +500   Mythic 30 per part Weapon : 20% 3% -&amp;gt; 6% Armor 35, Hand / Foot Armor 25 Armor : Recover 400 MP every 5 seconds Foot Armor : max HP +46141 (+18000 relatively) Hand armor : max MP +500       Added Crit Factor value per part Added additional damage when attacking monsters option to weapon Increased amplification and resistance increase upon enchanting from 3% to 6% Added PVP defense increase to armor, hand armor, and foot armor Added MP recovery option to armor Added maximum HP increase value to foot armor Added maximum MP increase option to hand armor    Developer comment 마흐트난 장비의 기본 스펙을 상승시키고, 해방된 카이아 장비에서 준 필수 옵션들을 계승하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.06.30 patch notes (v108.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v108-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Added new dungeon : Fusion Laboratory (5-Person instance)     Fusion Laboratory      Entry limit None   Adventure Coin 280   Entry level 70   Matching item level 504       Completion reward  Option lock material, Option Boost Scroll, Mahtnan Gear Crate, Mahtnan gear enchanting material, Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Belt, Etching material, Superior Halidom / Relic, Card Fragment   Entry method  Teleportal is located at Verrak Fortress, with access via Dungeon Teleportal Scroll sold from Exodor Specialty Store, Vanguard Request dungeon entrance teleport, or through Instance Matching     Added remake instance : Stormed Citadel (5-Person instance)     Encroached Damned Citadel      Entry limit None   Adventure Coin 280   Entry level 70   Matching item level 504       Completion reward  Option lock material, Option Boost Scroll, Mahtnan Gear Crate, Mahtnan gear enchanting material, Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Mask, Etching material, Superior Halidom / Relic, Card Fragment   Entry method  Teleportal is located at Plaza of the Mighty, Val Aureum, with access via Dungeon Teleportal Scroll sold from Specialty Store, Vanguard Request dungeon entrance teleport, or through Instance Matching     Updated Ace Dungeons and Echoes of Aranea reward appropriate to the new gear update  Removed Kaia&amp;rsquo;s gear-related reward, changed to Mahtnan gear and Skill Advancement-related reward   Proceeded with dungeon redistribution  Added and closed select instances  Removed Story quest related to closed instances Added new achievements, recategorized existing achievements and changed select achievement to Legacy Achievements appropriate to the newly distributed instances          Removed instances      Gossamer Vault Ruinous Manor Akalath Quarantine [Conquest]   Catalepticon Killing Grounds Draakon Arena   Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord] Corrupted Skynest Ruinous Manor (hard)   Killing Grounds (hard) Catalepticon (hard) Corrupted Skynest (hard)   Rampaging RK-9 Kennel Commander&amp;rsquo;s Residence -        Operating instances      Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum Fusion Laboratory Stormed Citadel   Grotto of Lost Souls (hard) Damned Citadel Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold   Akalath Quarantine Abscess -       Key dungeon reward and Adventure Coin cost upon entry is the following :       Difficulty Instance Entry limit Adventure Coin Key reward     Low Abscess ilvl 498 175 Rare Halidom / Relic I Token, Skill Advancement Scroll, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare), Warlord&amp;rsquo;s Ring, Handwear Etching : Energetic IV   &#39;&amp;rsquo; Akalath Quarantine &#39;&amp;rsquo; &#39;&amp;rsquo; Rare Halidom / Relic I Token, Skill Advancement Scroll, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare), Warlord&amp;rsquo;s Necklace, Footwear Etching : Grounded IV   Medium Damned Citadel ilvl 501 200 Rare Halidom / Relic II Token, Skill Advancement Scroll, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare), Mahtnan Gear Crate (Legendary), Warlord&amp;rsquo;s Earring, Weapon Etching : Energetic IV, Mahtnan&amp;rsquo;s Option Change Scroll, Forge Fragment   &#39;&amp;rsquo; Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold &#39;&amp;rsquo; &#39;&amp;rsquo; Rare Halidom / Relic II Token, Skill Advancement Scroll, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare), Mahtnan Gear Crate (Legendary), Warlord&amp;rsquo;s Circlet, Armor Etching : Grounded IV, Mahtnan&amp;rsquo;s Option Change Scroll, Power Fragment   High Stormed Citadel ilvl 504 280 Superior Halidom / Relic I Token, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare), Mahtnan Gear Crate (Legendary), Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Mask, Mahtnan&amp;rsquo;s Option Change Scroll, various Essences, Mahtnan Gear Design Box (Mythical), Mahtnan Jewel, Mahtnan Ash, Blacksmith&amp;rsquo;s Token   &#39;&amp;rsquo; Core Reactor &#39;&amp;rsquo; &#39;&amp;rsquo; Superior Halidom / Relic I Token, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare), Mahtnan Gear Crate (Legendary), Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Belt, Mahtnan&amp;rsquo;s Option Change Scroll, various Essences, Mahtnan Gear Design Box (Mythical), Mahtnan Jewel, Mahtnan Ash, Tough Nut Token   &#39;&amp;rsquo; Grotto of Lost Souls (hard) &#39;&amp;rsquo; &#39;&amp;rsquo; Superior Halidom / Relic I Token, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Rare), Mahtnan Gear Crate (Legendary), Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Brooch, Mahtnan&amp;rsquo;s Option Change Scroll, various Essences, Mahtnan Gear Design Box (Mythical), Mahtnan Jewel, Mahtnan Ash, Token of Vigour   Highest Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum ilvl 510 400 Superior Halidom / Relic II Token, Mahtnan Gear Crate (Legendary), Mahtnan Gear Crate (Mythical), accessory Etching IV (ring necklace), Greedy Mahtnan Option Change Scroll, Mahtnan Gear Design Box (Mythical), Mahtnan Jewel, Mahtnan Ash, Forge Crystal       [Dungeon] Vanguard Initiative Request list and reward is the following (added 6/29) :       Name Difficulty XP Gold Vanguard Credit EP XP Dragonscale Noctenium Infusion Skill Advancement Token AWAKE Token Additional reward     Abscess Low 250,000,000 1,500 30 1,518 1 20 2 0 1 Mahtnan Ash, 1 Skill Advancement Tome (Extra-Large)   Akalath Quarantine Low 250,000,000 1,500 30 1,518 1 20 2 0 1 Mahtnan Ash, 1 Skill Advancement Tome (Extra-Large)   Damned Citadel Medium 33,000,000 2,250 40 1,518 1 25 4 3 2 Mahtnan Ash   Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold Medium 33,000,000 2,250 40 1,518 1 25 4 3 2 Mahtnan Ash   Stormed Citadel High 100,000,000 3,300 75 1,518 1 75 0 9 2 Mahtnan Ash   Fusion Laboratory High 100,000,000 3,300 75 1,518 1 75 0 9 3 Mahtnan Ash, 1 Accessory Resizing Stone Box (Random)   Grotto of Lost Souls (hard) High 100,000,000 3,300 75 1,518 1 75 0 9 3 Mahtnan Ash, 1 Accessory Resizing Stone Box (Random)   Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum Highest 100,000,000 6,000 100 1,518 1 100 0 17 3 Mahtnan Ash, 1 Accessory Resizing Stone Box (Random)   Fusion Laboratory Highest 100,000,000 6,000 100 1,518 1 100 0 17 4 Mahtnan Ash, 3 AWAKE Token    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.06.23 patch notes (v107.02.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Item  Changed to be able to discard 1-day Summer Festival style cosmetic  3. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.  (TERA KR exclusive additional sale listing)
 6/30(수) 점검 이후부터 7/28(수) 점검 전까지 테라 샵에서 아래 상품들이 여름 특별 할인으로 가격이 일시 조정될 예정입니다.  (TERA KR exclusive discount sale listing)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.06.16 patch notes (v107.02.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Event (TERA KR exclusive)  던전 드랍 확률 1.5배 증가 이벤트가 진행됩니다.  기간: 2021년 6월 16일 점검 이후 ~ 2021년 6월 23일 점검 전까지   강화 성공 확률 2배 증가 이벤트가 진행됩니다.  기간: 2021년 6월 16일 점검 이후 ~ 2021년 6월 20일 23:59까지    3. Homepage (TERA KR exclusive)  Activated ranking system on main website  홈페이지 -&amp;gt; 순위 메뉴를 통해 확인해 보실 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.06.09 patch notes (v107.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Summer Festival  Summer Festival begins  Completing guide quests per festival unlocks daily quests to obtain [Summer Festival Coin]  Beach Party               Guide quest [Event] Life&amp;rsquo;s a Beach   Quest level requirement Lv.48   Festival location Serpentis Isle - Boan Strand region   Daily quests Splash Cannon Mini-Game, Melon Bash Mini-Game, Sand Castles in The Sand, The Horn Carver&amp;rsquo;s Concerns, Beauty at the Beach, Ramsay&amp;rsquo;s New Hobby   Item obtained 2021 Summer Festival Coin           15 [2021 Summer Festival Coin] can be obtained per character via Beach Party festival   Festival of the Sun               Guide quest [태양의 축제] 지혜의 나무로   Quest level requirement Lv.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.06.02 patch notes (v107.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Services  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.     아이템명 가격(블루) 판매 시작일 판매 종료일     [랜덤] 돌아온 밀리터리 코스튬x연합 의장복 상자 40 2021-06-02 점검 후 2021-06-23 점검 전   [랜덤] 돌아온 핫! 토끼 스타일 상자 40 2021-06-02 점검 후 2021-06-23 점검 전   [랜덤] 신비한 파트너 상자 55 2021-06-02 점검 후 상시 판매    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.05.26 patch notes (v107.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v107-01/</guid>
      <description>Developer comment Addition update on new gear release together with a class balance is in preparation. key detail in preparation is, for each class, stat-related passive revision, skill damage and effect adjustment, and select skill revision and addition. through these changes, we hope to match the necessary balance between classes that were not applied in this balance update, so please stay tuned for more information. Update 1. Combat balance  Berserker  Unleash  Unleashed: Sinister, Unleashed: Dexter  Increase skill damage by 20% Changed 폭주 : 강화 효과 stack limit to 7 Changed damage increase per 폭주 : 강화 효과 stack from 5~10% -&amp;gt; 8~14%   Unleashed: Rampage  Changed 야수의 돌진 강화 효과 stack limit to 7 Changed damage increase per 야수의 돌진 강화 효과 stack from 5~10% -&amp;gt; 8~14%   Unleashed: Beast Fury  Changed cooldown duration from 10s -&amp;gt; 8s   Unleash  Increased skill damage by 30%   Cyclone  Changed stagger effect to players to apply on 1st, 2nd, 3rd hit   Bloodlust  Skill level 1  Increased skill damage increase upon successful hit on monsters from 10% -&amp;gt; 12%   Skill level 2  Increased skill damage increase upon successful hit on monsters from 10% -&amp;gt; 15%     Flatten  Increased skill damage by 15%   Vampiric Blow  Increased skill damage by 15%   Tackle  Increased skill damage by 20%        Developer comment Unleash-related skill and Bloodlust skill adjustments - Regarding the Berserker class, we realized there was a risk due to the lack of utility while using Unleash, especially in the current meta where frequency repositioning is necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.05.20 patch notes (v106.02.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Event  Changed Undying Warlord and Tyrant cosmetic items received from event, including ones already received, to no longer be able to dismantle  3. Services  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.     아이템명 가격(블루) 판매 시작일 판매 종료일     [랜덤] 반짝반짝 황금빛 코이노보리 상자 55 2021-05-18 00:00 2021-06-09 점검 전   [랜덤] 흩날리며 타오르는 꽃의 유카타 상자 40 2021-05-18 00:00 2021-06-09 점검 전   [랜덤] 돌아온 태양신 발더의 무기 상자(10+1) 400 2021-05-21 00:00 2021-06-02 점검 전   [랜덤] 돌아온 태양신 발더의 무기 상자 40 2021-05-21 00:00 2021-06-02 점검 전    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where select box items with time duration could be duplicated Fixed issue where Multi-Nostrum added on Monthly Pass was displayed in PC Bang benefits  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.05.12 patch notes (v106.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Item  Changed item properties of superior Halidom / Relic  Cannot be stored in storage -&amp;gt; can be stored in storage Bind of pickup -&amp;gt; bind on equip    3. TERA Pass  Revised to update TERA Pass UI upon using TERA Pass item while UI is open  4. Services  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.05.06 patch notes (v106.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Non-migrated account data deletion  2021년 4월 30일까지 이관하지 않은 계정의 데이터를 삭제 처리하는 작업을 진행합니다.  2021년 4월 30일까지 이관하지 않은 계정 정보는 모두 삭제되며 계정 정보 복구가 불가합니다. 2021년 4월 30일까지 이관하지 않은 계정 정보는 추가 이관 또는 수동 이관 지원이 불가합니다. 2021년 5월 6일 정기점검 이후 미이관 계정에 포함된 캐릭터 이름은 재사용할 수 있으며, 게임 내 컨텐츠에 삭제된 캐릭터 이름이 등록되어 있을 경우 “다른 차원의 수호자”로 표기됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.04.28 patch notes (v106.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Battleground  Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold  Tanks  Adjusted to increase damage Adjusted to increase HP Adjusted to increase movement speed   Sieges  Adjusted to increase damage Adjusted to increase HP   Platform-based sieges  Increased damage range to reach Outer Gates Adjusted to increase damage to Gates Adjusted to decrease HP   Ships  Adjusted to increase HP   Fraywind Canyon  Adjusted to decrease maximum number of healers from 5 to 3   Added skill effect to equalized gear distribution Brooch  Revised to be able to register in a skill slot Added skill to disable abnormalities (3 minute cooldown)      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.04.21 patch notes (v105.02.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilization  Proceeded with overall structural stabilization to minimize server instability  2. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.     아이템명 가격(블루) 판매 시작일 판매 종료일     [랜덤] 스쿨룩 컬렉션 상자 40 2021-04-21 점검 후 2021-05-12 점검 전   [랜덤] 뚠뚠 드래곤 펫 상자 40 2021-04-21 점검 후 2021-05-12 점검 전   [랜덤] 돌아온 프레이아의 골든 글로리 웨폰 박스 40 2021-04-21 점검 후 2021-05-12 점검 전    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where &amp;lsquo;Lie Like a Rug&amp;rsquo; Collection Effect is not removed upon entering Pit of Petrax  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.04.14 patch notes (v105.02.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilization (TERA KR exclusive)  서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다.  2. Dungeon  Adjusted to decrease the drop amount of Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Tokenm in the following instances :     Dungeon      Akalath Quarantine [Gauntlet] Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord]   Corrupted Skynest Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum   Draakon Arena Ruinous Manor (hard)     Reopened Akalath Quarantine [Gauntlet] that was temporarily closed  3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.04.07 patch notes (v105.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Added new : [Ace Dungeon] Gardan&amp;rsquo;s Trial     [Ace Dungeon] Gardan&amp;rsquo;s Trial      Entry limit 2 daily, 3 with VIP   Adventure Coin 400   Level requirement 70   Instance Matching requirement -     Loot table includes Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Token, superior Halidom / Relic, enchanting materials, and Soul Option Change Scroll Added Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Token to Ace Dungeon - Lumikan&amp;rsquo;s Trial Added a chance to drop Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Gear Box to level 66 and above instances  Opening said box results in gear appropriate to your class       Dungeons with added dropitem      Gossamer Vault Corrupted Skynest   Ruinous Manor Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord]   Akalath Quarantine Catalepticon (hard)   Akalath Quarantine [Gauntlet] Killing Ground (hard)   Damned Citadel Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum   Catalepticon Ruinous Manor (hard)   Killing Ground Corrupted Skynest (hard)   Draakon Arena Rampaging RK-9 Kennel    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.03.31 patch notes (v105.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Service stabilizaton  서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다.  2. Services  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. 판매 상품: [랜덤] 엘린의 시크릿 박스 상품 판매 가격: 55블루 판매 기간: 2021년 3월 31일(수) 점검 후 ~ 2021년 4월 14일(수) 점검 전 2021년 3월 31일(수)부터 아래의 펫 및 일부 부속 아이템의 가격이 인하될 예정으로, 사전 안내드립니다.  ※ 아이템 구매 시 유의해 주시기 바랍니다.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.03.24 patch notes (v105.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v105-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Added remake instance : Damned Citadel     Damned Citadel      Entry limit No limit   Adventure Coin 200   Entry level 70   Matching item level 479     Loot table includes newly added equipments Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Fury / Wisdom Mask / Brooch / Belt Loot table also ihncludes enchanting materials, Card Fragment Box, Halidom / Relic, Unstable Option Change Scroll [Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Mask / Brooch / Belt], Card Fragment - Harnovog, and Card Fragment - Dark Reach Citadel Roof Reopened : Manglemire     Manglemire      Entry limit 2 entries daily, 4 entries with monthly vip   Adventure Coin 200   Entry level 66   Matching item level 479     Instance is opened temporarily, and rewards include event rewards and Card Fragment - Manglemore 자세한 사항은 추후 이벤트 공지를 통해 안내해 드릴 예정입니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.03.17 patch notes (v104.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다.  2. 보상  3/10(수) 정기점검시 진행된, &amp;lsquo;사용처 소실 아이템 제거&amp;rsquo; 진행 중, 의도치 않게 삭제된 아이템을 다시 복구하였습니다. 3/17(수) 정기점검 이후, 해당 아이템 삭제로 인해 불편을 겪으신 수호자 여러분께 다음과 같은 보상이 우편으로 지급됩니다.     삭제된 아이템 명 보상 아이템 수량     마일리지 토큰 고급 카드 조각 상자 10   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; 여행자의 비약 5   승리의 증표 승리의 증표 100   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; 여행자의 비약 5    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.03.10 patch notes (v104.01.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Increased enchanting materials drop amount in the following instances :     Dungeon Reward Changelog     Catalepticon Lumikan&amp;rsquo;s Wing Fragment Increase drop amount by 2x   Catalepticon (hard) Lumikan&amp;rsquo;s Horn Piece Increase drop amount by 1.5x   Killing Ground Tyrant&amp;rsquo;s Belt Increase drop amount by 2x   Killing Ground (hard) Tyrant&amp;rsquo;s Soul Increase drop amount by 1.5x     Decreased HP of boss monster in Lumikan&amp;rsquo;s Trial (Ace Dungeon)  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.03.03 patch notes (v104.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Completed stage 1 of server stabilization process  2. Services (TERA KR exclusive)  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. 판매 상품: [랜덤] 아자작! 얼어붙은 할라트 무기 상품 판매 가격: 40블루 판매 기간: 2021년 3월 3일(수) 점검 후 ~ 2021년 3월 24일 8:59(점검 전까지)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.02.24 patch notes (v104.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v104-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Adjusted to increase solo dungeon difficulty and reward appropriate to the latest gear set  Pit of Petrax Celestial Arena Ace Trials Echo of Aranea    2. Item / gear  Changed sale value of rare / superior tier Relic / Halidom to 5 Gold Decreased Travel Journal reuse cooldown from 30 seconds to 10 seconds Changed item icon display by tier  Removed tier mark at top left corner Changed display tier via icon background and border color  Icon background color is initially applied to select items, and will be updated for all items in the future   Removed select items that are no useful Changed the following items to be tradable  *Changed fishing Bait type items to be tradable and limit is no longer applied Fish Fillet Bait I~V Angleworm I-V Puppy Figurine, Piglet Figurine, Popori FIgurine   Removed Puppy Figurine from Merchant Changed Golden / Silver Talent related Crafting Designs to no longer be usable Removed Sergheto Box from Development Merchant    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.02.09 patch notes (v103.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Adjusted Killing Grounds balance  Slightly decreased Attack of Gardan Slightly adjusted damage of ice puddle from the arena Decreased duration of ice puddle in Killing Grounds (hard) Decreased duration of silence abnormality imbued before Unleash mechanic and after leash mechanic in normal and hard mode Fixed to prevent frost release abnormality from ending upon death in normal and hard mode Fixed boss monster to become targetable a temporarily invincible moment before casating Unleash mechanic in normal and hard mode Fixed to prevent chained Giant to throw ice projectile during Unleash mechanic in normal and hard mode   Added &amp;lsquo;Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Token&amp;rsquo; to drop in High difficulty and above instances  Token exchange shop is of the following       New token Listing Token cost      - -   Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Token Marine Ring RStone 15   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Blazing Necklace RStone 15   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Wind Earring RStone 15   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Earth Circlet RStone 15   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Solar Stone 120   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Lava Stone 120   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Glacial Stone 120   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Frost Stone 120   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Lightning Stone 120   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Glorious Duranium Ore 50   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Glorious Duranium Crystal 50     Catalepticon (trial, normal mode, hard mode)  Fixed shield abnormality duration during skull mechanic from 4 seconds to 6 seconds   Catalepticon Trial  Revised instance&amp;rsquo;s Lancer NPC to display a guide message once skull mechanic starts Fixed shield abnormality to apply to Lancer NPC during skull mechanic Fixed to use shield mechanic once    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.02.03 patch notes (v103.01.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Decreased HP of boss monster in Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord] Adjusted to increase reward of the following instances     Dungeon Changelog     Draakon Arena Increase drop rate of Soul OCS, Increase drop rate of Warlord accessories, increase drop rate of Azart Force / Thulsan Legion War Trophy Chest   Corrupted Skynest &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;   Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord] &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.01.28 patch notes (v103.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-01-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Content schedule   Bamarama : Everyday 17:00 ~ 05:00
  ~~Daily quest : Everyday 07:00~
  Civil Unrest: Velika : Opens Sunday 18:00, starts 20:00
  Battleground : Refer to the table below
  Delayed due to issue where game time does not sync with designated time
  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where Velik&amp;rsquo;s Call quest can be cancelled to receive Endgame Package items repeatedly Fixed issue where 70 Glyph Points can be achieved by completing Velik&amp;rsquo;s Call quest and Apex awakening quests simultaneously Fixed issue where items on Calendar does not display properly Fixed issue where there is no portal out of Velik&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary FIxed issue in Killing Grounds where Gardan does not execute shield mechanic at 1% Fixed issue where renewed Endgame Package does not contain superior Glyph Box Fixed issue where characters have 70 Glyph Points instead of 65 Glyph Points Fixed issue where level 69 characters cannot use teleportal into Ruinous Manor and Akalath Quarantine  Item changes  Changed [Velik&amp;rsquo;s Call] to be available for users level 1-70, and added &amp;lsquo;Mystel&amp;rsquo;s Awakened Glyph Box&amp;rsquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.01.27 patch notes (v103.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v103-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Added new dungeon : Killing Grounds (5-Person)     Killing Grounds requirement      Entry limit No limit   Adventure Coin 280   Entry level 70   IMS ilevel 496       Killing Grounds (hard) requirement      Entry limit No limit   Adventure Coin 350   Entry level 70   IMS ilevel 501     Killing Grounds loot table includes :  Tyrant&amp;rsquo;s Belt, Card Fragment - Tyrant Gardan, Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Soul Cryolite, Thulsan Forces War Trophy Chest, Soul Option Change Scroll, Magic Alloy, Azart Force War Trophy Chest, Sea of Honor Voyage Map, superior Relic / Halidom, Common / Uncommon Card Fragment Box   Killing Grounds (hard) loot table includes :  Tyrant&amp;rsquo;s Soul, tier 4 brooch etching, Soul Greedhead&amp;rsquo;s Option Change Scroll, Magic Ingot, Sea of Honor Voyage Map, tier 2 superior Relic / Halidom, Common / Uncommon Card Fragment Box   Added one-time quest &amp;lsquo;[Dungeon - 496] [Party] Killing Grounds&amp;rsquo;, automatically acquired Added new instance : The Catalepticon Trial     The Catalepticon Trial requirement      Entry limit 2 daily   Adventure Coin 600   Entry level 70     Lumikan&amp;rsquo;s Wing Fragment is guaranteed to drop upon defeating the boss Lumikan&amp;rsquo;s Horn Piece, Soul Option Change Scroll, Magic Alloy, Azart Force War Trophy Chest, superior Relic / Halidom, and/or Common / Uncommon Card Fragment Box has a chance to drop upon defeating the boss Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord] changes  Changed to apply Neophyte Resurrection Decreased boss&amp;rsquo; Attack, Attack Speed, and HP Removed Accumulation abnormality applied when shield is broken Changed cooldown of select mechanics   The Catalepticon changes  Decreased camera shake effect Decreased boss&amp;rsquo; Attack, Attack Speed, and HP Decreased frequency of select mechanics Decreased recommended item level 498 &amp;gt; 494   The Catalepticon (hard) changes  Decreased camera shake effect Changed to remove select mechanic during cage mechanic   Draakon Arena changes  Decreased HP of boss monster Decreased recommended item level 498 &amp;gt; 496   Decreased difficulty of Draakon Arena (1-Person) instance related to quest  Decreased Attack of boss monster Changed to display attack radius of select mechanics Changed to apply abnormality to constantly replenish HP / MP of player   Increase drop count of &amp;lsquo;Improved Dark Shard Feedstock&amp;rsquo; in Gossamer vault, Ruinous Manor, Akalath Quarantine Changed to have a chance to drop &amp;lsquo;Kaia&amp;rsquo;s Cryolite&amp;rsquo; in all 5-Person instances of level 66 and above Added Soul Option Change Scroll [Hand / Foot Armor] as loot item to instances     Item (Hand / Foot Armor) Soul Unstable OCS Soul OCS Soul Greedhead OCS     Obtained from Gossamer Vault Catalepticon Catalepticon (hard)   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Ruinous Manor Killing Grounds Killing Grounds (hard)   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Akalath Quarantine Draakon Arena Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;  Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord] Corrupted Skynest (hard)   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;  Corrupted Skynest      Added Thulsan Forces Loot Chest to dungeon drop table  Thulsan Forces Loot Chest : Gives 1 &amp;lsquo;Tyrant&amp;rsquo;s Belt&amp;rsquo; Thulsan Forces War Trophy Chest : Gives 1 &amp;lsquo;Tyrant&amp;rsquo;s Soul&amp;rsquo;       Item Thulsan Legion Loot Crate Thulsan Legion War Trophy Chest     Obtained from Gossamer Vault Gossamer Vault   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Ruinous Manor Ruinous Manor   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Akalath Quarantine Akalath Quarantine   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;  Catalepticon   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;  Killing Grounds   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;  Draakon Arena   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;  Forbidden Arena [Undying Warlord]   &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;  Corrupted Skynest    2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>