<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 September suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/09/</guid>
      <description>+ : Suggestion accepted / in progress in the same or alternative form ? : Suggestion in review - : Suggestion rejected Item + Suggestion to fix Summon: Bay Gelding item distributed via event to be destroyable 10/13 패치로 ‘연합 보급품: 갈색 군마 소환 I’ 아이템이 파괴 가능으로 변경되었습니다.
+ Suggestion to change item properties of Murky Powder obtained from Ghillieglade to be able to store in Storage 11월까지는 적용 완료되는 것을 목표로 창고 보관 가능으로 변경하겠습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 August suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/08/</guid>
      <description>+ : Suggestion accepted / in progress in the same or alternative form ? : Suggestion in review - : Suggestion rejected System / UI - Suggestion to exclude play record via cross-server Instance Matching on Leaderboard 서버 교차 매칭 플레이 기록은 리더보드에서 제외하는 방향으로 내부 확인을 하였습니다만, 시스템적으로 리더보드를 등록 못하게 되면, 서버간 매칭 자체에도 문제가 생길 여지가 있어서 해당 건의 사항 대응은 진행을 보류하였습니다. 양해 부탁드립니다. While we did confirm internally in the direction of excluding cross-server Instance Matching play record from Leaderboard, there is a chance it might cause issues to the cross-server Instance Matching system itself if we systematically disable recording on Leaderboard so we have decided to withhold further progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 July suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/07/</guid>
      <description>+ : Suggestion accepted / in progress in the same or alternative form ? : Suggestion in review - : Suggestion rejected System / UI ? Suggestion to expand number of beneficial effect list of Manage Effect UI 이상 상태 관리 개수를 검토하여 늘리도록 하겠습니다.
+ Suggestion to prevent changing delivery listing even after maintenance (server restart) due to difficulty disposing fish caught before maintenance when Fish Delivery listing changes upon maintenance (server restart) 점검 이후에도 물고기 납품을 위한 낚시터가 변경되지 않도록 하겠습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 June suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/06/</guid>
      <description>+ : Suggestion accepted / in progress in the same or alternative form ? : Suggestion in review - : Suggestion rejected System / UI + Suggestion to make a party matching notification system 테라가 비활성화 되어있는 상태에서도 파티 매칭이 되면 알림이 될 수 있도록 하겠습니다.
아페만패에서 딜사이클 연습 중에 던전 매칭이 가능하도록 하겠습니다. We will update to be able to use dungeon instance matching while practicing skill rotation in Training Ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 May suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/05/</guid>
      <description>+ : Suggestion accepted / in progress in the same or alternative form ? : Suggestion in review - : Suggestion rejected System / UI + Suggestion to add a feature to toggle off other player&#39;s mount sound 4월 28일 업데이트를 통해 요청하신 기능을 추가했습니다.
+ Suggestion to add a name save feature to easily differentiate between different Card Collection slots 현재 프리셋 기능 개선을 계획하고 있습니다. 장비와 문장, 특성, 그리고 카드 등 선택가능한 다양한 옵션을 간단하게 스위칭할 수 있도록 구현을 준비하고 있으며, 추후 업데이트 시 공지를 통해 적용 시점을 안내 드리겠습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 April suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/04/</guid>
      <description>+ : Suggestion accepted / in progress in the same or alternative form ? : Suggestion in review - : Suggestion rejected System / UI + Suggestion to revise crafting time depending on item crafted 예전에는 제작 속도를 빠르게 해주는 아이템들이 있었으나, 현재는 구입처가 마땅하지 않은 것이 사실입니다. It is true that there have been item to speed up crafting, which are currently not quite available.
제작 시간은 제작하는 아이템의 수량에 의해 결정되는 현 시스템을 개편하도록 하겠습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 March suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/03/</guid>
      <description>+ : Suggestion accepted / in progress in the same or alternative form ? : Suggestion in review - : Suggestion rejected System / UI + Suggestion to add a Game Guide for new players 테라의 서비스 기간이 길어지다 보니, 각종 시스템과 컨텐츠의 복잡도가 높아지고 있는게 사실입니다. 특히나 신규 및 복귀로 테라를 플레이하고 계신 수호자님들께는 정보 획득이 또 하나의 허들이 될 수도 있을 것으로 생각합니다.
개발진은 이러한 정보의 불균형을 해소하기 위해 게임을 플레이하면서 자연스럽게 필요한 정보를 습득하고 안내 받을 수 있는 통합 가이드시스템을 개발 중에 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 February suggestions review result | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/suggestions/2021/02/</guid>
      <description>Suggestions applied System / UI
 Suggestion to decrease game exit countdown (01/27)  Decreased game exit countdown 10 seconds -&amp;gt; 5 seconds   Suggestion to change all minimum input value to 1 (01/27) Suggestion to no longer add quest to Quest List UI when removed quest manually and defeated quest monster (01/27) Suggestion to display Adventure Coin status per character on character selection screen (02/24) Suggestion to add a confirmation pop-up when sending parcel to prevent accidents (02/24)  Revised to display pop-up to confirm recipient   Suggestion to add a confirmation pop-up when leaving a group to prevent accidents (02/24) Suggestion to add a confirmation pop-up when using a Monthly Pass, VIP item (02/24) Suggestion to be able to use Unstuck when players are stuck airborne (02/24) Suggestion to apply Resurrect skill and auto-resurrect before Neophyte Resurrection (02/24) Suggestion to be able to register different box item without having to close UI (02/24) Suggestion to add option to toggle on / off showing face costume (02/24)  Added &amp;lsquo;Show face costume&amp;rsquo; option to Options &amp;gt; Game &amp;gt; Set appearance (02/24)    Content</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>