<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2020 on mysterium</title>
    <link>/mysterium/tags/2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2020 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/mysterium/tags/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 03월 26일 업데이트 안내 (v94.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v94-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v94-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 벨릭의 신전/벨리카 지하 관문 - 엑소도르 정찰대 장비 강화 재료 드랍량이 증가합니다. - RK-9 격납고/혁명단 은거지 - 던전 매칭 및 발키온 지령서 출력 조건이 변경됩니다. (장비레벨 453 -&amp;gt; 452) - 금비늘호 - 딕시 핀쳐의 보물상자 보상 목록에서 &#39;변화의 증거&#39;가 삭제됩니다. ### 2. 아이템 - 강화 손상/하락 보호권 - 차원의 비밀상인 세그레토에게 강화 손상/하락 보호권을 획득할 수 있습니다. - 상급 이상 위상의 던전에서 마지막 네임드 처치 시, 확률적으로 비밀상인이 출현합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020.03.12 patch notes (v93.02) | KTERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v93-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v93-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Sea of Honor - Adjusted to decrease HP of monsters (Seawolf Crew / Hunter / Fighter) - Grotto of Lost Souls (hard) - Changed to apply chain lightning to 1 other person upon hit - Decreased HP and explosion damage of orbs of swipe mechanics - Changed to display electric charge as stack abnormality - Changed dungeon timer to 30 minutes - Gossamer Vault (hard) - Changed dungeon timer to 30 minutes - Antaroth&#39; Abyss (hard) - Decreased damage of certain boss mechanics - Decreased HP of shield applied on Antaroth during cage mechanic - Decreased damage taken during orb mechanic, slightly increased Mana Burst abnormality duration - Changed Antaroth&#39;s - 안타로스의 마력 각성 제한 시간이 7분에서 20분으로 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 03월 12일 업데이트 안내 (v93.02)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v93-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v93-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 금비늘호(항해 지도 던전) - 일반 몬스터(바다늑대 졸개/싸움꾼/베테랑) HP가 하향 조정됩니다. - 왜곡된 리안의 지하 전당 - 패턴에 피격 시 발생되는 체인 라이트닝이 1인에게만 적용됩니다. - 휩쓸기 패턴으로 생성하는 구슬의 HP와 폭발 위력이 감소합니다. - 전기 충전 스택이 이상상태 스택으로 표시됩니다. - 던전 타임어택 시간이 30분으로 변경됩니다. - 찬란한 파르퀴나의 둥지 - 던전 타임어택 시간이 30분으로 변경됩니다. - 공허한 안타로스의 심연 - 안타로스의 일부 패턴 위력이 감소합니다. - 가두기 패턴에서 안타로스에게 부여되는 보호막 HP가 감소합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020.02.27 patch notes (v93.01) | KTERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v93-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v93-01/</guid>
      <description>## Content update ### 1. Dungeon and reward revision - Closed the following 15 instances : - Dungeon - Demokron Factory - Ravenous Gorge - Demokron Factory (hard) - RK-9 Kennel (hard) - Shadow Sanguinary - Antaros&#39; Abyss - Lilith&#39;s Keep - Dark Reaches Citadel - Ruinous Manor - Channelworks - Ruinous Manor (hard) - Gossamer Vault - Velik&#39;s Sanctuary (hard) - Grotto of Lost Souls - Thaumetal Refinery - A portion of these instances will be reopened after revision - Changed Velik&#39;s Hold player count (7 -&amp;gt; 5) - Removed Gossamer Vault (hard) from Leaderboard - Changed starting position of Ace Dungeon : Lilith&#39;s Trial (1st -&amp;gt; 3rd boss) - Changed to apply Neophyte Ressurrection in starter to high difficulty instances - Changed Neophyte Ressurrection limit to 999 times - The following notes Neophyte Ressurection cost : - Lower ~ medium difficulty: 50 Gold - High difficulty: 500 Gold - Guardian gear enchanting materials no longer drop in dungeons - (2/27 edited) Changed party and solo dungeon rewards - Equalized gem drops of dungeon rewards to Rubies - eg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 02월 27일 업데이트 안내 (v93.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v93-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v93-01/</guid>
      <description>## 컨텐츠 업데이트 ### 1. 던전 및 보상 개편 - 15종의 던전 운영이 중단됩니다. - 던전명 - 베르노의 실험실 - 하르키아의 안식처 - 포악한 베르노의 실험실 - 궁극의 RK-9 격납고 - 듀리온의 안식처 - 안타로스의 심연 - 릴리스의 성 - 테네브리스 성채 - 라켈리스의 폐허 - 고대의 지하수로 - 초월한 라켈리스의 폐허 - 파르퀴나의 둥지 - 함락된 벨릭의 신전 - 리안의 지하 전당 - 사이럭스 연구 기지 - 일부 던전은 추후 리뉴얼을 통해 재오픈 예정입니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020.02.13 patch notes (v92.02) | KTERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v92-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v92-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Other - K TERA exclusive T-cat changes ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue where Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge quest clear condition was unclear - Fixed issue where accessing a chat channel ID of exceeding chat channel count left only the `Default` chat channel to exist - Fixed issue where using monthly vip voucher at reduced Adventure Coin state did not increase Adventure Coin for other characters of the same account - K TERA exclusive comment - Fixed issue where using Infinite Adventure Coin event item when character does not have enough Adventure Coin to queue prevented user from using Instance Matching System - Fixed issue where Champion Laurel icon colour from Achievement UI did not match color on Character Window UI - Fixed issue where Priest&#39;s and Mystic&#39;s amount of healing was decreased - Fixed issue where Exodor achievement [Fox Hunt] did not describe its achievement condition properly - Fixed issue where Etching Powder/Dust/Sand/Grit icons were the same yet of different tier - Fixed issue where Female Castanic Slayer&#39;s Plasma Weapon Skin penetrated character&#39;s avatar - Fixed issue where defeating Naga Punisher during Exodor quest [Punishment for Betrayal II] displayed an awkward message source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 02월 13일 업데이트 안내 (v92.02)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v92-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v92-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 기타 - T-cat 상점의 탭 명칭이 수정됩니다. - 기능성과 전투소모품 상품 → 전투 - 외형과 뷰티 상품 → 성장 &amp;amp; 편의 - 펫과 낚시, 기타 상품 → 낚시, 서번트, 기타 ### [버그수정] - 켈사이크 부활 저지 퀘스트 조건이 명확하지 않은 문제 - 채팅 채널의 개수가 초과된 ID에 접속 시, 채팅 탭이 &#39;기본&#39;탭만 존재하는 문제 - 모험의 주화가 소모된 상태에서 월간패스 사용 시, ID 내 다른 캐릭터의 주화가 증가하지 않는 문제 - * 점검 전까지 위 오류로 불편을 겪으신 수호자님께는 별도로 보상을 지급해드릴 예정입니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020.02.06 patch notes (v92.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v92-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v92-01/</guid>
      <description>1. PvP content revision - Added the following rank 1 specific reward ~~per class~~ to the following Battlegrounds (edited 2/7) : - Corsairs&#39; Stronghold : Corsairs&#39; Stronghold Season Rank 1 Trophy - Shorehold : Shorehold Season Rank 1 Trophy - Trophies can be sold to the merchant for 25,000 gold, or collect exchange 6 or 10 trophies to exchange for 6 Time Rank 1 Trophy or 10 Time Rank 1 Trophy (added 2/7) - 6 Time Rank 1 Trophy and 10 Time Rank 1 Trophy can be exchanged from the pop-up merchant via right click (added 2/7) - A custom title will be made to those in possession of 6 Time Rank 1 Trophy (added 2/7) - A custom weapon skin will be made to those in possession of 10 Time Rank 1 Trophy (added 2/7) - The item can be used before Jan 31st, 2021, by 23:59, and will be removed automatically - The rewards will start distributing starting with season 13 (added 2/7) - Battleground Vanguard Request - Adjusted gold reward of the following Vanguard Requests : - Corsairs&#39; Stronghold : from 2,200 gold to 3,000 gold - Shore Hold : from 800 gold to 2,500 gold - Champion&#39;s Skyring : from 200 gold to 500 gold - Added (Random) Skill Advancement Tome Box - (Random) Skill Advancement Tome Box gives a Skill Advancement Tome giving between 30,000 and 200,000 Skill Advance XP - Bellicarium Credit Merchant - Significantly decreased the cost to purchase PvP gear enchanting materials - Decreased resale price to a tenth of the current price as appropriate to the decrease in credit cost - Violet Particle : from 31,250 credit to 3,125 credit - Violet Plate : from 218,750 credit to 21,875 credit - Azure Particle : from 31,250 credit to 3,125 credit - Azure Plate : from 218,750 credit to 21,875 credit - Added the following items to the credit merchant : - Skill Advancement XP Tome IV (200,000 XP) : 1,000,000 credit - Refined Lepidoptera Crystal Dust : 200,000 credit - Refined Lepidoptera Crystal Dust : 200,000 credit - Purified Ring Fragment : 200,000 credit - Purified Ornament Fragment : 200,000 credit - Honed Dark Shard Cohesion Arcane : 1,500,000 credit - Annealed Dark Shard Cohesion Arcane : 1,000,000 credit - Refined Duranium Fragment : 10,000 credit 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 02월 06일 업데이트 안내 (v92.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v92-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v92-01/</guid>
      <description>[업데이트] 1. PVP 컨텐츠 개선 - 전장 순위표 각 직업 전체 랭킹 1위에게 고유 보상이 추가됩니다. (2/7 수정) - 포화의 전장 : 포화의 전장 시즌 1위 트로피 - 해안 점령지 : 해안 점령지 시즌 1위 트로피 - 고유 보상은 상점에 25만 골드로 판매하거나, 6개/10개를 모아 6관왕/10관왕 트로피로 교환할 수 있습니다. (2/7 수정) - 6관왕/10관왕 트로피는 아이템 우클릭 시 열리는 전용 상점에서 구매가 가능합니다. (2/7 추가) - 6관왕 트로피를 보유하고 있을 경우, 원하는 커스텀 칭호를 제작해 드립니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020.01.16 patch notes (v91.03) | KTERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v91-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v91-03/</guid>
      <description>### 1. January combat balance - Berserker - Level 69 Skill Option - Increased duration increase from 18 seconds to 21 seconds - Lancer - Increased skill damage to field monsters by approximately 33.3% - Debilitate - Changed to prevent resistance by targets - Guardian Shout, Line Held - Changed to prevent removal upon knockdown - Guardian Shout, Front Defense - Changed to prevent sharing of cooldown - Brawler - Jackhammer - Changed to prevent resistance by targets - Ninja - Circle of Steel (Glyph of Energy) - Decreased glyph cost from 4 to 2 - Focus - Changed to prevent removal upon knockdown - EP - Lethal Lesson - Changed to prevent removal upon knockdown - Ninja [Double Cut], Gunner [Burst Fire] - Changed to prevent removal upon reactions (knockdown, stagger) - Slayer [Overhand Strike], Archer [Rapid Fire] - Changed to prevent removal upon knockdown ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 01월 16일 업데이트 안내 (v91.03)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v91-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v91-03/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 1월 전투 밸런스 - 광전사 - 69레벨 격노 [광분] 연마 - 격노 [광분] 스킬 사용 시, 적용되는 광기 증폭 효과의 지속 시간이 18초에서 21초로 증가합니다. [개발자 코멘트] - 그 동안 격노[광분] 스킬과 함께 폭주 스킬을 사용했을 때, 폭주의 지속시간 중 마지막 2~3초 구간은 광기 증폭의 효과를 받지 못했습니다. 이번 조정을 통해 폭주 지속시간 동안 끝까지 &#39;폭주&#39; 하실 수 있도록 개선합니다. - 창기사 - 필드 몬스터를 대상으로 스킬 위력이 약 33.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020.01.09 patch notes (v91.02.01) | KTERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v91-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v91-02-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Madness Arena - Decreased boss&#39; Whirlwind damage - Adjusted to not pull players into the same location as the boss ### 2. Elin Valkyrie - Changed to allow race change to Elin Valkyrie ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue in Madness Arena where damage received varied depending on the class - Fixed issue where the last hit bonus reward swapped with the jackpot reward - Fixed issue in Madness Arena where the aggro&#39;d player did not display properly source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 01월 09일 업데이트 안내 (v91.02.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v91-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v91-02-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 광기의 투기장 - 불멸의 투사 회전 베기 스킬의 데미지가 감소됩니다. - 끌어당기기 패턴 사용 시, 불멸의 투사와 캐릭터가 겹치지 않도록 조정됩니다. ### 2. 엘린 월광무사 - 엘린 월광무사로 종족 변경이 가능해집니다. ### [버그수정] - 광기의 투기장 네임드의 클래스 별 데미지 편차가 존재하던 문제 - 필드보스 마지막 타격 보상과 대박 보상이 서로 변경되어 드랍되는 문제 - 광기의 투기장 불멸의 투사 어그로 대상이 어색한 문제 source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020.01.02 patch notes (v91.02) | KTERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v91-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2020/v91-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Leaderboard - Leaderboard season 12 ends and starts anew, added Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge (hard) ### 2. Dungeon - Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge (hard) - Changed to remove Parasite abnormality upon entering 15% implosion mechanic - Revised effects that disrupt vision ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue where 1.5x Glimmering Ice Dragon proc overwrote the 2.0x Glimmering Ice Dragon proc - Fixed issue in Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge where a certain mechanic resisted debuffs occasionally - Fixed issue in Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge where the boss started a wipe mechanic upon starting the fight - Fixed issue in Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge where the event UI remained occasionally - Fixed issue in Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge (hard) where dungeon clear count achievement did not update - Fixed issue in Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge (hard) where simultaneously receiving 3 stacks of parasite debuff and dying resulted in having the abnormality remain - Fixed issue where Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge (hard) displayed as Kelsaik&#39;s Refuge instead in Guild UI - Fixed issue where the Christmas decor covered stamina when setting Character HP bar UI vertically - Fixed issue where declaring GvG on a GvG-eligible guild resulted in an error message and not being able to declare GvG - Fixed issue where tooltip for unequipped gear in Inventory UI displayed tooltip for the currently equipped gear - Fixed issue where Lancer&#39;s block did not have gear&#39;s movement speed effect applied - Fixed issue where wearing Christmas weapon skin penetrated the character for female Castanic Slayer - Fixed issue where the Christmas weapon skin for female Castanic Slayer was displayed backwards - Fixed issue in Madness Arena where using a skill to reset aggro prevented certain mechanics to stop - Fixed issue where the OX quiz event UI did not pop up at its proper designated time source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020년 01월 02일 업데이트 안내 (v91.02)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v91-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2020/v91-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 순위표 - 12시즌이 종료되며, 불멸의 켈사이크 은폐지 던전이 순위표에 추가됩니다. ### 2. 던전 - 불멸의 켈사이크 은폐지 - 불멸의 켈사이크 HP 15% 붕괴 패턴 시, 아르곤 기생충 이상상태가 해제되도록 변경됩니다. - 일부 화면을 가리는 효과가 완화됩니다. ### [버그수정] - * 채팅창 UI 위치가 초기화되는 문제는 1/16(목) 수정될 예정이며, 채팅창 UI 설정이 초기화되는 문제는 현재 확인 중에 있습니다. 가능한 빠르게 수정될 수 있도록 최선을 다하겠습니다. 이용에 불편을 끼쳐드려 죄송합니다. - 빙룡의 주인 패시브 스킬이 치명타 위력 2배 증가 패시브보다 상위로 적용되는 문제 - 켈사이크 은폐지에서 확률적으로 파멸 패턴을 저항하여 적용되지 않는 문제 - 켈사이크 은폐지에서 전투 시작 시, 확률적으로 전멸기를 시전하는 문제 - 켈사이크 은폐지에서 간헐적으로 이벤트 게이지가 남아있는 문제 - 불멸의 켈사이크 은폐지에서 던전 클리어 카운트 업적이 달성되지 않는 문제 - 불멸의 켈사이크 은폐지에서 기생충 3중첩 이상상태 효과가 받는 타이밍에 따라 종료된 이후 부활해도 지속되는 문제 - 길드 정보에서 불멸의 켈사이크 은폐지가 켈사이크 은폐지로 출력되는 문제 - HP/MP바를 세로 정렬할 경우, 크리스마스 데코 UI가 스테미너를 가리는 문제 - 길드전을 진행하지 않은 길드에게 재선포 시간이 지나지 않았다는 메시지와 함께 선포가 불가능한 문제 - 착용중인 장비와 인벤토리 장비를 비교하는 툴팁에서 착용중인 장비의 귀속 캐릭터명이 노출되지 않는 문제 - 창기사 방패 방어 스킬 사용 시, 장비의 이동속도 증가 옵션 효과가 적용되지 않는 문제 - 케스타닉 여자 무사 캐릭터로 크리스마스 무기 아이템 장착 시, 무기가 캐릭터 외형을 뚫는 문제 - 크리스마스 FUN 무기 대검을 케스타닉 여 종족으로 장착 시, 앞 뒤가 바뀌어 출력되는 문제 - 광기의 투기장에서 특정 타이밍에 적대치 초기화 스킬을 사용하면 일부 연계 패턴이 나오지 않는 문제 - OX 이벤트 전용 UI가 이벤트 시작 시간이 되어도 출력되지 않는 문제 source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>