<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v59 on tera-mysterium</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v59/</link><description>Recent content in v59 on tera-mysterium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v59/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2017.05.18 patch notes (v59.02.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-02-01/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-02-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Quest Zone quest : Linkia&amp;rsquo;s Brief Added feature to get back quest item 퀘스트 진행 구조를 아이템 사용 및 방문하는 방식으로 변경하였습니다. 해당 퀘스트는 칸스트리아의 헤카샤 NPC 를 통해 진행할 수 있습니다. Zone quest : One Father&amp;rsquo;s Legacy Added feature to get back quest item 해당 퀘스트는 연합군 지휘소의 달무리 자온 NPC 를 통해 진행할 수 있습니다. 2. Item Changed properties of Pet skill book obtained from achievements Changed the properties of the following 19 Pet skill book to no longer be bankable [이벤트] 펫 랜덤상자를 사용하여 획득할 수 있는 펫 스킬교본이 대상에 포함됩니다.</description></item><item><title>2017.05.11 patch notes (v59.02) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-02/</guid><description>Update 1. Services 2017 웨딩 드레스 색상이 백색으로 변경됩니다. 어두운 장소에서도 순백의 웨딩 드레스가 잘 표현되도록 색상이 변경됩니다. Bug fixes Skill Fixed issue where Amani Female Archer&amp;rsquo;s Rain of Arrows VI~IX damage is the damage Talent 인술사 정신집중 가속이 14단계에서 15단계로 올라갈 때 감소되는 시간이 줄어드는 문제 Guild Fixed issue where Guild Skills cannot be used through shortcut UI Event PC방 보상 중 &amp;lsquo;월광 그림자 쌍검 (1일)&amp;rsquo; 아이템이 상점 판매 가능한 문제 테라코인 스페셜 탭에서 판매된 [이벤트] Fun 무기상자 구성품이 기간제인 문제 Dungeon 데모로스의 룰렛 1네임드 이동경로 다리의 좌, 우 난간 위 허공으로 이동할 수 있는 문제</description></item><item><title>2017.04.28 patch notes (v59.01.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-01-01/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-01-01/</guid><description>Bug fixes Quest Fixed issue where multiple players could not progress with the starting quest for Demoros&amp;rsquo;s Roulette During Demoros&amp;rsquo; Roulette quests, qest to follow NPC Diana to the town of San Alema has been fixed for multiple players to complete simultaneously Skill Lancer Fixed issue where crit chance correction on Shield Counter did not work Archer Fixed issue where stagger animation for Sequential Fire did not apply Fixed issue where chance to knockdown for Sequential Fire was too high Warrior Fixed issue where enhancement from Rain of Blows did not apply for certain races Fixed issue where Traverse Cut could not be chained for certain races Fixed issue where Attack Speed buff from Traverse Cut was applied to the target Fixed issue where Scythe III~IX did not take effect from Screen Shake Reduction option Sorcerer Fixed issue where Meteor Strike VIII~X did not take effect from Screen Shake Reduction option Brawler Fixed issue where damage for Ground Pounder XII was low 전적 정보 28일 주기로 목요일 새벽4시에 전장 전적 정보가 초기화되지 않던 문제 이벤트 테라코인 스페셜 탭에 등록된 Fun 무기상자가 기간제인 문제 영구제 아이템으로 교체되며, 이미 기간제 아이템을 구매하신 수호자분들은 5월 11일 정기점검 시 영구제로 자동 교체됩니다.</description></item><item><title>2017.04.27 patch notes (v59.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-01/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2017/v59-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon Added new dungeon &amp;lsquo;Demon&amp;rsquo;s Wheel&amp;rsquo; Level 65, 5-Person party dungeon, requiring ilvl 423 to use IMS Teleportal is located near Allemantheia Tier 2 Godly accessories, Visionmaker material (VM9), Dyad Niveot Structure, Tier 11 Feedstock, Masterwork / Extensive Alkahest, Goddess&amp;rsquo; Tear, Goldfinger Token, Gold Ticket, etc can be obtained. Removed Manglemire 2. Skill Reaper Soul Reversal Changed to change location in area behind boss in case there is no optimal distance behind boss to teleport to Mystic Volley of Curses (Glyph of Enfeeblement) Changed endurance debuff from 9% to 10% Aura of the Merciless Changed power buff from 40 to 48 and attack speed buff from 6 to 9.</description></item></channel></rss>