<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v74 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v74/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v74 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v74/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.28 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Elin Gunner  Can now create Elin Gunner  Cannot use Race Change Voucher to create an Elin Gunner    2. Balance  Slightly adjusted balancing of all classes except reaper throughout level progression  Bug fixes  Leaderboard  Fixed issue where ranking titles were not collected from players   Island of Dawn  Fixed issue where caiman thieves did not spawn    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.21 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Item  Added clear face cosmetic  This item equipped in the face style slot hides the expressed appearance of masks Randomly drops from level 65 party dungeons Sells for 8,000 T-cat in the T-cat merchant   Added clear back cosmetic  to level 65 dungeons and Tikat This item equipped in the back style slot hides the expressed appearance of weapons Randomly drops from level 65 party dungeons Sells for 8,000 T-cat in the T-cat merchant    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.14 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Summer festival (TERA KR exclusive)  07/12(목)까지 여름 축제가 오픈되며, 여름 축제 홍보용 NPC가 배치됩니다.  여름 축제 NPC 배치 장소  대도시 내부-벨리카, 알레만시아, 카이아도르 축제장소-태양의 정원, 뱀의 섬      2. Guardian Legion mission  Decreased HP of the initial two dragons for Superior GLM Adjusted Superior GLM time from 15:30 minutes to 18:30 minutes  3. Dreadspire  Adjusted 5th floor and 10th floor reward  Adjusted to increase gold reward  5th floor : 22,000 gold to 30,000 gold 10th floor : 22,000 gold to 50,000 gold   Removed the following rewards  Carved Ornament Copper Clasp Otherwordly SHard Pansophic Ash   Added combat consumables  Bravery Potion, Superior Noctenium Elixir, Fed: Health Potion, Fed: Rejuvenation Potion      4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.05 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Level progression reward UI revision  Revised to receive all accumulated rewards at once  *이미 보상 UI가 4개를 초과하여 보상을 받지 못하신 수호자님께 오늘 중 보상을 지급해드릴 예정이었으나, 대상자 추출에 문제가 있어 07/12(목)으로 지급일이 연기되었습니다. 안내드린 일정을 지키지 못해 죄송합니다.    Bug fixes  Skill  Fixed issue where Brawlers could endlessly maintain Rhymthmic Blows buff by repeating Punch, Counter, and Rhythmic Blows   Item  Fixed issue where passive effects on gear occasionally did not work    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>