<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v112 on mysterium</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v112/</link><description>Recent content in v112 on mysterium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v112/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2021.11.17 patch notes (v112.02.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v112-02-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v112-02-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Service stabilization 서버 불안정 현상 최소화를 위해, 전반적인 인프라 안정화 작업을 진행합니다. 2. Services (TERA KR exclusive) 테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. Image not available
Bug fixes Fixed issue in Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) Dungeon Resonance where Priests can pull players outside of the combat area after combat starts Fixed issue in Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) Dungeon Resonance where multiple orbs can be destroyed at a distance during orb pattern Fixed issue where Adventure Coin for Ace Dungeons is consumed at different times Fixed issue in Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) Dungeon Resonance where mana burst Resonance Effect does not apply Fixed issue in Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) Dungeon Resonance where damage from clones is low Fixed issue where Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold event reward chance is not applied correctly Fixed issue where Serghetto event NPC continues to spawn after event has ended Fixed issue where tooltip for [Untradable] Murky Mahtnan Powder, [Untradable] Gleaming Mahtnan Powder, [Untradable] Sparkling Mahtnan Powder notes that they can be used for crafting</description></item><item><title>2021.11.10 patch notes (v112.02) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v112-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v112-02/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon Resonance Opened Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) as Dungeon Resonance Entry method Entrance is only available through Bloody Resonance Gate located in Balderon Either Corrupted Skynest (hard) or Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) is chosen automatically upon entering Bloody Resonance Gate (will be revised to be able to choose in a future patch) Entry requires 1 AWAKE Resonance Stone (per party member) Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) Entry level 70 Item level 510 Resonance Effect Resonance Effect applied in Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) is the following : Applied level Effect Icon Description 11 ~ Max Rage Accelerator (pl.</description></item><item><title>2021.11.03 patch notes (v112.01.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v112-01-01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2021/v112-01-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon Resonance Changed title distributed for Dungeon Resonance season 1 to the following : Rank 1 title : 차원 저 너머에 도달한 Rank 2~3 title : 차원 저 너머를 바라본 2. Event (TERA KR exclusive) 9월 15일(수) 진행된 익스프레스 점핑 타임! 이벤트 전용 아이템 및 퀘스트가 삭제됩니다. 3. Services (TERA KR exclusive) 테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다. Image not available
결제 수단이 추가됩니다. 네이버 페이 Bug fixes Fixed issue where items distributed as reward from Island of Dawn cannot be merged or fused together Fixed issue where Dopey Cocomin and Mature Cocomin can receive abilities</description></item></channel></rss>