<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v80 on mysterium</title>
    <link>/mysterium/tags/v80/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v80 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/mysterium/tags/v80/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.17 patch notes (v80.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-03/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Server merge - Servers are now merged ### 2. Dungeon - Level progression dungeon - Instance matching system - Changed from 5-man to 3-man instances - Changed Joy of Partying effect (2-man : 200%, 3-man : 400%) - Changed dungeons : Bastion of Lok, Sinistral Manor, Savarash&#39;s Ascent, Cultists&#39; Refuge, Necromancer&#39;s Tomb, Golden Labyrinth, Saleron&#39;s Sky Garden, Labyrinth of Terror, Ebon Tower - Adjust dungeon difficulty - Can now be cleared without a healer - Changed Instance Matching to be able to match regardless of class - Fixed for named monsters to drop health motes ### 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 17일 업데이트 안내 (v80.03)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-03/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 서버통합 - [아룬의 영광] [카이아의 가호] 서버가 통합됩니다. &amp;gt;[통합 세부 내용 확인] ### 2. 던전 - 성장구간 던전 - 던전 매칭 인원 변경 - 5 -&amp;gt; 3인으로 변경됩니다. - 매칭 인원이 변경됨에 따라 성장의 즐거움 효과가 변경됩니다. (2인 200%, 3인 400%) - 변경 던전: 비밀기지, 밤피르의 저택, 자바르만 소굴, 사교도의 은신처, 사령술 연구소, 황금의 미궁, 살레론의 공중 정원, 공포의 미궁, 검은 탑 - 던전 난이도 조정 - 힐러 클래스가 없이도 클리어가 가능해집니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.10 patch notes (v80.02.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02-01/</guid>
      <description>- 1. Fishing - XP - Successfully catching fish now provides XP - XP gained varies at different levels - XP gained varies by different grades of fish - Item - Changed to obtain Talyph XP scroll I~II by chance upon successful catch - Delivery - Fish delivery - Changed Association Fishmonger to Association Fishmonger - Increased delivery limit to 30 times - Can obtain gold by delivering grade 0-10 fish and BAF - Fish crate delivery - Changed Association Resource Manager to Association Fish Crate Manager - Changed to deliver up to 3 times - Can obtain gold by delivering Fish Crate I-V - Fish Crate designs can be exchanged with Angler Tokens through Angler Token Vendor - VIP users can deliver fish up to 50 times, deliver fish crates up to 5 times - Fishing Supplies merchant - Added Recipe: Apple-Pumpkin Smoothie - Can be crafted 50 Apples, 50 Moongourd Pulp and 100 Fresh Milk (2x for crit) - Provides &#39;20% XP boost&#39; effect ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 10일 업데이트 안내 (v80.02.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 낚시 - 경험치 - 낚시 성공 시 레벨 경험치를 획득합니다. - 캐릭터 레벨에 따라 획득하는 경험치가 다릅니다. - 낚은 물고기의 등급에 따라 획득하는 경험치가 다릅니다. - 아이템 - 낚시 성공 시 일정 확률로 스킬 연마 경험치 서적I~ II을 획득할 수 있게 됩니다. - 낚시 납품 상점 - 물고기 납품점 - 낚시 납품점이 물고기 납품점으로 변경되었습니다. - 납품 횟수가 30회로 증가합니다. - 0등급~10등급 물고기와 대물을 납품하여 골드를 획득하실 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.03 patch notes (v80.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Quest - Added story quest-specific 1-man level progression dungeons - Bastion of Lok (1-man) - Can enter via appropriate story quest - Sinistral Manor (1-man) - Can enter via appropriate story quest - Cultists&#39; Refuge (1-man) - Can enter via appropriate story quest - Removed Kumas Royale story quest - Quest already received and not completed will automatically be completed upon update - Fixed to display escort quest NPCs on minimap via an orange dot marking ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 03일 업데이트 안내 (v80.02)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 퀘스트 - 미션 퀘스트 진행을 위한 퀘스트 전용 성장구간(1인) 던전이 추가됩니다. - 비밀기지(1인) - 미션 퀘스트 “비밀기지를 토벌하라” 를 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다. - 밤피르의 저택(1인) - 미션 퀘스트 “밤피르 저택 토벌”을 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다. - 사교도의 은신처(1인) - 미션 퀘스트 “로크 교도 괴멸”을 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다. - LV20 쿠마스의 놀이터 미션퀘스트가 삭제 됩니다. - 미션 퀘스트 쿠마스의 놀이터를 수주 받고 진행하지 않은 경우, 업데이트 후 완료된 퀘스트로 자동 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>