<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/tags/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.com/tags/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.12.24 patch notes (v91.01.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v91-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v91-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Bug fixes  Fixed issue where relogging characters occasionally restored Adventure Coin Fixed issue where chat tab reset and chat UI reset   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 12월 24일 업데이트 안내 (v91.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v91-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v91-01-01/</guid>
      <description>[버그수정]  캐릭터 재접속 시 모험의 주화가 간헐적으로 충전되는 문제 채팅창 탭 순서 및 채팅 UI 설정이 재접속 시 초기화되는 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.12.19 patch notes (v91.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v91-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v91-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Class balance  Priest  Zenobia&amp;rsquo;s Vortex  Increased the chance to crit   Holy Burst  Slightly decreased the chance to crit      2. Dungeon  Removed Forsaken Island (nm/hm) New : Madness Arena (5 man)  Requires level 69 and ilvl 461 to use Instance Matching System Requires 220 Adventure Coins, and allows up to 5 entries (10 entries with Elite/VIP status) Located in Plains of the Damned, Elenea Loot table includes Annihilation/Dark Light Brooch, Annihilation/Dark Light Brooch Token, Exodor rare/superior gear, and Darkshad Feedstock Related quest can be acquired upon completing [Dungeon] Desert Wolf (new) quest Added 4 achievements related to the instance  Achievement  Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name       New : Kelsaik&amp;rsquo;s Refuge (5 man)  Requires level 69 and ilvl 461 to use Instance Matching System Requires 220 Adventure Coins, and allows up to 5 entries (10 entries with Elite/VIP status) Located in Verrak Fortress, Exodor Loot table includes Mythical gear promotion material, Exodor rare/superior gear, and Darkshad Feedstock Related quest can be acquired upon completing [Imporatant] Exodor Advance Base quest Added 5 achievements related to the instance  Achievement  Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name       New : Kelsaik&amp;rsquo;s Refuge (hard) (5 man)  Requires level 69 and ilvl 480 to use Instance Matching System Requires 250 Adventure Coins, and allows up to 5 entries (10 entries with Elite/VIP status) Located in Verrak Fortress, Exodor Loot table includes Mythical gear promotion material, Mythical gear, Exodor rare/superior gear, Kelsaik&amp;rsquo;s style items (weapon skin), and Darkshad Feedstock Added 4 achievements and 2 hidden achievements and 1 server first clear achievement related to the instance  Server first clear achievement will not be imbued immediately and will be given upon checking appropriate clear  Achievement  Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name Achievement name          3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 12월 19일 업데이트 안내 (v91.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v91-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v91-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 전투 밸런스  사제  신의 숨결  치명타 발생 확률이 증가합니다.   찬란한 섬광  치명타 발생 확률이 소폭 감소합니다.   치유의 바람 연계  [치유의 빛, 물러서기, 속박의 낙인] 스킬 사용 후, 강력한 치유의 바람을 연계할 수 있는 시간이 소폭 증가합니다.      [개발자 코멘트]
 신의 숨결과 찬란한 섬광 스킬의 치명타 발생 확률을 조정합니다. &amp;lsquo;신의 숨결&amp;rsquo; 스킬의 경우 치명타 발생률이 상향되며, 치명타 유발 능력치에 대한 의존도를 낮춰 다른 능력치에 투자할 수 있도록 조정됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.12.12 patch notes (v90.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v90-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v90-03/</guid>
      <description>Bug fixes  Fixed issue where relogging reset chat UI position  Fixing this issue reset all chat settings   Fixed issue where UI positions reset for certain characters   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 12월 12일 업데이트 안내 (v90.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v90-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v90-03/</guid>
      <description>[버그수정]
 캐릭터 선택창으로 이동 후 재접속 시 채팅창의 위치가 초기화되는 문제  오류가 수정되며 채팅창 설정이 초기화되었습니다. 번거로우시겠지만, 재설정 후 이용 부탁드립니다.   특정 캐릭터의 UI가 초기화되는 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.12.05 patch notes (v90.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v90-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v90-02/</guid>
      <description>Bug fixes    Issue where changed character position reset to the previous position will be revised for the week after   Fixed issue where certain character&amp;rsquo;s Adventure Coin displayed 0/0 Fixed issue where using Elite Status did not add additional Adventure Coins (from 1000 to 1680)  Did not restore above 1680   Fixed issue where character slots did not expand for Frontier account Fixed issue where Reapers with Argog weapon skin displayed Christmas themed weapon skin   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 12월 05일 업데이트 안내 (v90.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v90-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v90-02/</guid>
      <description>[버그수정]    캐릭터 선택창으로 이동 후 재접속 시 채팅창의 위치가 초기화되는 문제는 UI 관련 코드에도 영향이 있어 보다 면밀한 테스트를 위해 12/12(목) 정기점검을 통해 수정될 예정입니다. 불편을 끼쳐드려 죄송합니다.   일부 캐릭터의 모험의 주화가 0/0으로 표시되는 문제 월간패스/VIP를 사용하여 모험의 주화 최대치가 1,000에서 1,680으로 확장될 때, 일부 캐릭터의 모험의 주화가 추가 충전되지 않는 문제  최대 680까지 충전되며, 1,680을 초과해서 충전되지는 않습니다.   11/28(목) 업데이트 이후 프론티어 ID의 캐릭터 슬롯이 확장되지 않은 문제 아스란의 비검 장착 시 크리스마스 외형이 출력되는 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.11.28 patch notes (v90.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v90-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v90-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Elin Valkyrie  Added [Valkyrie] class to Elin race  Cannot use race change voucher until 2020.01.09  Elin Valkyries can race change to Female Castanic Valkyries (but not vice versa)      2. Character slot  Increased max character slot from 22 slots to 23 slots  3. Character progression revision  Talent points (EP)  Changed starting Talent Point to 300 Existing characters with less than 300 Talent Points will be changed to 300   Experience points  Decreased XP required from level 65 to level 69 Decreased HP and damage of field monsters level 65 and above Increased level 65 and above party dungeon Vanguard Request XP and hunting XP Inrceased XP from daily quests Inceased fishing/crafting/gathering XP   Skill Advance  Increased Skill Advance XP gained from level 65 and above party dungeons Increased Skill Advance XP gained from Exodor story quests and zone quests Increased Skill Advance XP gained from Exodor daily quests   Skill Advance Scroll  Increased Skill Advance Scrolls gained from level 65 and above party dungeons Increased Skill Advance Scrolls gained from daily quests Added Skill Advance III Scrolls gained from Exodor daily quests Added Skill Advance III Scrolls to Exodor reputation merchants Increased Skill Advance Scrolls gained from field boss monster Ortan   Guardian gear  Revised necessary enchanting materials and item XP needed to enchant Frostmetal gear Revised necessary enchanting materials and item XP needed to enchant Stormcry gear Revised promotion success rate and necessary enchanting materials and item XP for the following accessories :  Below Entropic accessories Below Quatrefoil Brooch   Increased the promotion success rate of the following accessories :  Entropic accessories and above Quatrefoil Brooch/Marrow Brooch and above   Increased drop amount of Liquid Metal, Hypnotic Device  Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Keep Thaumetal Refinery Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold Red Refuge Dark Reaches Cathedral Shadow Sanguinary Forsaken Island Rakelith&amp;rsquo;s Manor RK-9 Kennel Velik&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary      4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 11월 28일 업데이트 안내 (v90.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v90-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v90-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 엘린 월광무사  엘린 종족으로 선택 가능한 직업에 [월광무사]가 추가됩니다.  2020년 1월 9일 점검 전까지 종족 변경권으로 변경할 수 없습니다.  엘린에서 케스타닉 여자로는 변경이 가능합니다. (케스타닉에서 엘린으로는 불가)      2. 캐릭터 소켓  최대 확장 가능한 슬롯 개수가 22개 → 23개로 변경됩니다.  (11/29 추가) 기본 슬롯 개수가 6개 → 7개로 확장된 것으로, 기존 보유 슬롯 개수에 1개가 확장되었습니다.    3. 캐릭터 성장 허들 완화  특성 포인트  시작 특성 포인트가 300으로 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.11.21 patch notes (v89.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v89-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v89-03/</guid>
      <description>Event  K TERA exclusive returning player event  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where characters with name of &amp;lsquo;name_number&amp;rsquo; due to server merge could not be restored   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 11월 21일 업데이트 안내 (v89.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v89-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v89-03/</guid>
      <description>[이벤트]  11/21 ~ 11/27 누적 출석체크 이벤트가 진행됩니다. [공지사항]  신규 수호자를 위한 레벨 상자의 구성품은 아래와 같습니다.    [버그수정]  서버 통합으로 인해 &amp;lsquo;캐릭터명_숫자&amp;rsquo; 형식으로 변경된 캐릭터를 셀프 복구할 수 없는 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.11.14 patch notes (v89.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v89-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v89-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Balance  Priest  Edict of Judgement  Reset cooldown of Zenobia&amp;rsquo;s Vortex and Holy Burst upon casting   Triple Nemesis [Stigma] Talent  Increased debuff duration from 12 seconds to 21 seconds     Mystic  Augmentation  Removed continuous MP consumption during effect   Arunic Release  Reduced MP cost from 1,050 to 700 Decreased skill damage from 9,750 to 8,287   Vollet of Curses [Stigma] Talent  Increased debuff duration from 12 seconds to 21 seconds     Valkyrie  Godsfall  Decreased cooldown from 5 minutes to 4 minutes   Talent  Changed Glaive Strike [Chained Speed Skating] talent to Glaive Strike [Velocity]  Before :  Glaive Strike [Chained Speed Skating] : Increase casting speed of the next skill   After :  Glaive Strike [Velocity] : Increase casting speed (of Glaive Strike) (max 20%)         Gunner  Revised Arcane Splash and damage skills  Skills generating Arcane Splash :  20% chance to generate 1 Arcane Splash per Mana Missile hit (removed explode feature) 15% chance to generate 1 Arcane Splash per Burst Fire hit and Bombardment hit (removed explode feature from Burst Fire) 100% chance to generate 1 Arcane Splash upon successful hit with Time Bomb 30% chance to generate 1 Arcane Splash upon successful hit with Targeted Burst Fire (removed explode feature) 20% chance to generate 1 Arcane Splash per Obliteration hit (removed explode feature and increase explode damage feature)   Skills exploding Arcane Splash :  Blast Arcane Barrage Laser of Remote Trigger Balder&amp;rsquo;s Vengeance II (Added effect to increase explode damage by 3 times upon successfully hitting Arcane Splash with Balder&amp;rsquo;s Vengeance)   Level 69 skill option  Modular Weapon System [Integration]  Added effect to increase explode damage by 2 times upon successfully hitting Arcane Splash with Arcane Barrage          2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 11월 14일 업데이트 안내 (v89.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v89-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v89-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 밸런스  사제  심판의 주문  시전 시, 신의 숨결과 찬란한 섬광 스킬의 재사용 대기 시간이 초기화 됩니다.   [천벌의 연쇄 – 낙인] 특성  지속 시간이 증가합니다. (12초 -&amp;gt; 21초)     정령사  정령화  효과 지속 중, MP 지속 소모 효과가 제거됩니다.   정기 폭발  MP 소모량이 감소합니다. (1,050 -&amp;gt; 700) 스킬 위력이 감소합니다. (9,750 -&amp;gt; 8,287)   [고통의 주박 – 낙인] 특성  지속 시간이 증가합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.10.31 patch notes (v89.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v89-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v89-01/</guid>
      <description>1. New dungeon: Sea of Honor  Eligible for players of level 65 and above, and requires a Wayfarer Map to enter  Wayfarer Map can randomly drop from ilvl 435 and above dungeons and monsters of level 65 and above  Macellarius Catacombs does not drop Wayfarer Map Wayfarer Map cannot be traded nor put in guild bank, and each map can be used to enter along with up to 5 party members     Entrance to the dungeon is at Cutthroat Harbor, via Roni (1 entry per week, 2 entry for Elite Status or equivalent) Upon entering the dungeon, players can select difficulty and use the Wayfarer Map to proceed Depending on the difficulty (1-4), monsters&amp;rsquo; HPs and damage varies, and additional mechanics may be added The following are the rewards for each difficulty  Bonus reward is given upon completing the instance in 30 minutes  Difficulty 1 (recommended ilvl 446 and above)  Reward : XP scroll, Golden/Silver Talent, Metamorphic Emblem   Difficulty 2 (recommended ilvl 453 and above)  Reward : Exodor Weapon Enchanting Scroll [rare], Exodor Armor Enchanting Scroll [rare], Azart Expedition Badge, Metamorphic Emblem   Difficulty 3 (recommended ilvl 461 and above)  Reward : Exodor Weapon Enchanting Scroll [superior], Exodor Armor Enchanting Scroll [superior], Azart Expedition Badge, Metamorphic Emblem   Difficulty 4 (recommended ilvl 475 and above)  Reward : Exodor Weapon Enchanting Scroll [superior], Exodor Armor Enchanting Scroll [superior], Ishara&amp;rsquo;s Halidom, Amarun&amp;rsquo;s Relic   Bonus  50-100x Sea Guardian Token     Exodor Weapon/Armor Enchanting Scrolls can be used on Exodor gear  Using the scroll to enchant costs no other materials, and enchanting success rate is the same as using the enchanting UI to enchant   The following items can be exchanged with Sea Guardian Token :  Skill Advance Scroll I-II, Skill Option Scroll I-II, Emerald, Dixie Pincher&amp;rsquo;s Sea Terror Hammer Dixie Pincher&amp;rsquo;s Sea Terror Hammer is a Berserker specific weapon skin      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 10월 31일 업데이트 안내 (v89.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v89-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v89-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 신규 던전: 항해 지도  65레벨 이상 캐릭터로 이용 가능하며, 던전을 진행하기 위해서는 &amp;lsquo;항해 지도&amp;rsquo; 아이템이 필요합니다.  항해 지도 아이템은 장비레벨 435 이상의 던전 및 65레벨 이상 필드 몬스터가 확률적으로 드랍합니다.  데모크론 실험실에서는 항해 지도가 드랍되지 않습니다. 거래 및 길드 창고 보관이 불가능한 아이템이며, 1개의 지도로 최대 5명이 참여할 수 있습니다.     동부 가드&amp;gt;거친 해안&amp;gt;거친 항구의 로니에게 말을 걸어 입장할 수 있습니다. (주간 1회/월간패스 2회) 입장 후, 난이도를 선택하고 항해 지도 아이템을 사용하여 던전을 진행할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.10.24 patch notes (v88.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-04/</guid>
      <description>null
 source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 10월 24일 업데이트 안내 (v88.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-04/</guid>
      <description>null
 source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.10.17 patch notes (v88.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Halloween event (K TERA exclusive)  Significantly decreased number of fake Gourdos Removed Frontera from spawn locations for Gourdos  Due to issue where too many spawned in areas that could not be accessed   Removed Gourdos Moongourd x2 from drop table, and adjusted drop rate of other items  Significantly increased the drop rate of Gourdos Moongourd x5    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where Halloween-themed style items disappeared upon entering dungeon/battlergound  Items lost due to this issue will be restored     source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 10월 17일 업데이트 안내 (v88.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 할로윈 이벤트  가짜 잭 오 랜턴의 숫자가 대폭 줄어듭니다. 잭 오 랜턴의 스폰 지역에서 &amp;lsquo;개척민 마을&#39;이 제외됩니다.  처치 불가능한 위치에 다수 스폰되는 현상이 확인되어 제외되었습니다.   드랍 보상에서 [이벤트] 잭오랜턴의 호박 2개가 제외되며, 아이템별 드랍 확률이 조정됩니다.  [이벤트] 잭오랜턴의 호박 5개 드랍 확률이 대폭 상승합니다.    [버그수정]  할로윈 스타일 아이템 일부가 임의의 던전/전장에 입장 시 사라지는 문제  위 오류로 소실된 아이템은 10/24(목) 정기점검 시 복구될 예정입니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.10.10 patch notes (v88.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Field  New : Darkstone Cipher  Defeat monsters on the outer islands of Exodor to obtain materials to combine into &amp;lsquo;Decoded Darkstone Cipher&amp;rsquo;, which is used to obtain hidden treasures on Exodor  Materials :  Damaged Darkstone Cipher Incomplete Darkstone Cipher Flawed Darkstone Cipher Darkstone Cipher Decoding Solution   Using &amp;lsquo;Decoded Darkstone Cipher&amp;rsquo; spawns enemy trackers, and defeating these monsters will reward Darkstone Fragments Darkstone Fragments can be exchanged for Darkshad Weapon/Armor Feedstock, Azart Elixir     New : Sealed Darkstone  Sealed Darkstones spawn on outer islands of Exodor  Sealed Darkstones can be unsealed using &amp;lsquo;Unsealing Scroll&amp;rsquo;, and a Darkstone Fragment can be obtained      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 10월 10일 업데이트 안내 (v88.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 필드  신규: 다크스톤 암호문  엑소도르 특정 지역에 숨겨져 있는 보물을 획득할 수 있는 아이템으로, 엑소도르 외곽섬 몬스터에게 &amp;lsquo;해독된 다크스톤 암호문&amp;rsquo; 아이템을 조합할 수 있는 재료를 획득할 수 있습니다.  암호문 조합 재료  훼손된 다크스톤 암호문 불완전한 다크스톤 암호문 손상된 다크스톤 암호문 다크스톤 암호문 해독 용액   특정 위치에서 &amp;lsquo;해독된 다크스톤 암호문&#39;을 사용하면 추적대가 등장하며, 추적대 몬스터를 처치하면 다크스톤 조각을 획득할 수 있습니다. 다크스톤 조각으로는 다크샤드 무기/방어구 강화석, 마력의 다크샤드 무기/방어구 강화석, 아르가프 영약 등의 아이템을 교환할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.09.26 patch notes (v88.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v88-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Companion  Added new Partners Ello and Rico  New Partners can be obtained via Combining/Evolving randomly (uncommon ~ superior) Bond Skill  Ello : Increase magical damage for a set duration Rico : Increase physical damage for a set duration   Gifted Skill  Ello : [ Fellowship I~III (duration), Emergency Service I~III (MP), Rapid Growth I~III (XP), Gathering Support (I~III) ] Rico : [ Fellowship I~III (duration), Urgent Recovery I~III (HP), Dual Boost I~III (XP &amp;amp; Skill Advance), Backup Fisherman (I~III) ]      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 09월 26일 업데이트 안내 (v88.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v88-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 파트너  신규 파트너 &amp;lsquo;엘로&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;리코&#39;가 추가됩니다.  펫 합성 / 진화에서 확률적으로 신규 파트너를 획득할 수 있습니다. (고급 ~ 전설) 교감 스킬  파트너 | 스킬명 | 설명  엘로 | 다채로운 에너지 | 일정 시간 동안 마법 증폭이 증가합니다. 리코 | 거친 기운 | 일정 시간 동안 물리 증폭이 증가합니다.     재능 스킬  파트너 | 획득 가능한 재능 스킬  엘로 | 교감 강화 I ~ III, 긴급 지원 I ~ III, 성장 가속 I ~ III, 채집 지원 I ~ III 리코 | 교감 강화 I ~ III, 긴급 회복 I ~ III, 복합 가속 I ~ III, 낚시 지원 I ~ III        2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.09.19 patch notes (v87.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v87-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v87-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Celestial Arena  Changed required item level from 439 to 431  Adjusted to decrease HP of monsters to reflect the item level change      2. Services  PC bang  K TERA exclusive  K TERA exclusive K TERA exclusive      3. Item  Changed to allow switching between Intel pieces and Naslow&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Map pieces  It is a 1:1 exchange, and cannot be traded on trade broker    4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 09월 19일 업데이트 안내 (v87.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v87-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v87-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  천공의 경기장  적정 수행 장비 레벨이 변경됩니다. (439 → 431)  권장 레벨에 맞게 몬스터의 HP 등 밸런스가 하향 조정됩니다.      2. 부가 서비스  PC방 혜택  [PC방] 차가운 금속 장비 상자가 [PC방] 전설 장비 상자로 변경됩니다.  해당 상자를 통해서 절멸, 검은 태양 장비, 빛나는 여신의 브로치, 불멸의 반지 등의 장비를 획득하실 수 있습니다. (PC방에서만 이용 가능한 장비) [PC방] 전설 장비 상자에서 획득한 아이템은 65레벨 이상부터 착용할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.09.10 patch notes (v87.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v87-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v87-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Field boss  Field boss contents Machnak, Avion, Royal Azart have been disabled  2. Item  Changed the following items&amp;rsquo; names and icons  Physical Machnak Belt -&amp;gt; Red Sun Belt Magical Machnak Belt -&amp;gt; Blue Moon Belt Physical Avion Mask -&amp;gt; Red Sun Mask Magical Avion Mask -&amp;gt; Blue Moon Mask   Added the following items to the shops of the following items  The items are equivalent conversion to the Exodor field monster drops  [Machnak Jaw Bone] | Azart Legion Tag, 1 [Avion Dranium Fragment] | Azart Mark, 1 [Royal Azart Powder] | Azart Suppression Medal, 1     Added the following 4 items  Item  Azart Force Badge Azart Token Exodor Superior Belt Box Exodor Superior Mask Box      3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 09월 10일 업데이트 안내 (v87.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v87-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v87-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 필드 보스  마흐나크, 아비온, 로열 파르프 컨텐츠가 중단됩니다. [공지사항 바로가기]  2. 아이템  아래 아이템의 이름, 외형, 아이콘이 변경됩니다.  변경 전  맹렬한 마흐나크의 허리띠 찬란한 마흐나크의 허리띠 맹렬한 아비온의 가면 찬란한 아비온의 가면   변경 후  절멸의 허리띠 검은 태양 허리띠 절멸의 가면 검은 태양 가면     마흐나크의 턱뼈, 아비온의 드라니움 조각, 로열 파르프의 날개가루 교환 목록에 하기 아이템이 추가됩니다.  동일한 위상의 아이템이며, 자세한 내용은 아래에서 안내 드리겠습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.09.05 patch notes (v87.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v87-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v87-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Increased XP reward for completing level 65+ Vanguard Requests and lass boss in dungeons Increased Joy of Partying effect of Macellarius Catacombs from 1.8 times to 1.9 times  2. Partner  Changed to be able to transfer partner Abilities Conditions to activate Gifted Skills for XP boost and skill XP boost has been changed to upon using Bond Skill  3. Class balance  Warrior  Head On (passive)  Changed to only activate crit power effect during Defense Stance   Level 69 Skill Option : Deadly Gamble  Changed [Bellicosity] Skill Option to the following :  Before :  Increase Deadly Gamble duration by 20% during Assault Stance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 09월 05일 업데이트 안내 (v87.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v87-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v87-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  65레벨 이상 파티 던전의 발키온 연합 지령서/마지막 네임드 처치 경험치 보상이 상향됩니다. 데모크론 실험실 3인 입장 시 부여되는 성장의 즐거움 효과가 상향됩니다. (1.8배 → 1.9배)  2. 파트너  파트너간 능력 전수가 가능하도록 변경됩니다. 재능 스킬인 &amp;lsquo;성장 가속&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;연마 가속&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;복합 가속&#39;의 발동 조건이 교감 스킬 사용 시로 변경됩니다.  3. 클래스 밸런스  검투사  정면 승부 [패시브]  치명타 위력 증가 효과가 [강철의 결의 II] 상태에서만 발동하도록 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.29 patch notes (v86.05) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-05/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Increased XP reward of level 65 or above Vanguard Request and final boss Increased Joy of Partying effect of Macellarius Catacombs from 1.8 times to 1.9 times  2. Gear (delayed)  Added new superior brooch Agenvant Brooch Can be equipped starting level 69, and active skill applies Agenvant&#39;s Power buff Upon usage, Azart Energy abnormality is applied for 1.5 minutes, and applies an increase of 30 power, 30 crit factor, and 12% attack speed for 20 seconds  3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 29일 업데이트 안내 (v86.05)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-05/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전 (9/5 적용 예정)  65레벨 이상 파티 던전의 발키온 연합 지령서/마지막 네임드 처치 경험치 보상이 상향됩니다. 데모크론 실험실 3인 입장 시 부여되는 성장의 즐거움 효과가 상향됩니다. (1.8배 → 1.9배)  2. 장비 (9/5 적용 예정)  신규 전설등급 브로치인 &amp;lsquo;맹렬한 아젠반트의 브로치&#39;와 &amp;lsquo;찬란한 아젠반트의 브로치&#39;가 추가됩니다. 69레벨부터 착용이 가능하며, 스킬 숏컷에 등록하여 &amp;lsquo;아젠반트의 힘&amp;rsquo; 버프를 발동시킬 수 있습니다.  사용 시, 아르가프의 힘 이상상태가 1분 30초 부여되며, 20초 동안 힘 30, 치명타 유발 30, 공격 속도가 12% 향상됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.22 patch notes (v86.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-04/</guid>
      <description>1. Field boss monster  Machnak, Avion, Royal Gossamer reopens Changed Royal Gossamer to spawn only in channel 1 Switched last hit reward and jackpot reward  Last hit reward will remain the same to receive both jackpot reward and contribution reward Jackpot reward is randomly given to one participant who has made significant contribution  Boss | last hit reward | jackpot reward  Ortan | Ortan Field Boss Gold Box | Ortan&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Hazard | Hazard Field Boss Gold Box | Hazard&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Cerrus | Cerrus Field Boss Gold Box | Cerrus&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Machnak | Machnak Field Boss Gold Box | Machnak&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Avion | Avion Field Boss Gold Box | Avion&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest       New field boss Agenvant update is delayed until 08/29 (Thurs)  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 22일 업데이트 안내 (v86.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-04/</guid>
      <description>1. 필드 보스 몬스터  마흐나크, 아비온, 로열 파르프 컨텐츠가 재오픈됩니다. 로열 파르프가 1채널에서만 스폰되도록 변경됩니다. 마지막 타격, 대박 보상으로 지급되는 아이템이 서로 변경됩니다.  마지막 타격 보상은 기존과 동일하게 대박 보상 또는 참여 보상과 중복 획득이 가능합니다. 대박 보상은 참여 인원 중 랜덤한 1명에게 지급되며, 처치 기여도가 낮을 경우 추첨 대상에서 제외됩니다.  보스 몬스터 | 마지막 타격 보상 | 대박 보상  오르탄 | 오르탄 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 오르탄의 보물상자 하자르 | 하자르 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 하자르의 보물상자 캘로스 | 캘로스 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 캘로스의 보물상자 마흐나크 | 마흐나크 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 마흐나크의 보물상자 아비온 | 아비온 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 아비온의 보물상자       신규 필드보스: 아젠반트의 업데이트가 8/29(목)으로 연기되었습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.14 patch notes (v86.03.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Exodor  Increased channel count to 3 Temporarily disabled spawn of Royal Parf, Machnak, and Avion  There was an issue where reward was delivered twice; content will reopen as it is fixed    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where reward parcel message for defeating Machnak was awkward Fixed issue where Jump Platforms on outer islands did not operate Fixed issue where Skill Advance data reset after 07/23 maintenance, and items to restore Skill Advance have been sent Skill Advance XP, scrolls, and gems for gold have will be distributed soon   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 14일 업데이트 안내 (v86.03.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03-01/</guid>
      <description>###1. 엑소도르
 채널이 3개로 증가됩니다. 로열 파르프, 마흐나크, 아비온 컨텐츠가 임시 중단됩니다.  특정 상황에서 보상을 중복으로 획득할 수 있는 문제가 확인되어 임시 중단되었으며, 수정 후 재오픈할 수 있도록 하겠습니다. 불편을 드려 죄송합니다.    [버그수정]  마흐나크 처치 보상 우편 문구가 어색한 문제 엑소도르 지역 외곽섬에서 간헐적으로 점프기어를 이용할 수 없는 문제 7/23(화) 점검 이후 초기화된 스킬 연마 정보를 복구할 수 있는 아이템이 지급됩니다. 스킬 연마 경험치, 스크롤, 골드에 상응하는 보석 아이템이 지급될 예정이며, 자세한 내용은 공지사항을 통해 확인해 주시기를 바랍니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.08 patch notes (v86.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Field boss  New : Avion  Spawns south of Vernark Fortress, Exodor (channel 1)  Island can be accessed through Argaff Jump Platforms   Upon defeating Avion, the player dealing the last hit will receive one of the following rewards :  Avion Treasure Box (1 of the following items) :  Shining Avion Mask Fierce Avion Mask   One random participant will also receive the following reward :  Reward  Avion Raid Gold Box     The following contribution reward will be distributed depending on the amount of damage dealt  Damage contribution is party-based No reward will be distributed to players who have not contributed enough to defeat the boss  Reward  Avion Raid Silver Box Avion Raid Box Avion&amp;rsquo;s Dranium Piece           (Fixed) Changed field boss content reward distribution to parcel  As per fix, Machnak and Royal Parf    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 08일 업데이트 안내 (v86.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 필드 보스  신규: 아비온  엑소도르 &amp;lsquo;베르아크 성채&amp;rsquo; 남동쪽의 &amp;lsquo;아르가프 침공지&amp;rsquo; 섬지역에 출몰합니다. (1채널)  아르가프 도약대를 이용하여 진입할 수 있습니다.   아비온 처치 시, 마지막 타격을 가한 캐릭터에게 아래와 같은 보상이 지급됩니다.  아비온의 보물상자 (하기 아이템 중 1종 획득)  찬란한 아비온의 가면 맹렬한 아비온의 가면     참여한 캐릭터 중 1명에게 참여보상 대신 아래와 같은 보상이 지급됩니다.  보상 아이템  아비온 공격대의 금빛 상자     필드보스 HP 감소 기여도에 따라 아래와 같은 참여 보상이 차등 지급됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.01 patch notes (v86.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Argaff&amp;rsquo;s Hatchery  Increased spawn rate of Nomadic Caimans and Dimensional Portal  2. Field Boss Monster  Reinforced criteria for earning wnd rank participation reward  3. Quest  Changed Card Index completion progress reward  Removed progression stage reward for completing Big Horn Argaff card set    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where Skill Advance points and Skill Advance state reset (to zero) Fixed issue where sorting inventory occasionally causes client to crash Fixed issue where using skill that reduce damage caused PC to decrease in defense (fixed Bamarama issue as well) Fixed issue where Slayer&amp;rsquo;s Measured Slice was coded as magical damage Fixed issue where Ninja&amp;rsquo;s Boomerang Shuriken&amp;rsquo;s skill damage was unexpectedly high Fixed issue where recent transactions on trade broker displayed irregular item levels Fixed issue where UI scaling did not affect pop-up UI for purchasing items Fixed issue where changing party or raid while fighting field boss monster resulted in rewarded twice the participation reward Fixed issue where participation reward was distributed for defeating Ortan, Cerrus, and Hazard to players who did not participate directly but had party/raid members who did Fixed issue where rewards for a different class was distributed for defeating Ortan, Cerrus, and Hazard Fixed issue where Partners occasionally spoke about item level Fixed issue where players could proceed through without being directed by quest NPC Fixed issue where certain NPCs were stacked Fixed issue where Nomadic Merchants could spawn in all channels Fixed issue where players could receive multiple quest items through Etching Crafting tutorial Fixed issue where items with expire dates had their extended expire dates reset to their issue dates when placed in bank Fixed issue where cracked ground aesthetics for Machnak combat area seemed like it was floating Fixed issue where returning player items displayed different expire date and stats than intended Fixed issue where Map and Intel pieces in Guild Bank did not disappear event after their expire dates have passed Fixed issue where summoned Partners displayed a chat upon spawning in each area Fixed a K TERA exclusive issue Fixed issue where using a skill in Velika: Civil Unrest causes self-damage   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 01일 업데이트 안내 (v86.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 아르가프 부화장  떠돌이 시누스와 차원문의 스폰 확률이 상향됩니다.  2. 필드 보스 몬스터  참여 보상 중, 2등급 보상(ex: 마흐나크 공격대의 상자)을 얻을 수 있는 기준이 완화됩니다.  3. 퀘스트  도감 편찬 퀘스트의 진행 단계가 일부 변경됩니다.  &amp;lsquo;큰 뿔 아르가스&amp;rsquo; 카드를 도감에 등록하는 단계가 제거됩니다.    [버그수정]  업데이트 이후 스킬 연마 포인트 및 연마 상태가 초기화된 문제 자동정렬 기능 사용 시 간헐적으로 서버가 다운되는 문제 데미지 감소 스킬 사용 시, PC의 방어력이 감소되는 문제 (임시 중단되었던 투기장이 정상화 되었습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.07.25 patch notes (v86.01.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Exodor  Increased channel count in all Exodor regions except Core region Added sub-title Butterfly Signal Distractor to two of the monsters  2. Quest  K TERA exclusive comment  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where Baramara BAMs did not fight one another Fixed issue where zone quest did not count while completing dungeon as a raid Fixed issue in Verark Fortress where certain 2nd boss mechanic caused client to crash Fixed issue in Verark Fortress where players could mount flying mounts in combat arena Fixed issue where certain NPC for Exodor story quest was placed twice Fixed issue where defeating quest monster before talking to Jalena preventing quest progress Fixed issue where completing Gathering Effect in Index UI prevented changing tabs Fixed issue where a certain monster&amp;rsquo;s effects did not display properly Fixed issue where spawn rate of Dimensional Portal upon defeating Nomadic Caimans was unexpectedly high during party status Fixed issue where 2019 summer event items displayed faulty expiration date Fixed issue where system message upon trying to inspect a logged out character had a typo   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 07월 25일 업데이트 안내 (v86.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 엑소도르  코어 지역을 제외하고 엑소도르 지역의 채널이 최대 3개로 증가합니다. 엑소도르 지역 &amp;lsquo;붉은 이끼게&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;외눈가시&amp;rsquo; 네임드 몬스터의 호칭으로 &amp;lsquo;나비 귀환지의 방해꾼&#39;이 추가됩니다.  2. 퀘스트  6/20 ~ 7/25 기간 진행 된 신규/복귀 이벤트의 &amp;lsquo;의뢰서 – 아르보레아 전선 돌파 I&amp;rsquo; 퀘스트 조건이 변경됩니다.  시험의 던전 – 황금의 미궁 2회 클리어 -&amp;gt; 천공의 경기장 2회 클리어    [버그수정]  투기장에서 몬스터가 서로 전투를 하지 않는 문제 녹슬지 않는 실력 1 퀘스트에서 공격대 상태로 몬스터 처치 시 카운팅되지 않는 문제 베르아크 성채 비밀지역 2네임드 특정 스킬 사용 시, 간헐적으로 클라이언트 크래시가 발생하는 문제 베르아크 성채 비밀지역 전투 공간에서 비행 탈 것 탑승이 가능한 문제 엑소도르 퀘스트 중 일부 퀘스트에서 NPC가 중복 배치되는 문제 코어 폭파 퀘스트 진행 중, 쟈넬라 NPC와 대화하기 전 칼리가르 몬스터 처치 시 진행이 불가능한 문제 수집 효과 UI에서 카드 완성 시, 탭이 넘어가지 않는 문제 뼈아귀 괴물의 이펙트가 출력되지 않는 문제 차원문, 소환된 파르프 등 몬스터 처치 시 스폰되는 NPC가 파티 상태에서 스폰 확률이 비정상적으로 증가하는 문제 2019 썸머 이벤트 아이템 툴팁의 삭제 일자가 잘못 기재되어 있는 문제 로그아웃 한 캐릭터를 살펴보기 했을 시 출력되는 안내 메시지에 오타가 있는 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.07.23 patch notes (v86.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Zone expansion  Expanded floating island “Exodor” zone  A new story quest is obtained from NPC 에키오르 라펠레이트 upon completing [Important] Bringing Down Exodor story quest Said NPC is located at Spring Valley Exodor consists of four regions :  Garden Ranch Viridian Wetland Verark Fortress      2. Dungeon  New : Vernark Fortress (5-man)  Instance Matching System can be accessed upon reaching level 69, and item level 458 Requires 385 Aventure Coins to enter, and is limited to 40 entries (80 for Elite) per week Teleportal is located on the upper floor of Verark Fortress, Exodor   Added Skill Advance XP reward to the following 12 dungeons  Dungeon :  Rakelith&amp;rsquo;s Manor (normal/hard) RK-9 Kennel (normal/hard) Velik&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary (normal/hard) Grotto of Lost Souls (normal/hard) Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (normal/hard) Forsaken Island Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum     Ghillieglade  Changed starting location to the front of the bridge   Red Refuge  Added a dungeon-specific weapon design  Argog Weapon  Can be obtained as weapon skin box, or by combining Refined Metal (가공된 광물) and Argog&amp;rsquo;s Toenail obtained upon defeating Argog       Ace dungeon  Changed level appropriately, and adjusted reward accordingly  Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Trial : ilvl 431 Akasha&amp;rsquo;s Trial : ilvl 412 to ilvl 439 Baracos&amp;rsquo; Trial : ilvl 412 to ilvl 446   Adjusted to increased Golden Talent and Silver Talent Added to apply a movement speed buff through all Ace dungeons Increased elevator speed in Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Trial   Celestial Arena  Changed total stage count (from 7 to 5) Changed monster HP, and revised to move to the next stage faster upon defeating all monsters Adjusted to increase Golden Talent/Daric/Plate and Silver Talent/Daric/Plate reward Changed item level appropriately (from 412 to 439) Significantly increased audience cheer buff   Adjusted to increase the enchanting material reward of the following dungeons :  Ravenous Gorge Channelworks Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold Thaumetal Refinery Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Keep    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 07월 23일 업데이트 안내 (v86.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 지역 확장  공중섬 &amp;lsquo;엑소도르&amp;rsquo; 지역이 확장됩니다.  &amp;lsquo;[중요] 격추 시도&amp;rsquo; 퀘스트 완료 및 68레벨 달성 시, &amp;lsquo;에키오르 라펠레이트&amp;rsquo; NPC를 통해 &amp;lsquo;엑소도르로 가는 길&amp;rsquo; 미션 퀘스트를 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다. 에키오르 라펠레이트 NPC는 바라카니아 구릉지&amp;gt;바라카니아 경제인 연합에 위치합니다. &amp;lsquo;엑소도르&#39;는 아래 4가지 지역으로 구성되어 있습니다.  로가쉬의 장원 엑소도르의 대농장 비리디안 습지대 베르아크 성채      2. 던전  신규: 베르아크 성채 비밀지역 (5인)  69레벨, 장비레벨 458 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.07.11 patch notes (v85.05) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-05/</guid>
      <description>1. Class  Priest  Zenobia&amp;rsquo;s Vortex Shocking Implosion  Increased HP regeneration of Zenobia&amp;rsquo;s Vortex by 2 times during Edict of Judgement   Triple Nemesis  Adjusted to increase duration of Glyph of Enfeeblement abnormality from 12 seconds to 21 seconds   Guardian&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary  Changed HP regeneration Changed to casting to be instant instead of having a 1.5 second casting duration      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 07월 11일 업데이트 안내 (v85.05)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-05/</guid>
      <description>1. 클래스  사제  심판의 손길  심판의 주문 상태에서 심판의 손길 스킬의 HP 회복량이 2배 상향됩니다.   천벌의 연쇄  약화의 문장 효과의 지속시간이 12초에서 21초로 조정됩니다.   평정의 가호  HP 회복량이 변경됩니다. 시전 시간이 1.5초에서 즉시 시전으로 변경됩니다.      [개발자 코멘트] -사제의 경우, [천벌의 연쇄 – 약화의 문장]의 효과 지속시간이 짧은 관계로 너무 잦은 빈도로 신경 써야만 하는 상황이었습니다. 따라서 지속시간을 상향 조정하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.07.04 patch notes (v85.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-04/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Forsaken Island (hard) (5-man)  Instance matching system can be used starting level 65, at item level 453 and above Costs 150 Adventure Coins, and can be accessed once per day (twice for VIP) Teleportal is located at Cutthroat Harbor Loot table includes Stormcry gear box, Sacred Mallet, Weights, Halidoms/Relics, Naslow&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Map right piece, and Mysterious Intel right piece   Forsaken Island (5-man)  Instance matching system can be used starting level 65, at item level 438 and above Costs 75 Adventure Coins, and can be accessed once per day (twice for VIP) Teleportal is located at Cutthroat Harbor Loot table includes Frostmetal gear box, Carved Ornament, Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools, Otherworldly Shard, Onset Mask, Sacred Mallet, Weights, Halidoms/Relics, and Naslow&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Map left piece   Ghillieglade  Added Superior innerwear as item reward  Supperior innerwear can now be used with randomizer cube   Slightly increased Goldfinger Token drop rate and drop amount    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 07월 04일 업데이트 안내 (v85.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-04/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  저주받은 번스타인의 악령섬 (5인)  66레벨, 장비 레벨 453 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 입장 시 모험의 주화가 150 소모되며, 1일 1회(VIP/월간패스 2회) 입장 가능합니다. 동부 가드&amp;gt;거친 항구&amp;gt;차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 울부짖는 분노의 장비 상자, 신성한 망치, 무게추, 유물/성물, 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 오른반쪽, 의문의 첩보 조각 오른반쪽 등의 아이템을 보상으로 획득할 수 있습니다. (추가) 사망 시 부활이 불가능하며, 마지막 보스 몬스터 HP 35% 미만에서만 사제/정령사의 부활 스킬로 부활이 가능합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.06.27 patch notes (v85.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Demokron Factory (normal/hard)  Adjusted to reduce HP of bosses    2. Vanguard Initiative Request  Added level XP to the following solo content Vanguard Requests :  Content :  The Pit of Petrax Echoes of Aranea Celestial Arena Ace Dungeon : Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Trial Ace Dungeon : Akasha&amp;rsquo;s Trial Ace Dungeon : Baracos&amp;rsquo; Trial Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Naga Battlemasters Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Iron Giants Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Onyx Hydraths Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Bloodbound Teraliths Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Fimbrilisks Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Searing Fangspawns Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Basilisks Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Orisks Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Ovoliths      3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 06월 27일 업데이트 안내 (v85.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  베르노의 실험실/포악한 베르노의 실험실  네임드 몬스터의 HP가 하향 조정됩니다.    2. 발키온 연합 지령서  하기의 솔로 컨텐츠 지령서에 레벨 경험치가 추가됩니다.  컨텐츠명  페트레 양성소 라크난 성의 기억 천공의 경기장 시험의 던전 – 릴리스의 성 시험의 던전 – 아카샤의 은신처 시험의 던전 – 황금의 미궁 흉포한 비늘 전사(상) 토벌 흉포한 강철 거인(상) 토벌 흉포한 어둠의 화신(상) 토벌 흉포한 블러드 골렘(중) 토벌 흉포한 다크리퍼(중) 토벌 흉포한 지옥불 괴수(중) 토벌 흉포한 바실리스크(하) 토벌 흉포한 기가니아(하) 토벌 흉포한 아라크네아(하) 토벌      3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.06.20 patch notes (v85.02.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Bug fixes  Fixed issue in Gossamer&amp;rsquo;s Vault (hard) where certain mechanics could be cancelled Fixed issue where certain Summer Festival event costumes could be used to as fodder for random costume box Fixed issue where Nomadic merchants spawned in all channels Fixed issue where gathering speed for certain gathering nodes was irregular   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 06월 20일 업데이트 안내 (v85.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-02-01/</guid>
      <description>[버그수정]
 특정 방법으로 찬란한 파르퀴나의 둥지 2네임드의 일부 패턴을 캔슬할 수 있는 문제 여름축제 이벤트 의상을 세미의 랜덤 큐브 재료로 사용할 수 있는 문제 유랑 상인이 모든 채널에서 스폰되는 문제 특정 채집물의 채집 속도가 비정상적인 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.06.13 patch notes (v85.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Balance  Mystic  Arunic Release  Increased crit chance by 2 times     Priest, Mystic  Battle Solution  Changed effect from increase attack speed to increase crit power  Crit power value is the same as other classes        2. Summer festival  K TERA comments  3. Dungeon  Adventure Coin cost has been reduced for the following dungeons :  Gossamer&amp;rsquo;s Vault (hard) : from 435 to 370 Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum : from 345 to 295 Demokron Factory (hard) : from 390 to 330 Gossamer&amp;rsquo;s Vault : from 290 to 245 Demokron Factory : from 260 to 220    4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 06월 13일 업데이트 안내 (v85.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 밸런스  정령사  정기 폭발  치명타 발생 확률이 2배로 상향됩니다.     사제, 정령사  전투 비약  기존의 공격속도 증가에서 치명타 위력 증가로 변경됩니다.  치명타 위력 증가 수치는 다른 클래스와 동일합니다.        [개발자 코멘트]
 힐러 클래스가 필드 사냥 시 보다 수월하게 플레이 할 수 있도록 공격속도 증가 옵션에서 치명타 위력 증가 옵션으로 변경됩니다. 또한 치명타 위력이 타 클래스와 같은 수준으로 적용되므로 파티 플레이에서 보다 공격적으로 플레이가 가능합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.06.03 patch notes (v85.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v85-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  New : Argaff&amp;rsquo;s Nest (hard)  Added a hard mode to existing Argaff&amp;rsquo;s Nest (1-man) Requires level 65, and can enter as a party (max 5-man)  Can only be accessed by party members of an existing party made before the dimensional portal spawns   Entry method is the same as is with existing Argaff&amp;rsquo;s Nest (1-man), and can receive approxiately 1.5 times the experience points   Reinforced certain wipe mechanics in Demon&amp;rsquo;s Wheel  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 06월 03일 업데이트 안내 (v85.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v85-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  신규: 아르가프 부화장(하드)  기존 아르가프 부화장(1인)의 고난이도 버전이 추가됩니다. 65레벨부터 입장할 수 있으며, 파티 상태로 이용이 가능합니다. (최대 5인 입장 가능)  차원문이 소환되기 전에 파티 상태였던 캐릭터만 함께 입장이 가능합니다.   입장 방법은 기존 아르가프 부화장(1인)과 동일하며, 경험치와 보상을 약 1.5배 더 획득할 수 있습니다. [아르가프 부화장 소개]   데모로스의 룰렛 던전 일부 전멸 패턴 난이도가 완화됩니다.  2. 필드  수호자 임무  태양의 정원 구출 작전 &amp;amp; 쿠챠트와 검은 그림자 임무 보스 몬스터의 HP가 증가됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.23 patch notes (v84.05) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-05/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Demon&amp;rsquo;s Wheel (5-man)  Open until maintenance on 6/27 Requires level 65, and item level 446 to use instance matching system Consumes 145 Adventure Coins upon entry, with up to 40 entries per week (80 enrties for VIP) Teleportal is located at Allementheia Outskirts   Loot table includes Gold/Silver Plate, Otherworldly Shard, Archdevan Formula, Scavenged Supplies, Devil&amp;rsquo;s Claws, Dragon Skull, and [Event] Demoros&amp;rsquo; Supply Box. Mysterious Intel pieces and Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 23일 업데이트 안내 (v84.05)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-05/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  데모로스의 룰렛(5인)  6/27(목) 점검 전까지 기간 한정으로 오픈됩니다. 65레벨, 장비 레벨 446 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 입장 시 모험의 주화가 145 소모되며, 주간 40회(VIP/월간패스 80회)까지 입장 가능합니다. 알레만시아 인근 &amp;lsquo;산 알레마 마을&#39;의 차원의 게이트를 통해 던전에 입장할 수 있습니다. 아르보레아의 금/은빛 판금, 이공간의 파편, 불길한 마법 스크롤, 낡은 보급품, 악마의 발톱, 용의 두개골, [이벤트] 데모로스의 낡은 상자 등의 보상을 획득할 수 있습니다. (기간 한정 이벤트 던전에서는 첩보 지도 조각, 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각이 드랍되지 않습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.16 patch notes (v84.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-04/</guid>
      <description>1. Other  Leaderboard  Extended current season by 7 days (5/9~6/13)    Bug fixes  Fixed issue in Gossamer Vault (hard) where certain last boss mechanics prevented voice lines from playing Fixed issue in Argaff Hatchery where a certain enemy pushed Brawlers that are blocking Fixed issue in Argaff Hatchery where players could move inside of a certain enemy Fixed issue where event gear that maxes at +7 could be registered in enchant UI Fixed issue where registering pet bank skill to skillslot UI and moving the skill to another slot displayed a default skill icon Fixed issue where players could go through certain objectives using Priest&amp;rsquo;s Divine Charge Fixed issue where premium slot items did not rest occasionally Fixed issue where certain items could be stored in bank and guild bank Fixed issue where rested XP stacked differently than intended (수정) 휴식 경험치 획득 방식이 몬스터 처치 시 획득 경험치를 기준으로 적용되지 않고 있던 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 16일 업데이트 안내 (v84.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-04/</guid>
      <description>1. 기타  던전/전장 순위표  5시즌 진행 기간이 7일 연장됩니다. (5/9 ~ 6/13)    [버그수정]  찬란한 파르퀴나의 둥지 던전에서 2네임드가 특정 패턴 사용 시 대사가 출력되지 않는 문제 아르가프 부화장의 황금 유충이 방어 중인 권술사를 밀어내는 문제 아르가프 부화장의 황금 유충의 배에 캐릭터가 묻히는 문제 7강화 몽환의 장갑, 신발 아이템을 강화 UI에 등록할 수 있는 문제 펫 보관함을 스킬 슬롯에 등록 후 슬롯 변경 시 더미 이미지가 출력되는 문제 사제 혼신의 주문 사용 시 일부 오브젝트를 뚫고 이동할 수 있는 문제 66레벨 이상부터 특성 공격력 증가 효과가 적용되지 않는 문제 간헐적으로 프리미엄 슬롯 아이템이 초기화되지 않는 문제 길드 창고 보관 가능, 계정 창고 보관 불가 속성의 아이템을 길드 창고에 보관할 수 없는 문제 휴식 경험치 중첩 방식이 사양과 다르게 적용되고 있던 문제 (수정) 휴식 경험치 획득 방식이 몬스터 처치 시 획득 경험치를 기준으로 적용되지 않고 있던 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.09 patch notes (v84.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Balance  Slayer  Overhand Strike: Focus  Adjusted to increased skill damage increase per stack from 1% to 2% (max stack from 15% to 30%)   Propulsion  Changed requirement to decrease cooldown of Measured Slice from &amp;lsquo;upon critical hit&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;upon hit&amp;rsquo; with Whirlwind   Punishing Blow  Increased skill damage by 10%      2. Content  Nomadic Caiman &amp;amp; Argaff Hatchery  Adjusted to increase chance to spawn Nomadic Caiman or Dimensional Door by 4 times Adjusted to decrease XP gained from defeating Nomadic Caiman Adjusted to decrease XP and skill advancement XP gained from defeating Hatchery monsters   Argaff Scout Intel  Changed Doubtful Intel piece to drop in the following dungeons  From Doubtful Intel (Left) to Doubtful Intel (Right)  Red Refuge RK9-Kennel Dark Reach Citadel Velik&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary Shadow Sanguinary Grotto of Lost Souls Ruinous Manor Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss     Changed Doubtful Intel piece to drop from the following monsters  From Doubtful Intel (Left) to either Doubtful Intel (Left) or Doubtful Intel (Right) (by chance)  List of 28 level 65-70 monsters  그림자 경계병 철갑가시 오칸 병든 롱터스크 불타는 유적 길리두 성역의 파수꾼 오염된 롱터스크 오염된 뿌리약탈자 폐허 파괴자 알쿠스 부활의 나무 오염된 볼칸 야수의 숲 볼칸 폐허를 방황하는 악마 시간의 수호자 오염된 뿌리약탈자 아둔한 장물꾼 사막 바실리스크 푸른이끼부족 예언가 파르프 비열한 도굴꾼 폐허 하이에나 푸른이끼부족 주술사 파르폰 둥근 부리 파수꾼 검은불꽃 알쿠스 푸른이끼부족 전사 폭주한 황금 정원사 낡은 거인의 하수꾼 고블린 도둑          3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 09일 업데이트 안내 (v84.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-03/</guid>
      <description>###1. 밸런스
 무사  일도양단: 집중  일도양단: 집중 중첩 당 상승되는 모든 스킬의 위력이 1%에서 2%로 상향 조정됩니다. (최대 중첩 시 15% -&amp;gt; 30%)   추진력  일섬 스킬의 재사용 대기시간 감소 조건이 회전 베기 &amp;lsquo;치명타 적중 시&#39;에서 &amp;lsquo;적중 시&#39;로 변경됩니다.   참격  스킬 위력이 기존대비 10% 상향됩니다.      [개발자 코멘트]
 추진력 패시브 변경을 통해 치명타 의존도를 감소시켰습니다. 이를 통해 회전 베기 치명타 여부에 따라 딜사이클이 자주 변경되어 무사의 난이도가 높아지는 문제를 완화하고자 하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.05.02 patch notes (v84.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Other  Changed path guide in Necromancer&amp;rsquo;s Tomb (1-man) Changed certain level progression instances to reset automatically upon re-entering the instance for convenience  Quest progression is adjusted accordingly Instances of the following quest are reset automatically :  Quest  1507 ???? (전염병의 원인을 찾아서) 2501 Secrets Not Meant to Be Known 2801 Vision of Destiny 3901 Unveil the Mask 401 Rescue the Core 5601 Drowned In Blood 5602 Sikander&amp;rsquo;s Bane 3702 Fragment of Hope 5201 Into the Furnace 17207 The Battle for Intrepid       Decreased chance of getting Banana Peel from Weird Sack (placeholder) from 50% to 20% for Stolen Cure quest  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 05월 02일 업데이트 안내 (v84.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 기타  사령술 연구소(1인) 던전 길찾기 가이드가 변경됩니다. 성장구간 퀘스트 진행 중 초기화되지 않으면 진행이 어려운 특수 공간들에 대해 재입장 시 자동으로 초기화되도록 변경됩니다.  특수공간 초기화에 맞춰 퀘스트도 진행하기 좋은 단계로 재설정됩니다. 특수공간 리스트는 아래와 같습니다.  퀘스트명 | 지역명  전염병의 원인을 찾아서 | 호송대 습격지 잊혀져야 하는 힘 | 고통의 전당 태고신의 파편 | 생명의 샘 가면을 벗겨라 | [툴사의 군단 지휘소, 말라키의 실험실] 코어 구출 작전 | 폭염의 산맥 심층부 피의 기둥을 파괴하라 | 칠흑의 제단 켈사이크 부활 저지 | 부활의 성소 희망의 조각 | 광대의 별장 용광로 속으로 | 용암의 홀 초대하지 않은 손님 | 엘카이아호       &amp;lsquo;도둑맞은 치료제&amp;rsquo; 퀘스트의 수상한 자루에서 바나나 껍질이 등장할 확률이 감소됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.04.25 patch notes (v84.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v84-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  New: Azart Hatchery (1-man)  Can be entered through a warp hole randomly generated by defeating Nomadic Caiman and/or level 65 and/or above monsters/BAMs Loot table includes Skill Advancement XP and Naga Guard Chest (placeholder) (Blightoath gear, rare Halidom/Relic)  Nomadic Caiman     Nomadic Caiman spawns by defeating level 65 and/or above monsters from the following zones Loot table includes Skill Advancement XP and Worldly Crystal :  Location  Celestial Hills Essenian Crest Timeless Woods Balder&amp;rsquo;s Refuge Ex Prima Sienna Canyon Progression dungeon   Changed Relic Weapon drop to be class-relevant to the classes within party    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 04월 25일 업데이트 안내 (v84.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v84-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  신규: 아르가프 부화장(1인)  떠돌이 시누스 혹은 65레벨 이상 일반/중형 몬스터를 처치 시 확률적으로 차원문이 등장하며, 해당 차원문을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. [아르가프 부화장 컨텐츠 소개 GM노트] 던전 보상으로 스킬 연마 경험치, 나가 경비병의 소지품(녹슨 맹세의 장비, 희귀 성물/유물)을 획득할 수 있습니다.  떠돌이 시누스     아래 지역의 65레벨 이상 몬스터 처치 시 확률적으로 &amp;lsquo;떠돌이 시누스&#39;가 등장합니다. 보상으로 스킬 연마 경험치, 세계의 결정을 획득할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.04.18 patch notes (v83.06) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-06/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Demokron Factory (nm/hm)  Changed 2nd boss to no longer be immune to damage during poison panel pattern    2. Item  Changed the following level progression quest items to be collected in its respective quest :  Quest name : Quest item  1506 ???? (붉은 저주의 마을) : 602033 ???? (광혈병 연구 보고서) 1507 ???? (전염병의 원인을 찾아서) : 602042 ???? (옛 보급창고 기록) 1505 Discredit Where Credit Is Due : 602039 ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 04월 18일 업데이트 안내 (v83.06)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-06/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  베르노의 실험실, 포악한 베르노의 실험실  2네임드가 독 장판 패턴을 사용할 때 무적 상태가 되지 않도록 변경됩니다.    2. 아이템  하기의 성장구간 퀘스트 아이템들이 퀘스트 진행 중 수거되도록 변경됩니다.  퀘스트 명 | 퀘스트 아이템  붉은 저주의 마을 | 광혈병 연구 보고서 전염병의 원인을 찾아서 | 옛 보급창고 기록 수상한 호출 | 특무대 명령서 그림자 지우기 | 거친 항구 첩자 보고서 티르카이 숲의 복구 | 오염된 버섯 새로운 적 | 잠입부대 신호기 든든한 지원 | 아크데바의 표식 냉정과 열정사이 | 포아롱의 두근두근 러브레터 아논족의 비극 | 시오즈의 초상화 다가오는 어둠 | 칸스트리아 정찰병의 징표     &amp;lsquo;사교도의 근거지로&amp;rsquo; 퀘스트 아이템이 파괴는 불가하나, 상점에 판매할 수 있도록 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.04.11 patch notes (v83.05) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-05/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Demokron Factory (hard) .. 7-man instance  Level 67 dungeon, requiring ilvl 456 Costs 490 Adventure Coins, limited to 40 entries a week (80 for Elite) Teleportal is located at Arx Umbra, Northern Arun Loot table includes Advance Skill XP, upgrade materials for Luminescent Necklace/Circlet, and Dr. Wilson&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Map (Right)   Demokron Factory .. 7-man instance  Level 66 dungeon, requiring ilvl 453 Costs 260 Adventure Coins, limited to 40 entries a week (80 for Elite) Teleportal is located at Arx Umbra, Northern Arun Loot table includes Advance Skill XP, Devil&amp;rsquo;s Claws, Dragon Skull, and Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 04월 11일 업데이트 안내 (v83.05)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-05/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  포악한 베르노의 실험실 (7인)  67레벨, 장비 레벨 456 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 입장 시 모험의 주화가 390 소모되며, 주간 40회(VIP/월간패스 80회)까지 입장 가능합니다. 바라카니아 가드&amp;gt;제국의 땅&amp;gt;차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 스킬 연마 경험치, 광명의 목걸이,서클릿 승급 재료(정화된 신수의 고리 조각, 정화된 신수의 장식 조각), 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 오른반쪽 등의 아이템을 보상으로 획득할 수 있습니다.   베르노의 실험실 (7인)  66레벨, 장비 레벨 453 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.04.09 patch notes (v83.04.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-04-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-04-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Services  Changed XP Boost items to stack  Skill XP Boost, EP Boost, Reputation Boost  Stacked items are inactive, and activates upon expiration of the existing boost      Bug fixes  Fixed issue where XP Boost item effects ended upon entering Battleground   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 04월 09일 업데이트 안내 (v83.04.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-04-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-04-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 부가서비스  경험치 획득량 증가 아이템을 중복으로 사용 시 이상상태가 누적되도록 변경됩니다.  스킬 연마 5(15일/30일), 해결사 50(15일/30일), 발키온 연합 해결사 50(15일/30일)  중복으로 사용한 아이템은 비활성 효과로 전환되어, 기존 효과 기간 만료 시 자동으로 활성화되어 효과가 적용됩니다. (최대 5개까지 누적 가능)      [버그수정]  경험치 획득량 증가 버프 아이템 효과가 전장 입장 시 해제되는 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.04.04 patch notes (v83.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-04/</guid>
      <description>1. Balance  Mystic  Enhanced: Thrall of Life  Changed to recover HP and cleanse caster as well upon using skill     Healer (common)  Ressurection  Adjusted skill effect to display the actual effect radius Changed to display skill effect equally for all race types     Reaper  Level 69 Talyph Dark Veil  Changed to increase cooldown of Shadow Reaping by a factor of 2     Ninja  Enhanced Burning Heart  Adjusted skill hit range     Slayer  Savage Strike  Adjusted to decrease skill cancel time after first hit for fluid chaining of skills      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 04월 04일 업데이트 안내 (v83.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-04/</guid>
      <description>1. 밸런스  정령사  강화: 생명의 정령  스킬 사용 시 HP 회복과 정화 기능이 시전자에게도 적용 가능하도록 변경됩니다.      [개발자 코멘트]
  현재 정령사의 자가 회복 능력이 다소 낮은 수준으로 판단되어 &amp;lsquo;강화: 생명의 정령&amp;rsquo; 소환 시 광역 회복 및 정화 효과를 시전자를 포함한 최대 5명에게 줄 수 있도록 상향 조정하였습니다. 다만, HP가 낮은 대상에게 회복 효과가 우선 적용되므로 파티원이 많은 공격대 상태에서는 상황에 따라 자신에게 회복 효과가 적용되지 않을 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.03.28 patch notes (v83.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Parquina&amp;rsquo;s Nest (hard)  Changed Adventure Coin cost from 535 to 435   Macellarius Catacombs (3-man)  Can access upon reaching level 65, item level 440 Costs 285 Adventure Coins, and can access up to 40 times (80 times for VIP) per week Teleportal is located in Arx Umbra Loot table contains Experience Scroll I (time limited), Emeralds, Relic/Hallow, merging material   Manglemire (5-man)  Reopened until April 18th Can access upon reaching level 65, item level 439 Costs 80 Adventure Coins, and can access up to 1 time (2 times for VIP) per day Teleportal is located in Pora Elinu Loot table contains Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools, Copper Clasp, Liquid Metal, Dyad Niveot Structure, Hypnotic Device, Archdevan Surfactant    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 03월 28일 업데이트 안내 (v83.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  찬란한 파르퀴나의 둥지  모험의 주화 소모량이 535 -&amp;gt; 435로 변경됩니다.   데모크론 실험실 (3인)  65레벨, 장비 레벨 440 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 입장 시 모험의 주화가 285 소모되며, 주간 40회(VIP/월간패스 80회)까지 입장 가능합니다. 바라카니아 가드&amp;gt;제국의 땅&amp;gt;라크난의 요새&amp;gt;차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. (수정) 경험치 서적 I(기간제), 에메랄드, 유물/성물 아이템, 합성 재료 장비 아이템 등을 보상으로획득하실 수 있습니다. (데모크론 실험실에서는 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각이 드랍되지 않습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.03.21 patch notes (v83.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Servant (placeholder)  Revised Servant functions  Added on/off toggle for Servant chat bubbles  Option is available through Option &amp;gt; Game &amp;gt; Community   Added sort, delete function  Can be sorted through Servant UI, via &amp;lsquo;sort&amp;rsquo; button Can delete Servant through Servant UI, via &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; button   Changed to be able to summon Servant via hotkey  Option is available through Option &amp;gt; Key settings &amp;gt; Servant      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 03월 21일 업데이트 안내 (v83.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 서번트  서번트 기능이 개선되었습니다.  서번트 말풍선 ON/OFF 기능이 추가되었습니다.  시스템 설정 &amp;gt; 게임 설정 &amp;gt; 커뮤니티 &amp;gt; 서번트 말풍선 감추기 경로에서 설정하실 수 있습니다.   서번트 정렬, 삭제 기능이 추가됩니다.  서번트 목록 UI 창에서 &amp;lsquo;관리&amp;rsquo; 버튼을 통해 정렬하실 수 있습니다. 서번트 목록 UI에서 서번트에 &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; 버튼을 사용하여 삭제하실 수 있습니다.   서번트를 단축키로 소환할 수 있게 됩니다.  시스템 설정 &amp;gt; 단축키 설정 &amp;gt; 서번트 경로에서 설정하실 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.03.14 patch notes (v83.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v83-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Balance  Gunner  Bombardment  Changed cooldown start point to the start of missile launch After using skill, if the skill is cancelled before missile launch, then cooldown does not apply      2. Battleground  Battleground matching  Changed to form teams based on player rankings Applies to all battlegrounds with ranking    3. Merchant NPC  Added magic materials merchant in cities (Highwatch, Velika, Allementheia, Kaiator) The following items are sold :  Supreme Metal Enchantment Seal Accessory Morpher Uncommon Accessory Morpher Ancient Accessory Morpher   Added Ancient Accessory Morpher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 03월 14일 업데이트 안내 (v83.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v83-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 밸런스  마공사  폭격탄  발사의 재사용 대기시간이 적용되는 시점이 폭격탄이 발사되는 시점으로 변경됩니다. 스킬 사용 후, 폭격탄 발사 스킬의 공격이 발동되기 전 다른 스킬을 통해 스킬을 취소시킬 경우 재사용 대기시간이 적용되지 않습니다.      2. 전장  전장 매칭  전장 팀 구성 시 플레이어가 평점을 기준으로 양 팀에 고르게 분배됩니다. 적용되는 전장은 평점이 존재하는 모든 전장입니다.    3. 상인 NPC  대도시(이르카, 벨리카, 알레만시아, 카이아도르)에 마법재료 상인이 추가됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.03.07 patch notes (v82.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-04/</guid>
      <description>1. Balance  Sorcerer  Slightly decreased aggro obtained from the following skills :  Ice Lance Iceberg Prime Flame Arcane Storm Fusion     Priest  Focus Heal, focus talyph option  Changed from healing 2.5% HP per second for 5 seconds to healing 120 HP per second for 5 seconds Changed to apply effect from healing stats     Mystic  Arun&amp;rsquo;s Vitae - Glyph of Restoration  Changed from healing 20% HP to 35,000 HP after using skill      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 03월 07일 업데이트 안내 (v82.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-04/</guid>
      <description>1. 밸런스  마법사  하기의 스킬의 어그로 획득량이 소폭 하향됩니다.  얼음창 빙하 융기 태초의 불꽃 비전 폭풍 원소 융합     사제  치유의 빛 치유 옵션  5초간 1초마다 HP 2.5% 회복에서 5초간 1초마다 HP 120 회복으로 변경됩니다. 회복 성능에 영향을 받습니다.     정령사  회복의 정기 - 근성의 문장  스킬 사용 후 HP 20% 회복에서 HP 35,000 회복으로 변경됩니다.      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.02.28 patch notes (v82.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Battleground  Wintera Snowfield  Reopened Wintera Snowfield  KTERA exclusive operation hours     Vanguard Request reward  100 Gold 1215 EP XP 1650 item XP Optional : [100 Gold|1215 EP XP]   Win/loss reward  Win : 40x Wintera Battleground Tokens, 130,000 BC credits Lose : 20x Wintera Battleground Tokens, 43,000 BC credits    2. Other  Added guide description to gift/feed servant in UI Added option to open pet bank through bank NPC  Option is only available to characters that have pets with bank abilities    Bug fixes  Fixed issue at 2nd boss of Parquina&amp;rsquo;s Nest where skill damage varied depending on whether or not the player is close to the center Fixed issue where Popori Brawler&amp;rsquo;s final Rhythmic Blows hit animation was awkward Fixed issue where range on Priest&amp;rsquo;s Focus Heal and Mystic&amp;rsquo;s _ was different from its respective tooltip Fixed issue where NPC Ron in charge of leading party to Treasure Box would get stuck on its path Fixed issue at 1st/2nd boss of Parquina&amp;rsquo;s Nest (hard) where skills that reset aggro did not reset aggro Fixed issue where cooldown of Ninja&amp;rsquo;s Death Blossom I was 10 seconds long Fixed issue in Parquina&amp;rsquo;s Nest where Warrior&amp;rsquo;s Combative Strike skill effect occasionally did not work Fixed issue where character event counter did not progress for defeating event monsters   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 02월 28일 업데이트 안내 (v82.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 전장  눈싸움 전장  눈싸움 전장이 오픈됩니다.  이용 시간은 하기와 같습니다. (모든 요일 동일)  운영 시간  9:00~11:00 15:00~17:00 22:00~24:00 1:00~3:00         발키온 지령서 보상  긴급지령  눈싸움 전장에서 전투를!  골드 : 100 특성 경험치 : 1215 장비 숙련도 경험치 : 1650     선택지령  눈싸움 전장에서 전투를!  골드 : 100 특성 경험치 : 1215       승패 보상  승리보상  눈싸움 전장 전리품 40개 승리의 인도자 130,000 점   패배보상  눈싸움 전장 전리품 20개 승리의 인도자43,000점      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.02.21 patch notes (v82.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Popori Brawler  Added new class [Brawler] to race Popori  Can be raced changed to Popori after March 28th   Expanded character limit from 21 slots to 22 slots  2. Dungeon  New : Parquina&amp;rsquo;s Nest (hard)  Can enter starting from ilvl 457 Teleportal is located in Essenian Crest, Essenia Can obtain Worldly Essence, Talyph XP, Supreme Metal, Weight Pendulum, Pure Essential Butterfly Gem, Pure Essential Butterfly Dust, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 02월 21일 업데이트 안내 (v82.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 포포리 권술사  포포리 종족으로 선택 가능한 직업에 [권술사]가 추가됩니다.  3/28 점검 전까지는 종족 변경권으로 변경할 수 없습니다.   캐릭터 생성 가능 개수가 21개 -&amp;gt; 22개로 확장됩니다.  2. 던전  신규: 찬란한 파르퀴나의 둥지(5인)  68레벨, 장비레벨 457달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 에세니아 가드&amp;gt;에세니아 구릉지대&amp;gt;차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 세계의 결정, 스킬 연마 경험치, 고급 금속물, 무게추, 순수한 보석 나비의 보석 샘, 순수한 보석 나비의 날개 가루, 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 오른반쪽, 투명 얼굴/등 악세서리, 유물/성물, 전설 속옷 등의 아이템을 보상으로 획득할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.02.14 patch notes (v82.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v82-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Field  Added Treasure Map content Treasure Map items can be obtained by merging two of Dr. Wilson&amp;rsquo;s Map Pieces (left, right)  조합  윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 왼반쪽 1개 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 오른반쪽 1개   결과물  윌슨 박사의 보물 지도[???] 1개   Dr. Wilson&amp;rsquo;s Map Piece (Left) can be obtained from ilvl 435-445 dungeons, while Dr. Wilson&amp;rsquo;s Map Piece (Right) can be obtained from ilvl 446-456 dungeons While Map Pieces cannot be traded, it can however be deposited into Guild Bank  Map Pieces expire in 15 days   A random Treasure Map can be obtained by using Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 02월 14일 업데이트 안내 (v82.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v82-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 필드  보물 지도 콘텐츠가 추가됩니다. 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각(왼반쪽,오른반쪽)을 조합하여 보물지도 아이템을 획득할 수 있습니다.  조합  윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 왼반쪽 1개 윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 오른반쪽 1개   결과물  윌슨 박사의 보물 지도[???] 1개   윌슨 박사의 지도 조각 왼반쪽은 장비 레벨 435 ~ 445 구간 던전에서 오른반쪽은 장비 레벨 446 ~ 456 구간 던전에서 매우 낮은 확률로 드랍 됩니다. 지도 조각은 거래가 불가능하나, 길드창고에 보관 가능합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.31 patch notes (v81.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v81-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v81-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  New : Parquina&amp;rsquo;s Nest  Level 65, ilvl 453 dungeon Teleportal is located in Essenian Crest Added Parquina&amp;rsquo;s Nest story quest (can be proceed after completing “In midst of falling and landing” story quest) Loot table includes Worldly Essence, talyph XP, Supreme Metal, Springy Draco Limb, Stormcry gear box, Veilthroch, Transcendence Mask, Transparent mask/weapon sheath, and accessories    2. Classic server open  Opened TERA classic server consisting of 2014 content such as Shandra Manaya and Kelsaik&amp;rsquo;s Nest Classic server can only be accessed through a separate client, and will be ported over to the same client as the client hosting Glory of Arun server on March 14th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 31일 업데이트 안내 (v81.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v81-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v81-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전  신규: 파르퀴나의 둥지(5인)  66레벨, 장비레벨 453달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 에세니아 가드&amp;gt;에세니아 구릉지대&amp;gt;차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. 파르퀴나 둥지 미션이 추가됩니다. (66레벨 미션 &amp;lsquo;추락과 착지 사이&amp;rsquo; 완료 후 진행할 수 있습니다) 세계의 결정, 스킬 연마 경험치, 고급 금속물, 용족의 활대, 울부짖는 분노 장비 상자, 마지막 원소, 초월의 가면, 투명 얼굴/등 악세서리 등의 아이템을 보상으로 획득할 수 있습니다.    2. 클래식 서버 오픈  샨드라마나이아, 켈사이크의 성소 등 2014년 컨텐츠를 플레이 할 수 있는 서버가 오픈됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.24 patch notes (v81.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v81-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v81-01/</guid>
      <description>New : Partner system   Added partner system  Upon reaching level 66, story quest &amp;lsquo;Thrall Egg&amp;rsquo; can be accepted from NPC Lumin in Highwatch, and receive partner [Coco Mingming] as reward   Partner structure  Rank and affinity  Rank  Rank can increased via upgrade Upon upgrading, affinity is randomly increased  Higher affinity increases effect of affinity skill         Skill  Affinity skill  Can be used every 3 minutes while partner is summoned   Ability skill  Upon register a partner, one of the following skills is randomly granted  Partner : Mari  Strengthen affinity I-III Urgent HP restorative I-III Swift XP progression I-III Crafting support I-III   Partner : Kunkun  Strengthen affinity I-III Urgent MP restorative I-III Swift talyph progression I-III Fishing support I-III   Partner : Coco Mingming  Strengthen affinity I-III Shield I-III Swift multi progression I-III Gathering support I-III   루미  교감 강화 I~III 긴급 회복 I~III 성장 가속 I~III 제작 지원 I~III   Skill : Effect  Strengthen Affinity : Increase duration of affinity skill at a low chance upon entering combat Urgent HP restorative : Restore HP per second for a limited time at a low chance upon decreasing HP Urgent MP restorative : Restore MP per second for a limited time at a low chance upon decreasing MP Shield : Absorb damage for a limited time at a low chance upon decreasing HP Swift XP progression : Increase XP gained for a limited time at a low chance upon giving a gift to your partner Swift talyph progression : Increase talyph XP gained for a limited time at a low chance upon giving a gift to your partner Swift multi progression : Increase XP and talyph XP gained for a limited time at a low chance upon giving a gift to your partner Crafting support : Increase chance of critical success for a limited at a low chance upon crafting Fishing support : Increase chance to catch BAF for a limited time at a low chance upon fishing Gathering support : Decrease gathering time for a limited time at a low chance upon gathering         Transmission  Abilities that a pet possesses can be transferred to your partner   Stamina  Partner stamina decreases by 1 per minute while summoned  Partner stamina can be restored by using gift items  Gift items can be crafted or bought from the merchant  Gift item designs can be bought from the processing materials merchant Dog statue Pig statue Popori statue          2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 24일 업데이트 안내 (v81.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v81-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v81-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 신규: 파트너 시스템  파트너 시스템이 추가됩니다.  레벨 66이되면 이르카 지역에 있는 NPC 루민을 통해 “정령의 알” 미션 퀘스트 진행이 가능하며, 보상으로 [코코밍밍] 파트너를 획득하실 수 있습니다.   파트너 구조  등급과 교감도  등급  승급을 통해 상승시킬 수 있습니다. 등급이 상승 시 교감도가 랜덤으로 상승합니다.  교감도가 높아지면 교감 스킬 성능이 향상됩니다.         스킬  교감 스킬  파트너가 소환된 상태에서 3분마다 사용할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.17 patch notes (v80.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Server merge  Servers are now merged  2. Dungeon  Level progression dungeon  Instance matching system  Changed from 5-man to 3-man instances Changed Joy of Partying effect (2-man : 200%, 3-man : 400%) Changed dungeons : Bastion of Lok, Sinistral Manor, Savarash&amp;rsquo;s Ascent, Cultists&amp;rsquo; Refuge, Necromancer&amp;rsquo;s Tomb, Golden Labyrinth, Saleron&amp;rsquo;s Sky Garden, Labyrinth of Terror, Ebon Tower   Adjust dungeon difficulty  Can now be cleared without a healer Changed Instance Matching to be able to match regardless of class Fixed for named monsters to drop health motes      3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 17일 업데이트 안내 (v80.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 서버통합  [아룬의 영광] [카이아의 가호] 서버가 통합됩니다. &amp;gt;[통합 세부 내용 확인]  2. 던전  성장구간 던전  던전 매칭 인원 변경  5 -&amp;gt; 3인으로 변경됩니다. 매칭 인원이 변경됨에 따라 성장의 즐거움 효과가 변경됩니다. (2인 200%, 3인 400%) 변경 던전: 비밀기지, 밤피르의 저택, 자바르만 소굴, 사교도의 은신처, 사령술 연구소, 황금의 미궁, 살레론의 공중 정원, 공포의 미궁, 검은 탑   던전 난이도 조정  힐러 클래스가 없이도 클리어가 가능해집니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.10 patch notes (v80.02.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Fishing   XP  Successfully catching fish now provides XP  XP gained varies at different levels XP gained varies by different grades of fish     Item  Changed to obtain Talyph XP scroll I~II by chance upon successful catch   Delivery  Fish delivery  Changed Association Fishmonger to Association Fishmonger Increased delivery limit to 30 times Can obtain gold by delivering grade 0-10 fish and BAF   Fish crate delivery  Changed Association Resource Manager to Association Fish Crate Manager Changed to deliver up to 3 times Can obtain gold by delivering Fish Crate I-V  Fish Crate designs can be exchanged with Angler Tokens through Angler Token Vendor     VIP users can deliver fish up to 50 times, deliver fish crates up to 5 times Fishing Supplies merchant  Added Recipe: Apple-Pumpkin Smoothie  Can be crafted 50 Apples, 50 Moongourd Pulp and 100 Fresh Milk (2x for crit)  Provides &amp;lsquo;20% XP boost&amp;rsquo; effect          2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 10일 업데이트 안내 (v80.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 낚시  경험치  낚시 성공 시 레벨 경험치를 획득합니다.  캐릭터 레벨에 따라 획득하는 경험치가 다릅니다. 낚은 물고기의 등급에 따라 획득하는 경험치가 다릅니다.     아이템  낚시 성공 시 일정 확률로 스킬 연마 경험치 서적I~ II을 획득할 수 있게 됩니다.   낚시 납품 상점  물고기 납품점  낚시 납품점이 물고기 납품점으로 변경되었습니다. 납품 횟수가 30회로 증가합니다. 0등급~10등급 물고기와 대물을 납품하여 골드를 획득하실 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.01.03 patch notes (v80.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v80-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Quest  Added story quest-specific 1-man level progression dungeons  Bastion of Lok (1-man)  Can enter via appropriate story quest   Sinistral Manor (1-man)  Can enter via appropriate story quest   Cultists&amp;rsquo; Refuge (1-man)  Can enter via appropriate story quest     Removed Kumas Royale story quest  Quest already received and not completed will automatically be completed upon update   Fixed to display escort quest NPCs on minimap via an orange dot marking  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 01월 03일 업데이트 안내 (v80.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v80-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 퀘스트  미션 퀘스트 진행을 위한 퀘스트 전용 성장구간(1인) 던전이 추가됩니다.  비밀기지(1인)  미션 퀘스트 “비밀기지를 토벌하라” 를 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다.   밤피르의 저택(1인)  미션 퀘스트 “밤피르 저택 토벌”을 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다.   사교도의 은신처(1인)  미션 퀘스트 “로크 교도 괴멸”을 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다.     LV20 쿠마스의 놀이터 미션퀘스트가 삭제 됩니다.  미션 퀘스트 쿠마스의 놀이터를 수주 받고 진행하지 않은 경우, 업데이트 후 완료된 퀘스트로 자동 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>