<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v81 on tera-mysterium</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v81/</link><description>Recent content in v81 on tera-mysterium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v81/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2019.01.31 patch notes (v81.02) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v81-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v81-02/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon New : Gossamer Vault Level 65, ilvl 453 dungeon Teleportal is located in Essenian Crest Added Gossamer Vault story quest (can be proceed after completing “In midst of falling and landing” story quest) Drop table includes Legacy Essence, Skill Advancement XP, Supreme Metal, Springy Draco Limb, Stormcry gear box, Veilthroch, Transcendent Mask, Transparent mask/weapon sheath, and accessories 2. Classic server open Opened TERA classic server consisting of 2014 content such as Shandra Manaya and Kelsaik&amp;rsquo;s Nest Classic server can only be accessed through a separate client, and will be ported over to the same client as the client hosting 아룬의 영광 server on March 14th.</description></item><item><title>2019.01.24 patch notes (v81.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v81-01/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v81-01/</guid><description>Update 1. New : Companion system Added Companion system Upon reaching level 66, story quest &amp;lsquo;Thrall Egg&amp;rsquo; can be accepted from NPC Lumin in Highwatch, and receive partner [Cocomin] as reward Companion structure Grade and Fellowship Grade Grade can increased via Promote Upon upgrading, Fellowship is randomly increased Higher Fellowship increases effect of Bond Skill Skill Bond Skill Can be used every 3 minutes while partner is summoned Gifted Skill Upon register a Partner, one of the following skills is randomly granted 파트너 별로 획득할 수 있는 스킬은 다음과 같습니다.</description></item></channel></rss>