<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v51 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v51/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v51 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v51/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.10.13 patch notes (v51.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Festival  Started Halloween Festival  할로윈 축제는 10월 13일부터 11월 10일까지 시행됩니다. 축제 기간 동안 각 마을 및 대도시에 [마녀의 성 지상 1층]으로 순간이동 시켜주는 &amp;lsquo;꼬마 마녀&#39;들이 등장합니다. 마녀의 성 지상 1층에서 &amp;lsquo;마녀탐정 티티아나&amp;rsquo; NPC와 대화하여 할로윈 퀘스트를 받을 수 있습니다.     마녀의 성 연회장  할로윈 호박 대포에 탑승하여 몰려오는 몬스터를 처치하는 디펜스 형태의 던전입니다. 마녀의 성 연회장에서 &amp;lsquo;하르니아&amp;rsquo; NPC와 대화하여 게임을 시작할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016.09.29 patch notes (v51.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2016/v51-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Added new dungeon [Broken Prison] Broken Prison is a 5man party dungeon  Can be entered through teleportal in Arcadia &amp;gt; Oblivion Woods &amp;gt; Deva Silva, and requires iLvl 417 to enter via IMS Rewards are Tier 2 Demense earring/ring, Imperator Belt, Cleansing Brooch, Goldfinger Token, Eau d&amp;rsquo;Fascination, Lachelith&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Box, Imperator designs, Ambush designs, Rare innerwear, Dyad Niveot Structure, and etc Added [Broken Prison] to guild quest   Harrowhold  Adjusted balance per phase  Phase 1  Decreased Agalith damage by 15% Decreased Agalith HP by 10%   Phase 2  Increased Balista skill damage by 20%   Phase 3  Decreased Vergoth defense by 5%   Phase 4  Increased attack speed of aerial breathe by 10% Increased attack speed of stoning attack due to close-range explosion by 15%     Decreased gold drop per phase  Gold Hunter Boost/Internet Cafe/Elite related bonus gold will no longer apply Increased the upper limit of gold given, and decreased lower limit Decreased the number of gold item dropped   Exchanged the loot table between Phase 1 and Phase 2  Clearing Phase 2 gives Phase 1 loot, and clearing Phase 1 gives Phase 2 loot   Changed loot table and loot probability of Vergoth&amp;rsquo;s Bronze/Silver/Gold Treasure Box  Removed Diamond Added Goddess&amp;rsquo;s Tear and Superior Etching Box   각 페이즈의 기본보상인 베르고스의 전투 주머니에 강화석이 추가로 구성됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>