<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018 on mysterium</title>
    <link>/mysterium/tags/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/mysterium/tags/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.27 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-27/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Achievement - Added first level 70 achievement for each class ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue where XP gained from goblin thieves was higher than intended - Fixed issue where XP bar UI did not display up to two decimal places - K TERA exclusive - K TERA exclusive  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 12월 27일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-27/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 업적 - 각 클래스 별로 최초 70레벨 달성 업적이 추가됩니다. ### [버그 수정] - 고블린 도적 떼 처치 경험치가 기획수치와 다르게 적용되었던 문제 - 경험치 바 수치가 소수점 둘째 자리까지 노출되지 않던 문제 - 월간 패스 일일 T-cat 주머니 쿨타임이 게임 미접속 시 적용되지 않는 문제 - (*월간 패스 T-cat 주머니 쿨타임 오류 보상은 확정 시 안내드릴 예정입니다.)  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.22 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-22/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Balance - Adjusted to increase XP on ilvl 412-456 dungeon bosses - Changed XP ranges differently per dungeon - Decreased XP required to level up between level 66-70 Developer comment - First off we increased XP earned through dungeons by 3 times through this maintenance. The XP gain has been adjusted using difficulty and clear time as basis, and therefore each each dungeon provides a different amount of XP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 12월 22일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-22/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 밸런스 - 412~456 레벨 던전 네임드 경험치가 상향 조정됩니다. - 던전 별로 경험치 변경 수준은 상이합니다. - 66레벨 ~ 70레벨 구간 레벨 달성 경험치 요구량이 하향되었습니다. [개발자코멘트] - 우선 금일 점검을 통해 던전에서 얻을 수 있는 경험치를 기존대비 3배 정도로 상향하였습니다. - 난이도와 클리어 타임 기준으로 획득 경험치량을 조절하였기에 던전별 획득 경험치가 상이할 수 있습니다. - 추후 보다 다양한 경로로 경험치를 획득하실 수 있도록 적용해 나가겠습니다. ### [버그 수정] - 칠흑의 테네브리스 성채(7인), 공허한 안타로스의 심연(7인), 왜곡된 리안의 지하 전당(7인) 던전에 파티의 즐거움 버프가 적용되지 않는 문제 - 미션 퀘스트 [장비 지급] 바라카들의 호의 퀘스트 보상인 스킬 교본: 갈색 비행 군마 소환 아이템이 파괴 불가 속성인 문제 - 공격대로 필드 보스 몬스터 처치 시 간헐적으로 보상 상자가 드랍되지 않는 문제 - PC방 대여 아이템이 파괴불가, 창고 보관 불가 속성인 문제 - 오칸의 잡동사니 상자에서 경험치를 대량 획득할 수 있는 문제 - 부활의 나무 중형 몬스터 처치 시 네임드 처치 업적이 달성되는 문제 - 인술사, 마법사 캐릭터에게 VIP 만능 전투 비약의 치명타 위력 증가가 적용되지 않는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.20 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-20/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Level cap expansion - Increased level cap to level 70 - Added new story quest `Break of Nightmare` - Can progress post-awakening - Adjusted required XP for levels 58 to 65 - Adjusted XP rewarded from monsters level 58 and above, quest, and Vanguard Request - New : Talyph System - Players can now use Talyph and Option Unlock - Talyph - Players can use Talyph upon reaching levels 66, 68, 70 - Talyph requires Talyph Scroll I, II, III and gold to improve skills - Option Unlock - Players can unlock options upon reaching levels 67, 69 - Each (unlockable) skill has 3 options, and requires Option Unlock Scroll I, II and gold to unlock - Options can be selected/changed out of combat - Talyph Scroll, Option Unlock Scrolls can be exchanged - 7 Talyph Scroll I : 1 Talyph Scroll III - 3 Option Unlock Scroll I : 1 Talyph Scroll III - 7 Talyph II : 1 Talyph Scroll III - 3 Option Unlock Scroll II : 1 Talyph Scroll III !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 12월 20일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-20/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 최대 레벨 확장 - 캐릭터 최대 레벨이 LV70까지 확장됩니다. - 신규 미션 퀘스트 “악몽의 시작”이 추가됩니다. - 각성을 완료해야 진행이 가능합니다. - 58~65레벨의 필요 경험치가 조정됩니다. - 58레벨 이상 몬스터, 퀘스트, 발키온 지령서 경험치 지급이 조정되었습니다. - 신규: 스킬 연마 시스템 - 스킬 연마와 옵션 개방을 할 수 있게 됩니다. - 스킬 연마 - 66/68/70레벨 도달 시 스킬 연마 할 수 있습니다. . - 스킬 연마 단계를 승급시키기 위해서는 스킬 연마 스크롤 I,II,III과 골드가 필요합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.13 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-13/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Balance - Slayer - Changed to reset cooldown of Overhand Strike to 0 upon using In Cold Blood ### 2. Wintera Snowfield - Applies equalized gear in this battleground - Changed round specific system message ### 3. Miscellaneous - Changed Travel Journal limit to 10 locations ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue where deactivating Noctenium Infusion in dungeons did not work properly - Fixed issue where Valkyrie&#39;s Godsfall skill did not receive chain effect from Gungnir&#39;s Bite - Fixed issue where during Reaper&#39;s Shadow Reaping, Grim Strike&#39;s Glyph of Persistence&#39;s system message did not display the skill&#39;s name in its message - Fixed issue where Wintera Snowfield description did not include win condition upon timeout to be dependent on number of team players remaining - Fixed issue where Slayer&#39;s `Startling Kick - Empowered Speed` talent did not display its activation requirement properly - Fixed issue where Reaper&#39;s `Death Spiral - Empowered Speed` talent did not display its activation requirement properly  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 12월 13일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-13/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 밸런스 (추가) - 무사 - 파괴의 기백 사용 시, 일도양단의 재사용 대기시간이 0으로 변경됩니다. ### 2. 눈싸움 전장 - 해당 전장 이용 시 노병 크로아스 통일 장비가 적용됩니다. - 라운드 시스템 메시지가 변경됩니다. ### 3. 기타 - 여행자의 책 장소저장 개수가 10개로 변경되었습니다. ### [버그 수정] - 인던 퇴장 후 녹테늄 강화탄 비활성화가 원활하지 못한 문제 - 월광무사 개전 스킬에 반월참 연계효과가 적용되지 않는 문제 - 비검사 어둠 강림 사용 중 비검 내려치기 기회의 문장 효과 적용 시 시스템 메시지에 스킬 이름이 출력되지 않는 문제 - 눈싸움 전장 승리 조건에 제한 시간 초과 시 남은 인원 수에 따른 승리 문구가 추가되지 않은 문제 - 무사 &#39;후퇴 차기 – 전투 가속&#39; 특성 툴팁에 발동 조건이 잘못 표기된 문제 - 비검사 &#39;비검 휘두르기 – 전투 가속&#39; 특성 툴팁에 발동 조건이 잘못 표기된 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.06 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-12-06/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Wintera Snowfield - Added a shrinking snowstorm area - Snowstorm area induces 5,000 damage per second - Changed to single round instance - Winning condition is to defeat all enemy players - Added relevant Vanguard Request - Vanguard Request - 눈싸움 전장에서 전투를! - Gold: 100 - talentXP: 1215 - itemXP: 1650 - Optional - 눈싸움 전장에서 전투를! - Gold: 100 - talentXP: 1215 - The following denotes win and loss rewards : - Win reward - 40 Wintera Token - 216,000 BC - Loss reward - 20 Wintera Token - 72,000 BC - Wintera Token Shop - Archdevan Surfactant : 400 - Elemental Essence : 1,650 - Veilthroch : 3,600 - Devil&#39;s Claws : 1,100 - Dragon Skull : 360 - Fireworks set : 20 - Dragon firework : 40 - Green Wintera Scarf : 100 - Green Wintera Scarf : 100 - Green Wintera Scarf : 100 - Green Wintera Scarf : 100 - Bravery Potion II : 100 - Lamb Bulgogi : 100 - Rejuvenation Elixir : 300 - EP Reset Potion : 1,000 - Frost Mantle of Indifference : 2,000 - Wintersilk Dress Box (14 days) : 3,000 - Snowflake firework (30 days) : 3,000 !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 12월 06일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-12-06/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 눈싸움 전장 - 중앙으로 점차 좁혀지는 눈보라 지역이 추가됩니다. - 눈보라 지역에 있으면 초당 5,000의 데미지를 입습니다. - 단판제로 변경 됩니다. - 승리 조건 : 모든 적을 처치 시 - 발키온 지령서 보상이 추가됩니다. - 긴급지령 - 눈싸움 전장에서 전투를! - 골드 : 100 - 특성 경험치 : 1215 - 장비 숙련도 경험치 : 1650 - 선택지령 - 눈싸움 전장에서 전투를! - 골드 : 100 - 특성 경험치 : 1215 - 승패 보상은 하기와 같습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.29 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-29/</guid>
      <description>### 1. UI - Revised boss gage info enrage information - Revised to display the amount of enrage time remaining ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue where cancelling Slayer&#39;s Whirlwind with Overhand Strike had discrepancies in cancelling time due at different skill levels - Fixed issue where Valkyries could not iframe debuff-type skills - Fixed issue where Reaper&#39;s Retribution tooltip was insufficient to explain &#39;cannot use Retribution against projectiles in PvP&#39;  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 11월 29일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-29/</guid>
      <description>1. UI - 몬스터 체력바 분노 표시 개선 - 분노 시작 이후 남은 분노시간이 표시되도록 개선됩니다. ### [버그 수정] - 무사클래스 회전 베기를 일도양단으로 캔슬 시 스킬 레벨에 따라 캔슬 타이밍이 상이한 문제 - 월광무사 클래스의 회피 스킬로 축복 류 스킬을 피할 수 없는 문제 - 비검사 &#39;반격&#39;스킬 툴팁에 &#39;PVP에서 투사체 공격에 반격 불가&#39;에 대한 설명이 부족한 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.22 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-22/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Balance - Mystic - Thrall of Life - Revised to increase speed of summoner recognition - Changed to use area of effect cleanse and healing skill immediately after summoning regardless of the distance between thrall and summoner - Slightly increased casting speed of area of effect cleanse and area of effect heal used after being summoned - Changed the maximum distance from summoner before attempting to move towards the summoner from 5m to 20m Developer comment - Slayer - In Cold Blood - Removed [Ultimate Overhand Strike], and changed effect to increase skill damage of Overhand Strike by 30% - Decrease cooldown of Overhand Strike upon casting - Overhand Strike - Changed to display [Ultimate Overhand Strike]&#39;s skill effect - 괴력 talent - Changed condition from during In Cold Blood to upon successful hit with Overhand Strike - Evasive Roll - Changed MP cost from 75 to 100 Developer comment - Reaper - Assassination - Added hit from behind effect to monsters during its effect - Shadow Step - Changed MP cost from 0 to 100 - Displays cooldown information after 1 time use - Grim Strike - Displays cooldown information after 1 time use Developer comment - Gunner - Bombardment - Decreased total skill damage of all 11 hit of missiles - Increased area of damage of each missile by 10% - Rolling Reload - Increased MP cost from 0 to 100 - There is no additional MP cost to use Dashing Reload Developer comment - Valkyrie - Evasion - Changed MP cost from 0 to 100 - Brawler - Never Retreat (passive) - Increased frontal damage from 7% to 10% - Quick Dash - Changed MP cost from 0 to 100 - Displays cooldown information after 1 time use - Growing Fury - Resets cooldown of [Provoke] if Growing Fury ends upon lack of Rage or player death Developer comment - Sorcerer - Backstep - Changed MP cost from 85 to 100 - Berserker - Evasive Roll - Changed MP cost from 0 to 100 Developer comment ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 11월 22일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-22/</guid>
      <description>1. 밸런스 - 정령사 - 생명의 정령 - 시전자를 인지하는 속도 향상 개선 - 소환 직후, 시전자와 거리에 상관 없이 광역 정화와 회복 스킬을 사용하도록 변경됩니다. - 소환 후 확정으로 광역 도트 힐/광역 정화 사용 시전 속도가 소폭 상향됩니다. - 시전자와 멀어지면 다가가는 거리가 5 → 20M로 변경됩니다. [개발자 코멘트] - 소환 직후 시전자와 생명의 정령의 거리가 멀어질 경우, 스킬을 사용하지 않고 시전자만 따라다니던 문제를 수정하여 스킬의 활용성을 개선하였습니다. - 무사 - 파괴의 기백 - [진 일도양단] 스킬이 제거되며, 시전 시 일도양단의 공격력이 30% 증가합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.15 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-15/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Shadow Sanguinary (hard) - Gear requirement : ilvl 446 - Teleportal location : Highwatch Outskirts - Potential reward : Onset Mask, top-tier enchanting material, transparent accessories (mask, back), etc. - Added appropriate guild quest - Shadow Sanguinary - Gear requirement : ilvl 439 - Teleportal location : Highwatch Outskirts - Potential reward, high-tier enchanting material, transparent accessories, etc. - Added appropriate guild quest - Velik&#39;s Sanctuary (hard) - Gear requirement : ilvl 453 - Teleportal location : Velika - Potential require : Infinity Mask, top-tier enchanting material, crafting additive I, transparent accessories, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 11월 15일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-15/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 폭군 듀리온의 안식처 - 장비 레벨 446 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 바라카니아 가드&amp;gt; 이르카 근교&amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장하실 수 있습니다. - 시작의 가면, 최상위 장비 강화 재료, 투명 액세서리 등을 획득하실 수 있습니다. - 해당 던전 길드 임무가 추가됩니다. - 듀리온의 안식처 - 장비 레벨 439 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 바라카니아 가드&amp;gt; 이르카 근교&amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장하실 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.08 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-08/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Reward - Added rewards to Antaroth&#39;s Abyss (hard) - Slightly increased the drop amount of Old Supply Crate upon defeating Nightmare Antaroth - Added Dragon&#39;s Skull to loot table Developer comment - Added new “Bahaar&#39;s Mask” to replace “Transcendence Mask” in Bahaar&#39;s Temple - Bahaar&#39;s Mask - Upper tier item that has one static line and 3 random static lines (can have the same stat) - Fixed field/dungeon item drop during level progression - Decreased gold rate rate while increasing drop amount - Removed gold drop from dungeons - Decreased crystal drop rate in field/dungeon ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 11월 08일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-08/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 보상 - 공허한 안타로스의 심연 던전의 보상이 추가됩니다. - 공허한 안타로스 처치 시 드랍되는 낡은 보급품 아이템 지급 개수가 소폭 증가합니다. - 공허한 안타로스 드랍 보상에 용의 두개골 아이템이 추가됩니다. [개발자 코멘트] - 공허한 안타로스의 심연 보상효율이 다른 453던전에 비해 부족한 것으로 판단되어 보상을 추가하였습니다. - 바하르의 신전 보상에 &#39;초월의 가면&#39;이 제외되고, 신규 &#39;바하르의 가면&#39; 이 추가됩니다. - 바하르의 가면 - 고정 옵션 1개와 랜덤 옵션 3개(동일 옵션 중복 가능)를 가지는 가면으로 초월의 가면보다 상위 아이템 입니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.01 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-11-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Balance - Changed all class&#39; base Endurance to 80, class-specific stats, and defense stats on gear - Berserker - Lethal Strike - Increased skill damage by 15% - Decreased PvP skill damage by 30% - Decreased the additional damage received as player&#39;s HP decreases - Increased MP cost from 0 to 300 - Thunder Strike - Adjusted Popori&#39;s hit point relative to the hit point of other race - Combo Attack - Adjusted all race&#39;s hit point relative to race Elin&#39;s hit point - Leaping Strike - Fixed issue where Leaping Strike could cancel Cyclone - Cyclone - Adjusted to apply stagger to other players without pulling them in if overcharged - Triumphant Shout - Changed immunity effect duration from 6 seconds to 5 seconds - Fearsome Shout - Changed to be cleansable - Unleash - Changed to be able to cancel with Regression/Plague of Exhaustion Developer comment - Valkyrie - Gungnir&#39;s Bite - Increased chain duration from 3 seconds to 4 seconds - Increased duration to use 2nd hit from 6 seconds to 7 seconds - Dreamblaze - Increased chain duration from 5 seconds to 7 seconds - Dark Herald - Changed hit radius from 12m to 8m - Charge - Changed dash speed relative to other classes - Bloodflower - Changed to remove stun effect to knocked down targets - Leaping Slash - Removed knockdown effect upon successful hit to other players - Ground Bash - Added knockdown effect upon successful hit to other players - Ragnarok &amp;amp; Godsfall - [Bloodflower] and [Overhead Slash] no longer receive cooldown reset or cooldown decrease effect - Twilight Waltz - Decreased PvP skill damage by 20% - this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 11월 01일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-11-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 밸런스 - 클래스 별 기본 맷집이 80으로 변경되며, 방어구의 방어 성능과 클래스별 보정치가 변경됩니다. - 광전사 - 혼신의 일격 - 스킬 위력이 15% 증가합니다. - PVP 스킬 위력이 30% 감소합니다. - 자신의 체력이 낮을수록 증가하는 데미지 상승률이 감소합니다. - Mp소모량이 0 -&amp;gt; 300으로 증가합니다. - 모아 치기 - 포포리 종족의 타격 시점이 다른 종족과 유사한 수준으로 조정됩니다. - 연속 공격 - 각 종족의 첫 타격 시점이 엘린 종족과 유사한 수준으로 조정됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.25 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-25/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - New : Guardian Training Room - Can be accessed in Highwatch - Can fight against a specified BAM to measure DPS and freely practice without entry limit ### 2. Security update - Updated security program ### 3. Elin Gunner/Brawler - Can now use Race Change Voucher to race Elin ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue where Reverse Scythe Retrieval allowed Reapers to clip through walls - Fixed issue where using Heart Thrust did not display skill name in system message - Fixed issue where Cultist&#39;s Weapon Chest was rendered as weed in Cultist&#39;s Refuge  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 10월 25일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-25/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 신규: 수호자 훈련소 - 바라카니아 가드&amp;gt;이르카 근교&amp;gt;이르카 지역에 있는 “어두운하늘 휘락” 훈련소 교관을 통해서 입장이 가능합니다. - 해당 던전은 입장횟수 제한이 없으며, 특정 몬스터와의 전투를 통해 자유롭게 DPS를 측정하거나, 플레잉 연습을 할 수 있습니다. ### 2. 보안 업데이트 - 보안 프로그램이 업데이트 됩니다. ### 3. 엘린 마공사/권술사 - 엘린 마공사/권술사로 종족 변경이 가능해집니다. ### [버그 수정] - 포화의 전장 대기 중에 비검사 역포획으로 문을 통과 할 수 있는 문제 - 무사 급소 치기 기회의 문장 효과 발동 시 시스템 메세지에 스킬명이 출력되지 않는 문제 - 사교도의 은신처 던전에 &#39;사교도 무기상자&#39; 오브젝트가 잡초로 보이는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.18 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-18/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Adjusted balance of Bahaar&#39;s Temple - Decreased daamge of 2nd phase Bahaar&#39;s Fury Swipes during enrage - Added Bahaar&#39;s Treasure Chest as reward - Spawns at 2nd phase area after completing 1st phase - Bahaar&#39;s Amplifier Token can be exchanged for Bahaar&#39;s Glove Amplifier or Bahaar&#39;s Boot Amplifier - Treasure Chest contains the following : - Rare Metal - Dragon&#39;s Bow - Balance Weights - Bahaar&#39;s Amplifier Token - Bahaar&#39;s Glove Amplifier - Bahaar&#39;s Boot Amplifier - 성장 구간 던전에서 클래스 상관 없이 매칭 수락 팝업창이 매칭 30초뒤 팝업되도록 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 10월 18일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-18/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 바하르의 신전 밸런스 조정 - 2페이즈 바하르의 분노 상태에서 사용하는 분노의 난타 피해량이 감소합니다. - 보상으로 바하르의 보물상자가 추가됩니다. - 보물 상자는 1페이즈 클리어 시 2페이즈 지역에서 스폰 됩니다. - 바하르의 보물 상자로 획득할 수 있는 아이템은 하기와 같습니다. - 바하르의 증폭제 코인은 바하르의 장갑 증폭제 또는 바하르의 신발 증폭제로 교환할 수 있습니다. - 획득 아이템 (확률드랍) - 고급 금속물 - 용족의 활대 - 무게추 - 바하르의 증폭제 코인 - 바하르의 장갑 증폭제 - 바하르의 신발 증폭제 - 성장 구간 던전에서 클래스 상관 없이 매칭 수락 팝업창이 매칭 30초뒤 팝업되도록 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.11 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-11/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Temporarily closed Dreadspire, Harrowhold - Removed Dreadspire from Leaderboard ### 2. Item - Brooch promotion - Marrow Brooch can now be promoted to Oblit Brooch - Quatrefoil Brooch can now be promoted to Brilliant Quatrefoil Brooch - Cost for promotion [for both brooch] is the following : - 158,994 item XP - 85 Silver Plate - 39 Old Supply Crate - 8 Devil&#39;s Toenail - 8 Dragon&#39;s Skull - 3 Diamond - 9,114 Gold !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 10월 11일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-11/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 환영의 탑, 파계된 신계의 관문 이용이 임시 종료됩니다. - 환영의 탑은 리더보드에서 시즌 오프됩니다. ### 2. 아이템 - 브로치 승급 - 고룡의 브로치 승급 시 악룡의 브로치를 획득 할 수 있습니다. - 빛나는 여신의 브로치를 승급 하여 신규 브로치 찬란한 여신의 브로치를 획득 할 수 있습니다. - 승급 비용은 하기와 같습니다. ![](https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/images/2018-10-11-1.png) ### 3. 스타일샵 - 발키온 정찰대 포인트로 구매 가능한 외형 아이템이 추가되었습니다. - 새로운 외형으로 &#39;무흐락 블랙라벨&#39; 시리즈를 판매합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.04 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-10-04/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Quest - Added new quest at Highwatch to be received from Strong wind Moont - Can receive at ilvl 439, and can complete once per day per character - Reward : - 6 Liquid Metal - 4 Hypnotic Device - 3 Artisan&#39;s Tools - 2 Copper Clasp - 1 Pansophic Ash - 4 Archdevan Formula - 2 Carved Ornament - 1 Old Supply Crate ### 2. Dungeon - Shattered Fleet is closed - Adjusted balance for Celestial Arena - Increased HP of monters by 5 times per stage, decreased movement speed by 80% - Added reward by ranking (rank 1-3) : - Rank 1 : - Archdevan Oil - Refined Archdevan Metal (new item) - Celestial Arena Box - Rank 2-3 : - Archdevan Oil - Refined Archdevan Metal (new item) - Celestial Arena Box (1 of) : - Metamorphic Emblem - Otherworldly Shard - Devil&#39;s Toenail - Dragon&#39;s Skull - Elemental Essence - Veiltroch ### 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 10월 04일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-10-04/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 퀘스트 - “중앙 경비대의 방식” 퀘스트가 추가되며 이르카에 있는 강철바람 문트 NPC에게 수주할 수 있습니다. - 439 아이템 장비 레벨이 되어야 수주가 가능하며, 한 캐릭터 당 1일 1회 참여할 수 있습니다. - 보상 - 이름 | 개수 - 미지의 액체 금속 | 6 - 어둠이 깃든 정신 지배 장치 | 4 - 아크데바 장인의 강화 도구 | 3 - 피로 물든 금속 구조물 | 2 - 무언의 가루 | 1 - 불길한 마법 스크롤 | 4 - 정밀하게 세공된 장식 조각 | 2 - 낡은 보급품 | 1 ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.09.20 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-09-20/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Balance - Slayer - Added chains to use [Whirlwind], [Heart Thrust], and [Knockdown Strike] after Savage Strike - Changed chance to proc Aggression talent level 1 to level 20 from [22-34%] to [22-60%] Developer comment - Archer - Find Weakness lv 3 - Decreased attack damage increase of [Thunderbolt, Radiant Arrow, Penetrating Arrow] from 20% increase to 15% increase - Crackshot lv 2, 3 - Decreased additional damage to monsters from 7% to 6% - Ninja - Boomerang Shuriken - Decreased skill damage by 15% - Changed power buff from Aggression talent level 1 to level 20 from [5-24] to [8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 09월 20일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-09-20/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 밸런스 (개발자 코멘트 추가) - 무사 - 섬단 스킬 후에 [회전 베기], [급소 치기], [후려 치기]가 연계되도록 추가됩니다. - 괴력 특성 1레벨부터 20레벨까지의 발동 확률이 [22~34%] 에서 [22~60%]로 변경됩니다. [개발자 코멘트] - 무사의 경우 괴력 특성의 발동 확률이 낮아 관련 특성을 최대 단계로 올려도 효과를 제대로 받기 어려운 문제가 있었습니다. 따라서, 괴력 발동 확률을 상향 조정하여 특성 효과를 보다 잘 활용할 수 있도록 하였습니다. 또한, 섬단 스킬에 주요 시작스킬을 연계할 수 있도록 하여 상황에 맞춰 자유롭게 딜사이클을 운용할 수 있도록 개선하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.09.13 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-09-13/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Fishing - Fishing can be learned through quest - Quest can be found in Highwatch via NPC Jeremy Wayng - Added Vanguard Request “Fshing is fun!” and the following is rewarded : - 500 gold - 50 Vanguard Initiative credit - 500 Item XP - 20 Fisherman&#39;s Token - 5 low-tier worm - 1 Gathering supply box - The following can be given from the Gather supply box : - Produce - Corn - Carrot - Orange Mushroom - Old Pumpkin - Apple - Gem - Uncut Cobala Gem - Uncut Shadmetal Gem - Uncut Xermetal Gem - Uncut Normetal Gem - Uncut &#39;Galvorn&#39; Gem - Crystal - Red Essential Energy - Green Essential Energy - Blue Essential Energy - White Essential Energy - Black Essential Energy !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 09월 13일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-09-13/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 낚시 - 낚시 가이드 퀘스트 &#39;낚시! 좋아하세요?&#39; 가 추가됩니다. - 65레벨 달성 후 이르카의 제레미 웨잉 NPC를 통해 퀘스트를 진행할 수 있습니다. - 발키온 지령서 “낚시는 즐거워!” 가 추가되며, 지령서 완료 보상은 아래와 같습니다. - 500골드 - 발키온 평판 포인트 50 - 특성 경험치 500 - 낚시꾼의 증표 20개 - 최하급 지렁이 5개 - 채집 재료 상자 1개 ![](https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/images/2018-09-13-1.png) - 낚시터 물가에서 낚싯대와 미끼를 이용하여 낚시를 진행할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.09.06 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-09-06/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Server stabilization ### 2. DB gear exchange Developer comment  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 09월 06일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-09-06/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 서버 안정화 - 서버 안정화 작업이 진행되었습니다. ### 2. DB 장비 교체 - DB 장비교체로 점검 시간이 다소 길어진 점 양해 부탁드립니다. [개발자코멘트] - 리리 제멋대로의 선물 오류 원인 파악이 완료되어 차주 정기점검 시 수정될 예정입니다. 불편을 끼쳐 드려 죄송합니다.  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.30 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-30/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Server stabilization ### Bug fixes - Fixed issue where character boss event quest item was not usable - Fixed issue where option to see monters on radar UI would automatically uncheck - Fixed issue where certain new/returning player event items would have different item type than described  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 08-30월 일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-30/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 서버 안정화 - 서버 렉 현상 완화를 위한 안정화 작업이 진행되었습니다. ### [버그수정] - 성장지원 이벤트 퀘스트 의뢰서 사용이 불가능한 문제 - 레이더 옵션에서 몬스터 마커 표시 체크가 자동으로 해제되는 문제 - 신규 복귀 이벤트의 일부 아이템 속성이 사양과 상이한 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.23 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-23/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Bamarama - Changed round times - Changed time per round to 180 seconds - Changed Gold Ticket round from once every 10 minutes to once every 5 minutes - Changed Diamond Ticket round from every 50 minute of the hour to every 25 and 55 minute of the hour - Changed Gold Ticket and Diamond Ticket to `cannot trade` status, and changed sale price - Golden Ticket : 90 silver to 1 gold, Diamond Ticket : 9 gold to 10 gold - Changed betting time and betting limit - Time - Changed betting time to 90 seconds - Golden Ticket - Changed round frequency from 10 minutes to 5 minutes, and changed maximum betting limit from 30k tickets to 100k tickets - Diamond Ticket - Changed round frequency from 60 minutes to 30 minutes, and changed maximum betting limit from 10k tickets to 30k tickets - Applied tariff upon winning - From 0% to 10% - Place a Trade Broker (beside banker) - Changed Bamarama BAM HP and enrage duration by half, and changed minimum HP required to use ultimate [from below 30%] to below 40% ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 08월 23일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-23/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 투기장 - 경기 시간이 변경됩니다. - 몬스터들의 경기 시간이 180초로 변경됩니다. - 황금 티켓 경기 10분 1회 -&amp;gt; 5분 1회 - 다이아 티켓 경기 매 시 50분(1회) -&amp;gt; 매 시 25분, 55분(2회) - 황금 티켓과 다이아 티켓의 속성이 거래 불가로 변경되며, 상점 판매 가격이 변동됩니다. - 황금 티켓(90은 -&amp;gt; 1금), 다이아 티켓(9금 -&amp;gt; 10금) - 베팅 시간 및 베팅 제한이 변경됩니다. - 베팅 시간 - 베팅 시간이 90초로 변경 됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.16 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-16/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Skill / balance - Brawler - Blitzkrieg [Placeholder] (new passive) - Acquired at level 65 - Increase frontal skill damage by 7% and aggro by 15% - Jackhammer - Changed max endurance debuff stack from 8 to 3 - Changed endurance debuff effect from 1.5% to 4.0% - Berserker - Unleashed: Beast Fury - Decrease damage received by 50% while casting - Valkyrie - Leaping Slash - Recover 10 Ragnarok Point upon successful 2nd hit - Half-moon Slice - Decreased Ragnarok Point recovered from 16 to 15 upon successful hit - Leaping Slash, Shining Crescent, Half-moon Slice - Now displays Ragnarok Point recovered in tooltip - Warrior - Enhanced Defensive Stance (new passive) - Acquired at level 65 - Increase frontal skill damage by 8% while in Defensive Stance - Sorcerer - Elemental Cores - Increase skill damage by 4% upon obtaining a core - Archer - Tempest Arrow - Slightly increased total skill damage - Slightly increased casting speed - Find Weakness - Added an effect to the skill Developer comment - Ninja - Enlightenment - Decreased cooldown by 40% - Decreased [Enhanced Boomerang Shuriken] damage by 33% - Decreased [Enhanced Leaves of the Wind] damage by 40% - Reaper - Restraining Chains - Added immunity while casting upon the end of animation - Slayer - Measured Slice - Changed to be chain-able after [Punishing Blow] ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 08월 16일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-16/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 스킬 밸런스 - 권술사 - 임전무퇴(신규 Passive) - 65레벨에 습득이 가능합니다. - 몬스터 전방 타격 시 스킬 위력이 7%, 적대치가 15% 상승합니다. - 폭연타 - 점혈 최대 중첩수가 8 -&amp;gt; 3으로 변경됩니다. - 점혈 1중첩 당 맷집 감소율이 1.5% -&amp;gt; 4%로 변경됩니다. - 광전사 - 야수의 돌진 - 스킬을 시전하는 동안 받는 피해가 50% 감소합니다. - 월광무사 - 승격참 - 2타 타격 시, 월광력이 10만큼 추가로 회복됩니다. - 반월참 - 타격 시, 월광력 추가 회복량이 16 -&amp;gt; 15로 감소합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-08-09 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-09/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Bahaar&#39;s Temple - Removed ilvl access restriction - Adjusted Vanguard Request ilvl requirement from 457 to 456 - Can now use IMS upon reaching ilvl 456 - Adjusted drop rate of Rare Metal, Sacred Hammer ### 2. Gear - Changed Heroic Oath enchanting cost for +2 -&amp;gt; +3 - Weapon - Gold : From 109,447 to 91,206 - Golden Plate : From 382 to 153 - Silver Plate : From 96 to 38 - Rare Metal : From 395 to 237 - Balance Weights : From 29 to 29 - Sacred Hammer : From 9 to 20 - Diamond : From 9 to 0 - Armor - Gold : From 65,668 to 54,723 - Golden Plate : From 229 to 92 - Silver Plate : From 57 to 23 - Rare Metal : From 237 to 142 - Balance Weights : From 17 to 17 - Sacred Hammer : From 5 to 12 - Diamond : From 6 to 0 - Gloves, boots - Gold : From 43,779 to 36,383 - Golden Plate : From 153 to 61 - Silver Plate : From 38 to 15 - Rare Metal : From 158 to 95 - Balance Weights : From 11 to 11 - Sacred Hammer : From 3 to 7 - Diamond : From 4 to 0 !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 08월 09일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-09/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 바하르의 신전 - 던전 입장 아이템 레벨 제한이 사라집니다. - 지령서 수주 장비레벨이 457에서 456으로 조정됩니다. - 장비레벨 456달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있게 됩니다. - 고급 금속물, 신성한 망치 드랍량이 상향 조정됩니다. ### 2. 장비 - 비장한 맹세 장비 2 -&amp;gt; 3강화 비용이 변경됩니다. ![](https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/images/2018-08-09-1.png) ### 3. 스타일샵 - 발키온 정찰대 포인트로 구매 가능한 외형 아이템이 추가되었습니다. - 새로운 외형으로 &#39;수호 컬렉션 의상&#39;시리즈를 판매합니다. - 해당 아이템은 9월 13일 정기점검 전까지 구입하실 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.02 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-08-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Bahaar&#39;s Temple - Requires ilvl 457 to use IMS - Located at Frymount - Drops Sacred Hammer, Dragon&#39;s Bow, Balance Weights, Rare Metal, Amplifier II, Transcendence Mask, auto-pot pet, Superior Etchings, and Meownya Innerwear (all 5 types) - Added Bahaar&#39;s Temple to Leaderboard - Added Replica Statue as Leaderboard reward ### Replica standards - Previous season rank 1 party - No replica is installed for the first season, and existing replicas are removed when seasons change - Only the rank 1 party will have their replica installed - Replica look saved as right before server maintenance - Replica look will reflect the look right before server maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 08월 02일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-08-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 신규: 바하르의 신전 - 장비레벨 457달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. (1일 1회 입장 가능/VIP 2회) - 동부 가드&amp;gt;폭염의 산맥&amp;gt;차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 신성한 망치, 용족의 활대, 무게추, 고급 금속물, 증폭제II, 초월의 가면, 자동물약 펫, 전설 각인서 상자, 고등어태비 냥이 속옷 등의 아이템을 보상으로 획득할 수 있습니다. - 리더보드에 바하르의 신전이 추가됩니다. - 리더보드 보상으로 레플리카가 추가됩니다. ### 레플리카 설치/변경 기준 1. 이전 시즌 전체 1위 파티 대상(서버) - 첫 시즌에는 레플리카가 설치되지 않으며, 시즌이 바뀔 때 기존 레플리카는 모두 제거됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.26 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-26/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Elin Brawler - Added class [Brawler] to class Elin - Cannot use Race Change Voucher ### 2. Character limit - Expanded character limi from 20 slots to 21 slots - Can receive `Additional Character Slot` from Elin Brawler event page ### 3. Battleground reward - Fixed tool tip on enchanting material that can be received from Battleground ### 4. Skill and balance - Valkyrie - Added 11% additional damage to boss monsters - Changed armor option `[Shining Crescent] Increase critical damage by 8%` to `Increase all skill damage by 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 07월 26일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-26/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 엘린 권술사 - 엘린 종족으로 선택 가능한 직업에 [권술사]가 추가됩니다. - 종족 변경권으로 변경 할 수 없습니다. ### 2. 캐릭터 소켓 확장 - 최대 소켓이 20칸에서 21칸으로 확장됩니다. - 엘린 권술사 이벤트 페이지에 방문하여 캐릭터 소켓 확장권을 지급받으실 수 있습니다. ### 3. 전장 보상 - 일부 전장 획득 강화 재료 툴팁이 사양에 맞게 수정됩니다. ### 4. 스킬&amp;amp;밸런스 - 월광무사 - 보스 몬스터 타격 시 공격력이 약 11% 상승합니다. - 갑옷 옵션 중, &#39;[신월: 달빛의 공명] 치명타 위력 8% 증가&#39; 옵션이 &#39;모든 스킬 위력 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.19 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-19/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - New : Lyan&#39;s Underground Temple (hard) - Requires ilvl 455 to use IMS (1 entry, 2 with VIP) - Located at Dragonfall - Drops Rare Metal, Dragons Bow, Balance Weights, Accessory Amplifier I/II, Transcendence Mask, and Meownya Innerwear (all 5 types) - New : Lyan&#39;s Underground Temple - Requires ilvl 453 to use IMS (1 entry, 2 with VIP) - Located at Dragonfall - Drops Elemental Essence, Pansophic Ash, Brooch etchings I/II, Accessory Amplifier I, Infinity Mask, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 07월 19일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-19/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 신규: 왜곡된 리안의 지하 전당 - 장비레벨 455달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. (1일 1회/VIP 2회 입장 가능) - 실바니아 가드&amp;gt;그림자 숲&amp;gt;차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 고급 금속물, 용족의 활대, 무게추, 액세서리 증폭제 I,II, 초월의 가면, 고등어태비 냥이 속옷 5종 (강인한, 생명의, 날카로운, 수호의, 흐름의)등의 아이템을 보상으로 획득할 수 있습니다. - 신규: 리안의 지하 전당 - 장비레벨 453달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.13 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-13/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Skill - Revert chain skill to the state before 07.12 Developer comment - Gunner - Rolling Reload - Changed skill cooldown to 4 seconds after using just 1 time, to be able to use 2 times - Dashing Reload - Changed skill cooldown to 4 seconds after using just 1 time, to be able to use 2 times ### Bug fixes - Skill - Sorcerer : Fixed issue where Elemental Fusion skill did not immediately go on cooldown - Fixed issue where charging skills would go off earlier than expected - Ninja : Fixed issue where using Leaves on the Wind as a chain skill in between Boomerang Shuriken occasionally crashed client - Gunner : Fixed issue where [Blast] related glyphs did not take effect on additional missiles from [Summon Beam Panel]-applied [Arcane Beam] - Fixed issue where hit from behind buff of Apex passive skills did not specify `on monsters` - UI - Fixed issue where Champion laurel did not display on party UI - Fixed issue where whisper alert setting would alert as `undefined` - Fixed issue where adjusting font size on chat UI would apply to all tabs (not fixed) - Fixed issue where adjusting shortcuts did not work properly - Fixed issue where skill or items did not register on item slot after immediately removing skill or item off the skill slot by drag and drop - Fixed issue where chain skills did not work upon registering in the right extended skill slot - Fixed issue where shortcut settings before 07.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 07월 13일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-13/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 스킬 - 이어지는 스킬이 7월 12일 업데이트 이전 사양으로 변경됩니다. [개발자 코멘트] - 자동으로 설정된 이어지는 스킬과 직접 설정한 이어지는 스킬을 동시에 이용하는 수호자님의 불편을 고려하여 기존의 방식대로 되돌렸습니다. - 마공사 - 구르기: 산탄 장전 - 1회만 사용했을 경우, 4초후에 다시 2회를 사용할 수 있도록 변경됩니다 - 대쉬: 미사일 장전 - 1회만 사용했을 경우, 4초후에 다시 2회를 사용할 수 있도록 변경됩니다 ### [버그수정] - 스킬 - 마법사 융합 스킬의 쿨타임이 사용 즉시 적용되지 않는 문제 - 차징류 스킬의 자동발동 시점이 이전보다 빠른 문제 - 인술사 표창 연사 스킬을 부메랑 수리검 이후 연계로 사용 시 확률적으로 클라이언트 크래시가 발생하는 문제 - 마공사 [일반 포탄 발사] 관련 문장 효과가 [빔 판넬 소환] 효과가 적용된 [아케인 빔 포격]의 추가 미사일에 효과가 적용되지 않는 문제 - 각성 후방판정 관련 패시브 스킬 설명에 &#39;몬스터 적용&#39; 조건이 누락된 문제 - UI - 파티창에서 챔피언 등급 업적 클래스 마크가 잘못 출력되고 있는 문제 - 귓속말 알림기능 설정 시 귓속말 내용이 undefined로 출력되는 문제 - 현재 탭 옵션에서 글자 크기 조절 시 다른 탭까지 값이 적용되는 문제 - 일부 메뉴 단축키 변경 시 변경된 단축키 정보가 비정상적으로 출력되는 문제 - 숏컷에 등록되어 있는 스킬이나 아이템을 드래그 앤 드롭으로 제거한 직후 스킬이나 아이템을 재등록 할 수 없는 문제 - 우측 추가 슬롯에 스킬 등록 시 연속 공격이 사용되지 않는 문제 - 7월 12일 정기점검 이전 설정해 놓은 일부 버튼이 패치 이후 중복되는 문제 - 파티장 메뉴 – 모든 던전 초기화 기능이 동작하지 않는 문제 - 퀘스트 - 각성 퀘스트 진행 중 내면 세계에서 사망 시 각성 퀘스트를 진행 할 수 없는 문제 - 던전 - 상급/하급 테네브리스 성채 3네임드에서 악마화 적용 후 받는 데미지 증가 효과가 고정 데미지에는 적용되지 않는 문제 - 테네브리스 성채 3네임드 악마화 효과가 꺼지지 않는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.12 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-12/</guid>
      <description>## Apex and skill udpate ### 1. Class Awakening - Adde Apex Skills to 6 classes : Archer, Ninja, Gunner, Reaper, Valkyrie, Sorcer - Mission quest can be proceeded upon reaching ilvl 439 and acquire [Apex Skills]. - Adjusted recommended glyph setup and chain skills for all Class Awakening part. 1 classes except Mystic ### 2. Skill and balance adjustments - Added new skills and changed a few existing skills appropriate to the Class Awakening update - Sorcerer - [Apex Skill] Elemental Cores (active) - Imbues elements to existing offensive skills, and elements divide into Flame, Frost, and Lightning - Depending on the combination of collected elements, skills enabled by [Elemental Fusion] changes - Normally you are allowed to fuse 2 elements, but during [Mana Boost] you can fuse up to 3 elements - [Apex Skill] Ice Spear (active) - Throws frost projectiles forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 07월 12일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-12/</guid>
      <description>## 각성 및 스킬 업데이트 ### 1. 클래스 각성 - 궁수,인술사,마공사,비검사,월광무사,마법사 6개 클래스에게 각성 스킬이 추가됩니다. - 장비레벨 439 달성 시 신규 미션 퀘스트 &#39;미스텔의 길&#39;을 통해 각성을 진행할 수 있으며, 퀘스트 완료 시 [각성 스킬]을 획득할 수 있습니다. - 정령사를 제외한 1차 클래스들의 추천문장과 모든 클래스들의 이어지는 스킬이 현재 딜사이클에 맞춰 조정됩니다. ### 2. 스킬 및 밸런스 조정 - 클래스 각성 업데이트에 따라 신규 스킬이 추가되고 일부 기존 스킬이 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 07월 05일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-07-05/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 레벨 달성 보상 UI 개선 - 보상을 누적하여 한번에 수령 가능하도록 개선됩니다. - * 이미 보상 UI가 4개를 초과하여 보상을 받지 못하신 수호자님께 오늘 중 보상을 지급해드릴 예정이었으나, 대상자 추출에 문제가 있어 07/12(목)으로 지급일이 연기되었습니다. 안내드린 일정을 지키지 못해 죄송합니다. ### [버그수정] - 스킬 - 권술사 클래스로 연타, 강타, 태풍연타를 반복 사용하여 진동 버프를 무한 유지하는 문제 수정 - 아이템 - 장비 패시브 옵션 효과가 간헐적으로 적용되지 않는 문제 수정  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.28 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-28/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Elin Gunner - Can now create Elin Gunner - Cannot use Race Change Voucher to create an Elin Gunner ### 2. Balance - Slightly adjusted balancing of all classes except reaper throughout level progression ### Bug fixes - Leaderboard - Fixed issue where ranking titles were not collected from players - Island of Dawn - Fixed issue where caiman thieves did not spawn  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 06월 28일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-28/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 엘린 마공사 - 엘린 마공사를 상시 생성할 수 있게 됩니다. - 종족 변경권으로 엘린 마공사로 변경은 할 수 없습니다. ### 2. 밸런스 - 비검사를 제외한 클래스들의 성장구간 밸런스가 소폭 조정됩니다. ### [버그수정] - 순위표 - 네임 플레이트가 회수되지 않은 문제 수정 - 여명의 정원 - 여명의 정원에서 시누스 도둑이 출현하지 않는 문제 수정  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.21 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-21/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Item - Added clear face cosmetic - This item equipped in the face style slot hides the expressed appearance of masks - Randomly drops from level 65 party dungeons - Sells for 8,000 T-cat in the T-cat merchant - Added clear back cosmetic - to level 65 dungeons and Tikat - This item equipped in the back style slot hides the expressed appearance of weapons - Randomly drops from level 65 party dungeons - Sells for 8,000 T-cat in the T-cat merchant ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 06월 21일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-21/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 아이템 - 투명 얼굴 장식 아이템이 추가됩니다. - 해당 아이템을 얼굴 스타일 슬롯에 장착할 경우 얼굴에 장착되어 있는 가면이 보이지 않게 됩니다. - 65레벨 파티 던전에서 일정 확률로 드랍됩니다. - T-cat 상점에서 8,000 T-cat 에 판매됩니다. - 투명 등 장식 아이템이 추가됩니다. - 해당 아이템을 등 스타일 슬롯에 장착할 경우 평화 상태에서 등에 있는 무기가 보이지 않게 됩니다. - 65레벨 파티 던전에서 일정 확률로 드랍됩니다. - T-cat 상점에서 8,000 T-cat 에 판매됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.14 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-14/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Summer festival - K TERA exclusive ### 2. Guardian Legion mission - Decreased HP of the initial two dragons for Superior GLM - Adjusted Superior GLM time from 15:30 minutes to 18:30 minutes ### 3. Cruel Dreadspire - Adjusted 5th floor and 10th floor reward - Adjusted to increase gold reward - 5th floor : 22,000 gold to 30,000 gold - 10th floor : 22,000 gold to 50,000 gold - Removed the following rewards - Carved Ornament - Copper Clasp - Otherwordly SHard - Pansophic Ash - Added combat consumables - Bravery Potion, Superior Noctenium Infusion, Fed: Health Potion, Fed: Rejuvenation Potion ### 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 06월 14일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-14/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 여름 축제 - 07/12(목)까지 여름 축제가 오픈되며, 여름 축제 홍보용 NPC가 배치됩니다. - 여름 축제 NPC 배치 장소 - 대도시 내부-벨리카, 알레만시아, 카이아도르 - 축제장소-태양의 정원, 뱀의 섬 ### 2. 수호자 임무 - 전설 수호자 임무 &#39;덮쳐오는 복수의 발톱&#39; 에 등장하는 에스트, 오스트의 HP가 하향됩니다. - &#39;덮쳐오는 복수의 발톱&#39; 임무 시간이 15분 30초 -&amp;gt; 18분 30초로 조정됩니다. ### 3. 잔혹한 환영의 탑 - 5층과 10층의 보상이 조정됩니다. - 골드 보상이 상향 조정됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.07 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-06-07/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Shadow Sanguinary (hard) - Requires ilvl 446 - Teleportal located at Highwatch Outskirts - Drops Mask of the Beginning, and other top-tier enchanting materials - Shadow Sanguinary (normal) - Requires ilvl 439 - Teleportal located at Highwatch Outskirts - Drops Golden Talent, Silver Talent, and other high-tier enchanting materials ### 2. Item - Added new accessories - Transcendence Necklace - Transcendence Earring - Transcendence Ring - Transcendence Circlet - Heroic Vow Belt - Added items required to promote to new accessories - (Following items can be acquired from Antaroth&#39;s Abyss (hard), RK-9 Kennel (hard), and Rakelith&#39;s Manor (hard)) - Worn crate - Devil&#39;s Claw - Dragon&#39;s Skull - Added Talent Reset Potion to Specialty Merchants at each town (K TERA exclusive) - Price : 2,000 gold ### 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 06월 07일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-06-07/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 폭군 듀리온의 안식처 - 장비 레벨 446 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 바라카니아 가드&amp;gt; 고대 바라카 유적터&amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장하실 수 있습니다. - 시작의 가면, 최상위 장비 강화 재료 등을 획득하실 수 있습니다. - 듀리온의 안식처 - 장비 레벨 439 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 바라카니아 가드&amp;gt; 고대 바라카 유적터&amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장하실 수 있습니다. - 아르보레아의 금빛 결정체, 아르보레아의 은빛 결정체 및 상위 장비 강화 재료 등을 획득할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.31 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-31/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Battleground - Added Bellicarium credits to rewards and enchanting material box - Revised reward - Corsairs&#39; Stronghold - Win : - 90,000 Bellicarium credits - 7x enchanting material boxes - Lose : - 30,000 Bellicarium credits - 4x enchanting material boxes - Fraywind Canyon - Win : - 90,000 Bellicarium credits - 8x enchanting material boxes - Lose : - 30,000 Bellicarium credits - 5x enchanting material boxes - Champion&#39;s Skyring (solo) - Win : - 9,000 Bellicarium credits - 7x Golden Talents - Lose : - 3,000 Bellicarium credits - 3x Silver Talents - Champion&#39;s Skyring (team) - Win : - 4,500 Bellicarium credits - 7x Golden Talents - Lose : - 1,500 Bellicarium credits - 3x Silver Talents !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 05월 31일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-31/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 전장 - 전장 보상에 승리의 인도자 평판 포인트가 추가되며, 강화 재료 상자가 추가 지급됩니다. - 개편 보상 ![](https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/images/2018-08-31-1.png) - 포화/명예의 전장 지령서 보상 중 투사의 강화재료 상자 1개가 투사의 강화 재료 상자II 2개로 변경됩니다. - 승리의 인도자 평판 포인트 최대치가 2,000,000으로 상승합니다. - 승리의 인도자 평판 상점 정보는 아래와 같습니다. - 평판 포인트 상점 - 아이템 이름 | 구매 포인트 - 미지의 액체 금속 | 3,000 - 어둠이 깃든 정신 지배 장치 | 6,000 - 상급 아크데바 묘약 | 30,000 - 아크데바 장인의 강화 도구 | 9,600 - 피로 물든 금속 구조물 | 18,000 - 무언의 가루 | 30,000 - 신비의 성수 | 600,000 - 불길한 마법 스크롤 | 6,000 - 정밀하게 세공된 장식 조각 | 12,000 - 이공간의 파편 | 200,000 - 마지막 원소 | 1,500,000 - 루비 | 10,000 - 강화 재료 상자를 통해 아래 아이템 중 1종을 획득할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.24 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-24/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Style shop - K TERA exclusive ### 2. Event item removal - K TERA exclusive ### Bug fixes - Dungeon - Broken Prison, 3rd boss : Fixed issue where portals did not get destroyed occasionally - Cruel Dreadspire, 8th floor : Fixed issue where 2 aggro marks were designated - Kalivan&#39;s Challenge : Fixed issue where defeating 1st boss did not open path to 2nd boss - UI - Fixed issue where certain profile elements were empty occasionally - K TERA event exclusive - Skill - Lancer : Fixed issue where Adrenaline Rush talent effect to increase skill damage by 5% did not apply  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 05월 24일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-24/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 스타일샵 - 발키온 정찰대 포인트로 구매 가능한 외형 아이템이 추가되었습니다. - 새로운 외형으로 &#39;무자비한 무기&#39; 시리즈를 판매합니다. - 해당 아이템은 6월 21일 정기점검 전까지 구입하실 수 있습니다. ### 2. 이벤트 아이템 삭제 - 슈퍼위크 럭키 이벤트 아이템인 [이벤트] 잔칫상, 정제된 녹테늄 강화탄[전설], [이벤트] 용맹의 물약II 가 기간종료로 삭제됩니다. ### [버그수정] - 던전 - 뒤틀린 라칸의 제단 3네임드 발바토스 차원의 문이 확률적으로 파괴되지 않는 문제 - 잔혹한 환영의 탑 8층에서 보스 몬스터의 어그로 마크가 2개 생성되는 문제 - 약화된 켈리반의 돌격선에서 1네임드 처치 후 다음 지역으로 가는 문이 열리지 않는 문제 - UI - 특정 상황에서 캐릭터 기본정보 UI가 빈 상태로 출력되는 문제 - 붉은 에메랄드 큐브 툴팁에 획득 가능한 아이템이 일부 누락되어 있는 문제 - 스킬 - 창기사 전투의 의지 스킬의 지속 특성 유지시간 중 스킬 위력 5% 효과가 적용되지 않는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.18 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-18/</guid>
      <description>### Bug fixes - Skill - Fixed issue where shield-type skills absorbed a static amount of damage - Item - 붉은 에메랄드 큐브 툴팁 획득 리스트에 희귀 스킬교본:블루/옐로우 리리가 누락된 문제 수정 - (* 희귀 스킬교본: 피닉스,본드래곤 누락 문제 또한 차후 점검을 통해 수정할 예정입니다.)  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 05월 18일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-18/</guid>
      <description>### [버그수정] - 스킬 - 보호막류 스킬이 고정 데미지를 흡수하는 문제 수정 - 아이템 - 붉은 에메랄드 큐브 툴팁 획득 리스트에 희귀 스킬교본:블루/옐로우 리리가 누락된 문제 수정 - (* 희귀 스킬교본: 피닉스,본드래곤 누락 문제 또한 차후 점검을 통해 수정할 예정입니다.)  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.17 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-17/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Skill and balance adjustment - Priest - Mana Infusion - Decreased total casting time by 2 seconds, and increased casting speed by 10% - Increased MP regeneration from 100 to 500 MP per second - Decreased duration from 20 seconds to 10 seconds - Increased cooldown from 10 seconds to 20 seconds - Changed to maintain abnormality even after using attack skills or getting hit - Slayer - Energy Rush - Changed skill to apply as increase 25% crit chance as it is written in the skill tooltip rather than increase 25% crit factor - Reaper - Shadow Reaping - Changed cooldown from 120 seconds to 90 seconds - Enhanced Shadow Reaping - Changed attacks peed increase from 5% to 4% - Berserker - Thunder Strike - Decreased PVP damage by 5% ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 05월 17일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-17/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 스킬 밸런스 조정 - 사제 - 마력 회복 - 전체 시전시간이 2초 감소하며, 시전속도가 10% 상승합니다. - 1초당 MP 회복량이 100에서 500으로 증가합니다. - 회복 유지시간이 20초에서 10초로 감소합니다. - 재사용 대기시간이 10초에서 20초로 증가합니다. - 공격 스킬 사용 시, 피격 시에 효과가 삭제되지 않도록 변경됩니다. - 무사 - 기력방출 - 툴팁에 치명타 확률 25% 로 기재되어 있었으나 치명타 유발 25% 증가로 적용되고 있던 부분을 툴팁 사양대로 변경하였습니다. - 비검사 - 어둠 강림 - 재사용 대기시간이 120초에서 90초로 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.10 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-10/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Event item removal - Removed Manglemire event related items ### 2. Guardian Legion mission additional reward - Distributed additional rewards that were not distributed to players properly - Distributed via parcel ### Bug fixes - UI - Fixed issue where Lancer&#39;s perfect block UI would display longer than the reflected damage splash - Fixed issue where items distributed through events could not be registered on a skill slot - Dungeon - Demon&#39;s Wheel, 1st boss : Fixed issue where aoe attacks would explode immediately when boss is defeated  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 05월 10일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-10/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 이벤트 아이템 삭제 - [이벤트] 타르스키 코인, [이벤트] 타르스키 코인 정제수, [이벤트] 정제된 타르스키 코인이 삭제됩니다. ### 2. 수호자 임무 추가 보상 지급 - 04/19(목) ~ 04/26(목) 점검 전 까지 오류로 미지급 된 수호자 임무 추가 보상이 지급됩니다. - 비행/전설 수호자 임무에서 추가 보상 지급 기준을 달성하였으나, 미지급 된 수량만큼 참여 캐릭터의 우편으로 보상이 지급됩니다. ### [버그수정] - UI - 창기사 완벽한 방어 UI가 반사 데미지 효과 시간보다 오래 출력되는 문제 - 이벤트로 지급된 수량성 전투 소모품 아이템을 단축키에 등록할 수 없는 문제 - 던전 - 데모로스의 룰렛 1네임드의 장판 공격이 1네임드 사망 시 즉시 폭발하는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.03 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-05-03/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Demon&#39;s Wheel - 5 man dungeon reopen - Teleportal : Alementheia Outskirts - ilvl required : 439 - Dyad Niveot Structure, [Event] Afro, [Event] Lamb Bulgogi can be earned ### 2. Civil Unrest - Changed so that only guild members with authority can place Guild Tower ### 3. Underground Arena - Changed operating hours - Changed rank rewards - 1st : 9x medals - 2-3rd : 7x medals - 4-7th : 6x medals - 8-10th : 5x medals - Medal shop - 2 : Health Potion - 4 : Bravery Potion II - 14 : Rare Noctenium Refiner - 6 : Underground arena golden talent box - 240 : Rare innerwear exchange voucher - 10 : Dragonscale - 120 : Niveot Structure - 800 : Smart Niveot Structure Developer comment ### 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 05월 03일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-05-03/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 데모로스의 룰렛 - 5인 파티 던전 데모로스의 룰렛이 05/31(목) 점검 전까지 오픈됩니다. - 알레만시아 인근 &#39;산 알레마 마을&#39;의 게이트를 통해 던전에 입장할 수 있습니다. - 장비 레벨 439 달성 시 발키온 지령서 선택 지령 목록에 데모로스의 룰렛이 표시됩니다. - 아티팩트 원석 VII, [이벤트] 아프로 헤어, [이벤트] 양 불고기 등 다양한 보상을 획득 할 수 있습니다. ### 2. 길드대전 - 길드 전초기지 건설 권한이 길드 자금 사용 권한을 가진 길드원만 설치 가능하도록 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.26 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-26/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Adjusted balance on Cruel Dreadspire - Adjusted to decrease HP of each monster - Decreased the frequency of patterns for 3rd floor Dakuryon - Decreased the stack debuff difficulty of 6th floor Krakatox - Closed Manglemire - Disabled usage of Chocolates (consumables) in ranking contents. entering dungeons with the buffs will removes the consumables. the following dungeons are affected : - Cruel Dreadspire - Antaros&#39; Abyss (hard) - Pit of Petrax Developer comment ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 04월 26일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-26/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 잔혹한 환영의 탑 밸런스가 조정됩니다. - 각 네임드의 체력이 하향 조정되었습니다. - 3층 듀리온 패턴 빈도수를 하향하였습니다. - 6층 퀴르갈 중첩 디버프 난이도를 하향하였습니다. - 타르스키의 놀이터가 입장 불가로 변경됩니다. - 순위기록 컨텐츠에서 초콜렛 아이템을 사용할 수 없도록 변경됩니다. 컨텐츠 이용 전, 이미 사용한 초콜릿의 효과는 입장 시 제거됩니다. 초콜렛을 사용할 수 없는 컨텐츠는 아래와 같습니다. - 잔혹한 환영의 탑 - 공허한 안타로스의 심연 - 페트레 양성소 [개발자 코멘트] - 이벤트성으로 지급된 소모품 아이템의 효과가 순위 경쟁에 영향을 끼칠 만큼 높은 성능을 지니고 있고, 해당 아이템의 유무에 따라 순위가 갈리는 현상을 방지하고자 하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.20 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-20/</guid>
      <description>### Bug fixes - Flying Guardian Legion mission - Fixed issue regarding server instability and reopen mission - Skill - Fixed issue where certain shield-type skills were able to absorb more damage than it should - Item - Fixed issue where mid-tier Island of Dawn enchanting box had missing possible items in its tool tip - Dungeon - Fixed issue in Rakelith&#39;s Manor where 3rd boss dropped Dyad Niveot Structure - Fixed the drops of the following dungeons : - Rebel&#39;s Hideout - Adjusted to decrease drop amount of Archdevan Formula - Island of Dawn - Adjusted to increase drop amount of Golden Talents to maximum in mid-tier Island of Dawn enchanting boxes - Rk-9 Kennel (hard) - Removed Enchanting Crate from reward - Sky Cruiser Endeavor - Adjusted to increase drop amount of Hypnotic Device - Event - K TERA exclusive  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 04월 20일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-20/</guid>
      <description>### [버그수정] - 비행 수호자 임무 - 서버 불안정 요인 수정 및 임무 재오픈 - 스킬 - 일부 보호막류 스킬 사용 시 보호막 수치보다 높은 고정 데미지까지 모두 흡수하는 문제 - 아이템 - 중급 여명의 강화 재료 상자 툴팁에 일부 획득 가능 아이템 내용이 누락되어 있는 문제 - 던전 - 라켈리스의 폐허 3네임드가 아티팩트 원석을 드랍하는 문제 - 4월 19일 패치내역 중 사양과 다르게 적용된 사항이 발견되어 아래와 같이 수정됩니다. - 혁명단 은거지 - 불길한 마법 스크롤 드랍량이 하향 조정됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.19 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-19/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Guardian Legion mission - Added flying Guardian Legion missions `Rhapsody of Wind and Fire` and `Recon Eradication Mission` - Can only be taken by level 65 players, and can participate in the same way as existing Guardian Legion missions - World map &amp;gt; Guardian Legion mode toggle &amp;gt; Track mission &amp;gt; Enter mission - As the mission partakes in the air, you can only carry out the mission with a flying mount - You can gain Guardian Legion points in the same way as existing Guardian Legion missions, and with enough points you can earn Guardian Legion gem box, item XP, and Guardian Legion credits - Successfully clearing flying Guardian Legion missions can reward either 1-3x Mark of Flight or a Superior Etching Box as [additional reward] - Additional reward ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 04월 19일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-19/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 수호자 임무 - 비행 수호자 임무 &#39;바람과 불의 광시곡&#39;과 &#39;정찰기 섬멸작전&#39;이 추가됩니다. - 65레벨만 진행할 수 있으며, 일반 수호자 임무와 동일한 방식으로 참여 가능합니다. - 월드맵 &amp;gt; 수호자 모드 활성화 &amp;gt; 아르보레아의 수호자 임무 추적 &amp;gt; 수호자 임무 입장 - 공중에서 진행되는 컨텐츠로, 비행 탈것에 탑승해야만 임무를 정상적으로 수행할 수 있습니다. - 일반 수호자 임무와 동일하게 &#39;수호자 임무 점수&#39;를 획득할 수 있으며, 포인트를 일정량 획득하면 수호자 임무 보석 상자, 장비 숙련도, 평판 포인트를 획득할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.12 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-12/</guid>
      <description>### 1. PVP - Disabled Outlaw content - Existing skill is turned off, and Infamy reset to 0 Developer comment ### Bug fixes - Dreadspire - Fixed issue where player&#39;s death location was different per player - Fixed issue on 3rd floor where projectiles from demokrons one shot players - Skill - Fixed issue where Baraka Priest&#39;s Zenobia&#39;s Vortex IX skill casting speed was different compared to other races - Fixed issue where Warrior&#39;s Blade Frenzy tooltip did not have cooldown information - Fixed issue where using Lancer&#39;s Stand Fast increased based attack speed stat in Profile UI - Fixed issue where Ninja&#39;s Jagged Path tooltip information of distance was different from actual distance traversed - Fixed issue where Reaper&#39;s Soul Reversal talent did not apply to large monsters Developer comment - Services - Some comment - Restyle Hat - Fixed issue where previewing a hat while equipping a restyled hat displayed the preview hat with the restyled settings  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 04월 12일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-12/</guid>
      <description>### 1. PVP - 무법자 컨텐츠가 임시 중단됩니다. - 기존에 습득한 무법자 스킬도 off 되며, 악명 포인트가 0으로 초기화 됩니다. [개발자 코멘트] - 의도치 않은 악용이 지속 발생하고 있으며, 사용성 개선이 필요하다고 판단하여 일시적으로 무법자 컨텐츠를 중단하게 되었습니다. 추후 개선된 모습으로 업데이트 될 예정입니다. ### [버그수정] - 환영의 탑 - 바포메트의 전방 올려치기 공격에 피격 시 사망위치가 플레이어별로 상이한 문제 - 3층에서 &#39;저주받은 실험체의 환영&#39;이 발사한 구슬에 피격될 시 즉시 사망하는 문제 - 스킬 - 바라카 사제의 재생의 바람 IX 스킬 시전 속도가 다른 종족과 상이한 문제 - 검투사 이단 검무 스킬 툴팁에 재사용 대기시간이 출력되지 않는 문제 - 창기사 방패 방어 스킬 사용 시 캐릭터 정보 UI (기본 능력치)에서 이동속도 수치가 증가하는 문제 - 인술사 연쇄도약 스킬 이동 거리가 툴팁과 실제 거리가 상이한 문제 - 비검사 위치 교환 – 연계 쾌속 특성을 중형 몬스터에게 사용 시 효과가 적용되지 않는 문제 - (추가) 광전사 피의 보복 패시브 효과가 힐/정화를 받을 때도 적용이 되던 문제 - (추가) 사제 수호자의 성역 탈출 특성이 찬란한 섬광에 의한 본인 피격에도 적용되던 문제 [개발자 코멘트] - 사제/광전사의 이번 오류 수정으로, 기존 상황에서 플레이 하셨던 수호자님께는 적지 않은 변화가 생겼다는 점을 인지하고 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.05 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-04-05/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Cruel Dreadspire - Added Final Element to 5th floor reward - Increased item drop rate by 2 times excluding gold by changing Joy of Partying to apply - Pit of Petrax - Changed Petrax to not enrage regardless of aggro unless damage is dealt - Changed timer condition to upon hitting monster ### 2. Leaderboard - Due to rankings made with a bug, Pit of Petrax rankings has been reset - Changed ranking conditions for Dreadspire - From clearing 4th floor -&amp;gt; to 1st floor ### 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 04월 05일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-04-05/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 잔혹한 환영의 탑 - 5층 클리어 보상으로 마지막 원소가 추가됩니다. - 파티의 즐거움이 적용되도록 변경하여 골드 보상을 제외한 아이템 드랍율이 2배 증가합니다. - 페트레 양성소 - 페트레에게 대미지 없이 적대치 획득만으로는 분노상태를 유발할 수 없게 변경됩니다. - 타이머 조건이 페트레에게 대미지가 적용되는 순간 시작으로 변경됩니다. ### 2. 순위표 - 페트레 양성소 기록이 비정상적인 방법으로 기록되어 이전 기록을 초기화합니다. - 잔혹한 환영의 탑 순위표 등록 조건을 변경합니다. - 4층 클리어 -&amp;gt; 1층 클리어 ### 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03.29 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-29/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - New dungeon : Cruel Dreadspire - 10 floor 5-man dungeon - There is no ilvl requirement, and 1 entry (2 for VIP) per day upon reaching level 65 - Dungeon teleportal is located at Tempest Reach - The following items are rewarded per floor : - Floor 5 - Elemental Essence - Copper Clasp - Pansophic Ash - Archdevan Formula - Carved Ornament - Otherworldly Shard - Gold Reward - Floor 10 - Final Element - Copper Clasp - Pansophic Ash - Archdevan Formula - Carved Ornament - Otherworldly Shard - Gold Reward - Floor 1-5 - Dreadspire Helmet - Floor 6-10 - Dreadspire Armor !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 03월 29일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-29/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 신규: [잔혹한 환영의 탑] - 1~10층까지 보스 몬스터로만 구성된 5인 파티 던전입니다. - 장비레벨에 따른 입장제한은 없으며, 65레벨 달성 시 1일 1회(vip 1일 2회) 입장할 수 있습니다. - 던전 입장 차원의 마법석은 웨스토니아 가드 &amp;gt; 얼어붙은 해안 &amp;gt; 빙하의 만에 위치해 있으며, 월드맵을 통해 상세 위치를 확인해 보실 수 있습니다. - 층 별 보상은 아래와 같습니다. ![](https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/mysterium/images/2018-03-29-1.png) - 던전 순위표에 잔혹한 환영의 탑이 추가됩니다. - 거짓말쟁이 타르스키의 놀이터 오픈 - 5인 파티 던전 거짓말쟁이 타르스키의 놀이터가 기간한정으로 재오픈 됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03.22 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-22/</guid>
      <description>### Bug fixes - Services - Fixed issue where Restyle Hat on cloud-type cosmetics crashed client  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 03월 22일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-22/</guid>
      <description>### [버그수정] - 부가서비스 - 구름 류 스타일 아이템을 위치 또는 회전 변환 시 게임이 종료되는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03-15 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-15/</guid>
      <description>- 1. Battleground - Adjusted rewards for `Corsair&#39;s Stronghold`, `Fraywind Canyon` - Win reward - Corsair&#39;s Stronghold - Champion&#39;s Enchanting Chest x5 -&amp;gt; x7 - Fraywind Canyon - Champion&#39;s Enchanting Chest x6 -&amp;gt; x8 - Lose reward - Corsair&#39;s Stronghold - Champion&#39;s Enchanting Chest x1 -&amp;gt; x4 - Fraywind Canyon - Champion&#39;s Enchanting Chest x1 -&amp;gt; x5 - Added the following items to `Champion&#39;s Enchanting Chest` : - Last Element, Mask of Infinity - Changed `Corsair&#39;s Stronghold` cooldown - Changed from 15 minutes -&amp;gt; 10 minutes ### Bug fixes - Skill - Lancer : Fixed issue where nearby PC emotes were cancelled upon holding shield - Mystic : Talent comment - Priest : Fixed issue where two of Backstep, Fiery Escape skills were displayed in the Chain Skill UI - Berserker : Fixed issue where maximum viewing distance would decrease upon dying during Berserk status - Priest : Fixed issue where Salvation (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 03월 15일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-15/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 전장 - &#39;포화의 전장&#39;, &#39;명예의 전장&#39;의 보상이 조정됩니다. - 승리 보상 - 포화의 전장 – 투사의 강화 재료 상자 5개 → 7개 지급 - 명예의 전장 – 투사의 강화 재료 상자 6개 → 8개 지급 - 패배 보상 - 포화의 전장 – 투사의 강화 재료 상자 1개 → 4개 지급 - 명예의 전장 – 투사의 강화 재료 상자 1개 → 5개 지급 - &#39;투사의 강화 재료 상자&#39;로 획득 가능한 아이템이 추가됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03.08 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-03-08/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Battleground - Kumas Royale - Changed kick vote rate - Changed from 100% yes votes to 80% yes votes excluding player to be kicked - Adjusted lose reward - Adjusted from 1 Kumas Royale Receipt to 3 Kumas Royale Receipts ### 2. Item/quest item deletion - K TERA exclusive - K TERA exclusive ### Bug fixes - Services - Fixed issue where game would crash when equipping and unequipping hat accesssory repeatedly - Dungeon - Fixed issue in Antaros&#39; Abyss where resetting instance did not teleport players out of the instance  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 03월 08일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-03-08/</guid>
      <description>###1. 전장 - 쿠마스 놀이터 - 추방 투표율이 변경됩니다. - 100% 찬성 → 추방 대상자 제외 80% 찬성으로 변경 - 패배 보상이 조정됩니다. - 1개 지급되던 &#39;전사 꿈나무 격려문&#39; 지급 수량이 3개로 조정 ### 2. 이벤트/퀘스트 아이템 삭제 - 혁명단 은거지/안타로스의 심연 의뢰서 아이템 및 퀘스트 삭제 - 코드네임 : TERA 이벤트 관련 아이템 (글자조각, 파편, 글자 조합 상자, GM의 두근두근 선물 상자) 삭제 ### [버그수정] - 부가서비스 - 특정 상황에서 스타일 모자 탈착 반복 시 게임이 종료되는 문제 - 던전 - 안타로스의 심연(상급/하급) 던전 클리어 후, 인던 초기화를 진행해도 던전 밖으로 이동되지 않던 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.28 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-28/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Skill and balance - Valkyrie - Balder&#39;s Tears - Added `Ragnarok Healing` effect to prevent decay, while recovering 67 points per second - Added `Ragnorok Healing` effect immediately ends upon end of Balder&#39;s Tears, or entering combat - Ragnarok point - Changed to not reset upon death - Changed `Gjallar Horn` and `Max Ragnarok` effects from ending upon death - Changed effect duration of `Max Ragnarok` which prevents decay upon 1000 Ragnarok points from 60 seconds to 40 seconds - Changed base decay rate to 50 points per second - Gunner - Talent : Burst Fire - [Force] (x% chance to apply y power which stacks up to 5 times) - Changed Talent effect duration from 5 seconds to 12 seconds - Command : Recall - Decreased cooldown at each skill level by 10 seconds - Bombardment - Decreased Arcane Energy cost from 1500 to 1000 - Increased skill damage by 20% - Burst Fire - Increased skill damage by 15% - Increased Arcane Energy cost from 70 to 75 - Mana Missiles - Increased skill damage by 8% - Scattershot - Increased skill damage by 10% - Energy shot (HB shot) - Increased skill daamge by 10% - Slayer - Piercing Lunge (Awakened skill) - Changed to immediately cancel any previous skill motion - Changed all attacks to be considered from behind after the 2nd hit (from 5 seconds) to 4 seconds - Priest - Innervate - Changed crit power increase description in the tooltip - Mystic - Augmentation - Changed crit power increase description in the tooltip - Sorcerer - Arcane Pulse - Decreased charging time by 20% (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 02월 28일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-28/</guid>
      <description>1. 스킬 및 밸런스 - 월광무사 - 달빛의 가호 - &#39;월광력 회복&#39; 효과가 추가로 적용되어 자연 감소하지 않고, 초당 67씩 회복됩니다. - &#39;월광력 회복&#39; 효과는 달빛의 가호 버프가 종료되거나, 전투상태로 돌입할 경우 즉시 해제됩니다. - 월광력 - 캐릭터가 사망해도 월광력이 초기화되지 않도록 변경됩니다. - 캐릭터가 사망해도 월광력 감소를 억제하는 달빛 집중, 월광력 최대 충전 효과가 제거되지 않습니다. - 월광력이 1,000이 되었을 때 월광력이 감소하지 않도록 하는 &#39;월광력 최대 충전&#39; 효과의 지속시간이 60초에서 40초로 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.22 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-22/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon server stabilization - Proceeded with sabilization update to reduce player lag issues ### 2. Proxy block - Proceeded with security update to block Proxy usage (memeslash block) ### Bug fixes - Dungeon - Fixed issue where player location did not sync with the server during certain dungeon mechanics - Quest - Fixed issue where `The Traitor of Acarum` quest NPC stated the wrong location - Fixed issue where Frymount NPCs Eurice and Kenela did not exist - Fixed issue where Reaper quest could not proceed by using Double Shear II - Services - Fixed issue where Elin&#39;s upswept hairstyle did not display properly to certain classes - Skill - Lancer : Fixed issue where Adrenaline Rush tooltip stated skill damage increase - Gunner : Fixed issue where blast was shot not out of Arcannon but elsewhere - Brawler : Fixed issue where using Divine Wrath glyphed with Energetic glyph fully filled rage gauge  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 02월 22일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-22/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 서버 안정화 - 던전 플레이 시 발생했던 끊김 및 렉 현상 완화를 위한 안정화 작업이 진행되었습니다. ### 2. Proxy 차단 - Proxy 사용 차단 보완 업데이트가 진행되었습니다. ### [버그수정] - 던전 - 던전 내에서 몬스터의 특정 패턴 대응 시 플레이어의 위치 싱크가 맞지 않는 문제 - 퀘스트 - 알레만시아의 위기 퀘스트 진행 중 NPC 대사의 지역명이 잘못 표기된 문제 - 폭염의 산맥의 슈리안 대항기지에 유레시안 실버레인, 키이나 란 NPC가 존재하지 않는 문제 - 비검사 호위대 승인 퀘스트를 비검 가르기 II로 진행이 불가능한 문제 - 부가서비스 - 엘린 종족의 특정 헤어 올림머리가 일부 클래스에서 깨져 보이는 문제 - 스킬 - 창기사 전투의 의지 I, II 이상상태 툴팁에 스킬 위력 증가 내용이 출력되는 문제 - 마공사의 일반 포탄 스킬 사용 시 포탄이 마공포가 아닌 외부에서 발사되는 문제 - 권술사가 정신의 문장이 적용된 분노의 승천타 스킬 사용 시 분노 게이지가 모두 차는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.08 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-08/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Quest - Revised `Tragedy and Triumph` story quest at Ex Prima to respawn experiment cage while progressing the quest ### Bug fixes - Party - Fixed issue where vote UI for kicking offline players did not display after entering dungeon/battleground - Dungeon - Fixed issue in Antaros&#39; Abyss (nm/hm) where players could not re-enter when defeating final boss and wiping simultaneously - Skill - Fixed issue where summoning shadow as Baraka Warrior did not summon shadow - Item - Cosmetics comment  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 02월 08일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-08/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 퀘스트 - 고대 바라카의 유적터에서 진행하는 &#39;실험실의 비극&#39; 퀘스트 진행 중 실험체 수용소 감옥 창살이 재스폰되도록 개선하였습니다. ### [버그수정] - 파티 - 던전/전장 입장 후, 오프라인 상태인 플레이어 추방 시도 시 추방 투표 UI가 출력되지 않는 문제 - 던전 - 안타로스의 심연(상급/하급) 3네임드 처치와 동시에 파티 전멸 시 3네임드 전투 공간으로 재진입 할 수 없는 문제 - 스킬 - 바라카 검투사로 그림자 분신 스킬 사용 시 그림자가 소환되지 않는 문제 - 아이템 - 11/23(목) 점검 이후 접속 시 소지하고 있던 마도공학회 엘리트 유니폼이 삭제되었던 문제 (오늘 중 우편으로 복구해드릴 예정입니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.01 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-02-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Battleground - Adjusted point scale for Underground Arena - Increased Warrior damage point scale - Increased Lancer technique point scale - Increased Ninja damage point scale - Increased Valkyrie damage point scale - Decreased Sorcerer damage point scale - Decreased Archer damage point scale - Decrased Priest technique point scale ### 2. Dungeon - Pit of Petrax - Revised Petrax HP per class - Reset dungeon rankings accordingly - Antaros&#39; Abyss (hard) - Increased movement speed of 3rd boss after 5 minute time attack - Significantly decreased item, gold, exp earned from monsters for those higher than a certain level limit from the following dungeon - Ebon Tower - Kelsaik&#39;s Nest - Labyrinth of Terror - Sabex Armory - Macellarius Catacombs - Sabex Armory, Macellarius Catacombs - Significantly decreased gold drop amount ### 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 02월 01일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-02-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 전장 - 지하의 격전장 점수 획득 밸런스가 조정됩니다. - 검투사 공격점수 획득비율 상향 - 창기사 테크닉점수 획득비율 상향 - 인술사 공격점수 획득비율 상향 - 월광무사 공격점수 획득비율 상향 - 마법사 공격점수 획득비율 하향 - 궁수 공격점수 획득비율 하향 - 사제 테크닉점수 획득비율 하향 ### 2. 던전 - 페트레 양성소 - 클래스 별 페트레 HP 보정치가 개선됩니다. - 페트레의 HP 보정치가 변경됨에 따라 던전 순위가 초기화 됩니다. - 공허한 안타로스의 심연 - 3네임드 광폭화 시 이동속도가 증가합니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.25 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-25/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Skill and balance - Lancer - Adrenaline Rush - Removed additional 5% damage to monsters effect - Warrior - Blade Waltz - Fixed issue where this skill could not cancel post animation of Torrent of Blows and Battle Cry - Berserker - Crush - Decreased skill damage by 25% - Smash - Decreased skill damage by 25% - Decimate - Decreased skill damage by 25% - Slayer - Colossus Blade - Changed cooldown from 5 minutes to 3 minutes - Piercing Lunge - Changed to definitely crit upon hit - Increased skill damage by 30% - Sorcerer - Meteor Strike - Increased base crit chance by 10% - Changed MP cost from 800 to 750 - Void Pulse - Increased base crit chance by 10% - Changed MP cost from 600 to 550 - Lightning Strike - Changed MP cost from 300 to 250 - Hailstorm - Changed MP cost from 900 to 800 - Gunner - Mana Missile - Increased skill damage by 10% - Time Bomb - Increased skill damage by 10% - HB bomb - Increased base crit chance by 20% - Burst Fire - Increased base crit chance by 15% - Ninja - Burning Heart - Talent : Changed talent condition from `upon critical hit` to `upon hit` - Circle of Steel - Increased skill damage by 20% - Priest - Invocation of Judgement - Changed cooldown from 3 minutes to 2 minutes and 40 seconds - Mystic - Thrall Augmentation - Changed maximum number of players to take effect from summoning thralls to 5 players for all thrall summons - Changed thrall buffs to no longer apply to raid members - Thrall of Sovereignty - Decreased skill damage to players by 30% ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 01월 25일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-25/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 스킬 및 밸런스 - 창기사 - 전투의 의지 - 몬스터 공격 시 공격력 5% 증가 효과가 삭제됩니다. - 검투사 - 이단 검무 - 도발 난무, 충격의 외침 스킬의 사후 모션을 취소시킬 수 없었던 문제가 수정됩니다. - 광전사 - 폭주 : 우수 I - 스킬 위력이 25% 감소합니다. - 폭주 : 좌수 I - 스킬 위력이 25% 감소합니다. - 폭주 : 쌍수 I - 스킬 위력이 25% 감소합니다. - 무사 - 거합 - 재사용 대기시간이 5분에서 3분으로 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.18 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-18/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - New dungeon : Antaros&#39; Abyss - Requires ilvl : 446 - Dungeon entrance : Velika Outskirts - Reward : Emerald, Diamond, high/top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier accessory enchanting material, Mask of Beginning - New dungeon : Antaros&#39; Abyss (hard) - Requires ilvl : 453 - Dungeon entrance : Velika Outskirts - Reward : Mask of Infinity, rare/superior innerwear, Stormcry gear box, Emerald, Diamond, top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier accessory enchanting material - Pit of Petrax - Removed Pit of Petrax shield phases, and changed additional mobs to drop HP motes upon death - Changed some of the other patterns - (Added) Changed daily entry limit from 3 to 2 (additional 1 entry for VIP ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 01월 18일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-18/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 신규: 안타로스의 심연 - 장비 레벨 446 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 벨리카 직할령 &amp;gt; 벨리카 근교 &amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 에메랄드, 다이아몬드, 상위/최상위 장비 강화 재료, 상위 액세서리 강화 재료, 시작의 가면 등을 획득할 수 있습니다. - 신규: 공허한 안타로스의 심연 - 장비 레벨 453 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 벨리카 직할령 &amp;gt; 벨리카 근교 &amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.11 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-11/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Ruinous Manor (hard) - Increased respawn time - This change is made in order to prevent users from resetting after combat and preventing certain mechanics from initiating - Rebel&#39;s Hideout, Rebel&#39;s Hideout (hard) - Revised first boss&#39; in/out pre-explosion effect - Revised obstructions on path to first boss ### 2. Achievement season 8 start - Achievement season 8 which was delayed last week due to an error will now start ### Bug fixes - Dungeon - Fixed issue where background music did not play in Rebel&#39;s Hideout and Rebel&#39;s Hideout (hard) - UI - Fixed issue where Guardian Mission UI displayed outside of Guardian Missions area  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 01월 11일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-11/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 초월한 라켈리스의 폐허 - 라켈리스의 리스폰 시간이 증가합니다. - 전투 시작 후 어그로 초기화 등을 이용하여 일부 패턴이 동작하지 않는 현상 방지 - 삼엄한 혁명단 은거지, 혁명단 은거지 - 카라부스의 원거리/근거리 폭발 스킬 시전 이펙트 가시성이 개선됩니다. - 카라부스로 이동 시 오브젝트로 인해 이동이 불편하던 현상이 개선됩니다. ### 2. 업적 시즌8 시작 - 지난 주 오류로 인해 시작되지 못했던 업적 시즌8 이 시작됩니다. ### [버그수정] - 던전 - 삼엄한 혁명단 은거지, 혁명단 은거지 배경 음악이 나오지 않던 문제 - UI - 수호자 임무 지역을 벗어났음에도 수호자 임무 UI가 출력되는 문제  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.04 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-01-04/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - New : Rebel&#39;s Hideout - Required ilvl for IMS : ilvl 439 - Teleportal is located in Feral Valley, Frontera - Frostmetal gear box, Emerald, Diamond, high/top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier jewelry enchanting material can be obtained - New : Rebel&#39;s Hideout (hard) - Required ilvl for IMS : ilvl 446 - Teleportal is located in Feral Valley, Frontera - Mask of Beginning, Stormcry gear box, Emerald, Diamond, High/top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier jewelry enchanting material can be obtained - Lilith&#39;s Keep (hard) - Increased drop rate of Liquid Metal - Decreased drop rate of Carved Ornament - Copper Clasp will no longer drop - Sky Cruiser Endeavor, Rakelith&#39;s Manor, RK-9 Kennel - Increased drop rate of Hypnotic Device - Decreased drop rate of Archdevan Formula - Artisan&#39;s Tools will no longer drop - Broken Prison - Increased drop rate of Liquid Metal - Decreased drop rate of Carved Ornament, Archdevant Surfactant - Artisan&#39;s Tools will no longer drop - Thaumetal Refinery (hard) - Increased drop rate of Liquid Metal - Decreased drop rate of Carved Ornament - Copper Clasp will no longer drop - Decreased damaged of certain skills for all three bosses - Increased cooldown of certain skills for all three bosses - RK-9 Kennel (hard) - Increased drop rate of Carved Ornament, Otherworldly Shard, Copper Clasp - Liquid Metal, Hypnotic Device, Archdevan Surfactant, Archdevan Formula, Artisan&#39;s Tools will no longer drop - Decreased drop rate of Emerald, Diamond, Elemental Essence - Decreased drop rate of jewelry etchings - Rakelith&#39;s Manor (hard) - Increased drop rate of Archdevan Formula, Otherworldly Shard, Artisan&#39;s Tools - Carved Ornament, Hypnotic Device, Copper Clasp, Archdevan Surfactant, Liquid Metal, Soul Fragment will no longer drop - Decreased drop rate of Elemental Essence - Decreased drop rate of jewelry etchings Developer comment - In accordance to adding new dungeons without retiring old dungeons, rewards for existing dungeons have been adjusted with the addition of new dungeons (Rebel&#39;s Hideout, Rebel&#39;s Hideout (hard)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018년 01월 04일 업데이트 안내</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2018/2018-01-04/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 신규: 혁명단 은거지 - 장비레벨 439 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 판노니아 가드 &amp;gt; 야만의 계곡 &amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 차가운 금속 장비 상자, 에메랄드, 다이아몬드, 상위/최상위 장비 강화 재료, 상위 액세서리 강화 재료 등을 획득할 수 있습니다. - 신규: 삼엄한 혁명단 은거지 - 장비레벨 446 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 판노니아 가드 &amp;gt; 야만의 계곡 &amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.05 patch notes | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2018/2018-07-05/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Level progression reward UI revision - Revised to receive all accumulated rewards at once ### Bug fixes - Skill - Fixed issue where Brawlers could endlessly maintain Rhymthmic Blows buff by repeating Punch, Counter, and Rhythmic Blows - Item - Fixed issue where passive effects on gear occasionally did not work  source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>