<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v85 on tera-mysterium</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v85/</link><description>Recent content in v85 on tera-mysterium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/tags/v85/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2019.07.11 patch notes (v85.05) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-05/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-05/</guid><description>Update 1. Class Priest Zenobia&amp;rsquo;s Vortex Shocking Implosion Increased HP regeneration of Zenobia&amp;rsquo;s Vortex by 2 times during Edict of Judgement Triple Nemesis Adjusted to increase duration of Glyph of Enfeeblement abnormality from 12 seconds to 21 seconds Guardian&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary Changed HP regeneration Changed to casting to be instant instead of having a 1.5 second casting duration Developer comment -사제의 경우, [천벌의 연쇄 – 약화의 문장]의 효과 지속시간이 짧은 관계로 너무 잦은 빈도로 신경 써야만 하는 상황이었습니다.</description></item><item><title>2019.07.04 patch notes (v85.04) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-04/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-04/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon Forsaken Island (hard) (5-Person) Instance matching system can be used starting level 65, at item level 453 and above Costs 150 Adventure Coins, and can be accessed once per day (twice for VIP) Teleportal is located at Cutthroat Harbor Loot table includes Stormcry gear box, Sacred Mallet, Weights, Halidoms/Relics, Naslow&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Map: Right Half, and Intelligence Report: Right Half (Added) 사망 시 부활이 불가능하며, 마지막 보스 몬스터 HP 35% 미만에서만 사제/정령사의 부활 스킬로 부활이 가능합니다.</description></item><item><title>2019.06.27 patch notes (v85.03) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-03/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-03/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon Demokron Factory (normal / hard) Adjusted to reduce HP of bosses 2. Vanguard Initiative Request Added level XP to the following solo content Vanguard Requests : Content The Pit of Petrax Echoes of Aranea Celestial Arena Ace Dungeon : Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Trial Ace Dungeon : Akasha&amp;rsquo;s Trial Ace Dungeon : Baracos&amp;rsquo; Trial Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Naga Battlemasters Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Iron Giants Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Onyx Hydraths Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Bloodbound Teraliths Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Fimbrilisks Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Searing Fangspawns Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Basilisks Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Orisks Island of Dawn : Hunt Brutal Ovoliths 3.</description></item><item><title>2019.06.20 patch notes (v85.02.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-02-01/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-02-01/</guid><description>Update Bug fixes Fixed issue in Gossamer Vault (hard) where certain mechanics could be cancelled Fixed issue where certain Summer Festival event costumes could be used to as fodder for random costume box Fixed issue where Nomadic merchants spawned in all channels Fixed issue where gathering speed for certain gathering nodes was irregular</description></item><item><title>2019.06.13 patch notes (v85.02) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-02/</guid><description>Update 1. Balance Mystic Arunic Release Increased crit chance by 2 times Priest, Mystic Battle Solution Changed effect from increase attack speed to increase crit power Crit power value is the same as other classes Developer comment - 힐러 클래스가 필드 사냥 시 보다 수월하게 플레이 할 수 있도록 공격속도 증가 옵션에서 치명타 위력 증가 옵션으로 변경됩니다. 또한 치명타 위력이 타 클래스와 같은 수준으로 적용되므로 파티 플레이에서 보다 공격적으로 플레이가 가능합니다.</description></item><item><title>2019.06.03 patch notes (v85.01) | TERA KR</title><link>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.github.io/tera-mysterium/en/patch/2019/v85-01/</guid><description>Update 1. Dungeon New : Azart Hatchery (hard) Added a hard mode to existing Azart Hatchery (1-Person) Requires level 65, and can enter as a party (max 5-Person) Can only be accessed by party members of an existing party made before the dimensional portal spawns Entry method is the same as is with existing Azart Hatchery (1-Person), and can receive approximately 1.5 times the experience points Reinforced certain wipe mechanics in Demon&amp;rsquo;s Wheel 2.</description></item></channel></rss>