<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v86 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/tags/v86/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v86 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seraphinush-gaming.com/tags/v86/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.29 patch notes (v86.05) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-05/</guid>
      <description>1. Dungeon  Increased XP reward of level 65 or above Vanguard Request and final boss Increased Joy of Partying effect of Macellarius Catacombs from 1.8 times to 1.9 times  2. Gear (delayed)  Added new superior brooch Agenvant Brooch Can be equipped starting level 69, and active skill applies Agenvant&#39;s Power buff Upon usage, Azart Energy abnormality is applied for 1.5 minutes, and applies an increase of 30 power, 30 crit factor, and 12% attack speed for 20 seconds  3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 29일 업데이트 안내 (v86.05)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-05/</guid>
      <description>1. 던전 (9/5 적용 예정)  65레벨 이상 파티 던전의 발키온 연합 지령서/마지막 네임드 처치 경험치 보상이 상향됩니다. 데모크론 실험실 3인 입장 시 부여되는 성장의 즐거움 효과가 상향됩니다. (1.8배 → 1.9배)  2. 장비 (9/5 적용 예정)  신규 전설등급 브로치인 &amp;lsquo;맹렬한 아젠반트의 브로치&#39;와 &amp;lsquo;찬란한 아젠반트의 브로치&#39;가 추가됩니다. 69레벨부터 착용이 가능하며, 스킬 숏컷에 등록하여 &amp;lsquo;아젠반트의 힘&amp;rsquo; 버프를 발동시킬 수 있습니다.  사용 시, 아르가프의 힘 이상상태가 1분 30초 부여되며, 20초 동안 힘 30, 치명타 유발 30, 공격 속도가 12% 향상됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.22 patch notes (v86.04) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-04/</guid>
      <description>1. Field boss monster  Machnak, Avion, Royal Gossamer reopens Changed Royal Gossamer to spawn only in channel 1 Switched last hit reward and jackpot reward  Last hit reward will remain the same to receive both jackpot reward and contribution reward Jackpot reward is randomly given to one participant who has made significant contribution  Boss | last hit reward | jackpot reward  Ortan | Ortan Field Boss Gold Box | Ortan&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Hazard | Hazard Field Boss Gold Box | Hazard&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Cerrus | Cerrus Field Boss Gold Box | Cerrus&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Machnak | Machnak Field Boss Gold Box | Machnak&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest Avion | Avion Field Boss Gold Box | Avion&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest       New field boss Agenvant update is delayed until 08/29 (Thurs)  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 22일 업데이트 안내 (v86.04)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-04/</guid>
      <description>1. 필드 보스 몬스터  마흐나크, 아비온, 로열 파르프 컨텐츠가 재오픈됩니다. 로열 파르프가 1채널에서만 스폰되도록 변경됩니다. 마지막 타격, 대박 보상으로 지급되는 아이템이 서로 변경됩니다.  마지막 타격 보상은 기존과 동일하게 대박 보상 또는 참여 보상과 중복 획득이 가능합니다. 대박 보상은 참여 인원 중 랜덤한 1명에게 지급되며, 처치 기여도가 낮을 경우 추첨 대상에서 제외됩니다.  보스 몬스터 | 마지막 타격 보상 | 대박 보상  오르탄 | 오르탄 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 오르탄의 보물상자 하자르 | 하자르 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 하자르의 보물상자 캘로스 | 캘로스 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 캘로스의 보물상자 마흐나크 | 마흐나크 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 마흐나크의 보물상자 아비온 | 아비온 공격대의 금빛 상자 | 아비온의 보물상자       신규 필드보스: 아젠반트의 업데이트가 8/29(목)으로 연기되었습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.14 patch notes (v86.03.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Exodor  Increased channel count to 3 Temporarily disabled spawn of Royal Parf, Machnak, and Avion  There was an issue where reward was delivered twice; content will reopen as it is fixed    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where reward parcel message for defeating Machnak was awkward Fixed issue where Jump Platforms on outer islands did not operate Fixed issue where Skill Advance data reset after 07/23 maintenance, and items to restore Skill Advance have been sent Skill Advance XP, scrolls, and gems for gold have will be distributed soon   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 14일 업데이트 안내 (v86.03.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03-01/</guid>
      <description>###1. 엑소도르
 채널이 3개로 증가됩니다. 로열 파르프, 마흐나크, 아비온 컨텐츠가 임시 중단됩니다.  특정 상황에서 보상을 중복으로 획득할 수 있는 문제가 확인되어 임시 중단되었으며, 수정 후 재오픈할 수 있도록 하겠습니다. 불편을 드려 죄송합니다.    [버그수정]  마흐나크 처치 보상 우편 문구가 어색한 문제 엑소도르 지역 외곽섬에서 간헐적으로 점프기어를 이용할 수 없는 문제 7/23(화) 점검 이후 초기화된 스킬 연마 정보를 복구할 수 있는 아이템이 지급됩니다. 스킬 연마 경험치, 스크롤, 골드에 상응하는 보석 아이템이 지급될 예정이며, 자세한 내용은 공지사항을 통해 확인해 주시기를 바랍니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.08 patch notes (v86.03) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-03/</guid>
      <description>1. Field boss  New : Avion  Spawns south of Vernark Fortress, Exodor (channel 1)  Island can be accessed through Argaff Jump Platforms   Upon defeating Avion, the player dealing the last hit will receive one of the following rewards :  Avion Treasure Box (1 of the following items) :  Shining Avion Mask Fierce Avion Mask   One random participant will also receive the following reward :  Reward  Avion Raid Gold Box     The following contribution reward will be distributed depending on the amount of damage dealt  Damage contribution is party-based No reward will be distributed to players who have not contributed enough to defeat the boss  Reward  Avion Raid Silver Box Avion Raid Box Avion&amp;rsquo;s Dranium Piece           (Fixed) Changed field boss content reward distribution to parcel  As per fix, Machnak and Royal Parf    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 08일 업데이트 안내 (v86.03)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-03/</guid>
      <description>1. 필드 보스  신규: 아비온  엑소도르 &amp;lsquo;베르아크 성채&amp;rsquo; 남동쪽의 &amp;lsquo;아르가프 침공지&amp;rsquo; 섬지역에 출몰합니다. (1채널)  아르가프 도약대를 이용하여 진입할 수 있습니다.   아비온 처치 시, 마지막 타격을 가한 캐릭터에게 아래와 같은 보상이 지급됩니다.  아비온의 보물상자 (하기 아이템 중 1종 획득)  찬란한 아비온의 가면 맹렬한 아비온의 가면     참여한 캐릭터 중 1명에게 참여보상 대신 아래와 같은 보상이 지급됩니다.  보상 아이템  아비온 공격대의 금빛 상자     필드보스 HP 감소 기여도에 따라 아래와 같은 참여 보상이 차등 지급됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.08.01 patch notes (v86.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-02/</guid>
      <description>1. Argaff&amp;rsquo;s Hatchery  Increased spawn rate of Nomadic Caimans and Dimensional Portal  2. Field Boss Monster  Reinforced criteria for earning wnd rank participation reward  3. Quest  Changed Card Index completion progress reward  Removed progression stage reward for completing Big Horn Argaff card set    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where Skill Advance points and Skill Advance state reset (to zero) Fixed issue where sorting inventory occasionally causes client to crash Fixed issue where using skill that reduce damage caused PC to decrease in defense (fixed Bamarama issue as well) Fixed issue where Slayer&amp;rsquo;s Measured Slice was coded as magical damage Fixed issue where Ninja&amp;rsquo;s Boomerang Shuriken&amp;rsquo;s skill damage was unexpectedly high Fixed issue where recent transactions on trade broker displayed irregular item levels Fixed issue where UI scaling did not affect pop-up UI for purchasing items Fixed issue where changing party or raid while fighting field boss monster resulted in rewarded twice the participation reward Fixed issue where participation reward was distributed for defeating Ortan, Cerrus, and Hazard to players who did not participate directly but had party/raid members who did Fixed issue where rewards for a different class was distributed for defeating Ortan, Cerrus, and Hazard Fixed issue where Partners occasionally spoke about item level Fixed issue where players could proceed through without being directed by quest NPC Fixed issue where certain NPCs were stacked Fixed issue where Nomadic Merchants could spawn in all channels Fixed issue where players could receive multiple quest items through Etching Crafting tutorial Fixed issue where items with expire dates had their extended expire dates reset to their issue dates when placed in bank Fixed issue where cracked ground aesthetics for Machnak combat area seemed like it was floating Fixed issue where returning player items displayed different expire date and stats than intended Fixed issue where Map and Intel pieces in Guild Bank did not disappear event after their expire dates have passed Fixed issue where summoned Partners displayed a chat upon spawning in each area Fixed a K TERA exclusive issue Fixed issue where using a skill in Velika: Civil Unrest causes self-damage   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 08월 01일 업데이트 안내 (v86.02)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-02/</guid>
      <description>1. 아르가프 부화장  떠돌이 시누스와 차원문의 스폰 확률이 상향됩니다.  2. 필드 보스 몬스터  참여 보상 중, 2등급 보상(ex: 마흐나크 공격대의 상자)을 얻을 수 있는 기준이 완화됩니다.  3. 퀘스트  도감 편찬 퀘스트의 진행 단계가 일부 변경됩니다.  &amp;lsquo;큰 뿔 아르가스&amp;rsquo; 카드를 도감에 등록하는 단계가 제거됩니다.    [버그수정]  업데이트 이후 스킬 연마 포인트 및 연마 상태가 초기화된 문제 자동정렬 기능 사용 시 간헐적으로 서버가 다운되는 문제 데미지 감소 스킬 사용 시, PC의 방어력이 감소되는 문제 (임시 중단되었던 투기장이 정상화 되었습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.07.25 patch notes (v86.01.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Exodor  Increased channel count in all Exodor regions except Core region Added sub-title Butterfly Signal Distractor to two of the monsters  2. Quest  K TERA exclusive comment  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where Baramara BAMs did not fight one another Fixed issue where zone quest did not count while completing dungeon as a raid Fixed issue in Verark Fortress where certain 2nd boss mechanic caused client to crash Fixed issue in Verark Fortress where players could mount flying mounts in combat arena Fixed issue where certain NPC for Exodor story quest was placed twice Fixed issue where defeating quest monster before talking to Jalena preventing quest progress Fixed issue where completing Gathering Effect in Index UI prevented changing tabs Fixed issue where a certain monster&amp;rsquo;s effects did not display properly Fixed issue where spawn rate of Dimensional Portal upon defeating Nomadic Caimans was unexpectedly high during party status Fixed issue where 2019 summer event items displayed faulty expiration date Fixed issue where system message upon trying to inspect a logged out character had a typo   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 07월 25일 업데이트 안내 (v86.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 엑소도르  코어 지역을 제외하고 엑소도르 지역의 채널이 최대 3개로 증가합니다. 엑소도르 지역 &amp;lsquo;붉은 이끼게&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;외눈가시&amp;rsquo; 네임드 몬스터의 호칭으로 &amp;lsquo;나비 귀환지의 방해꾼&#39;이 추가됩니다.  2. 퀘스트  6/20 ~ 7/25 기간 진행 된 신규/복귀 이벤트의 &amp;lsquo;의뢰서 – 아르보레아 전선 돌파 I&amp;rsquo; 퀘스트 조건이 변경됩니다.  시험의 던전 – 황금의 미궁 2회 클리어 -&amp;gt; 천공의 경기장 2회 클리어    [버그수정]  투기장에서 몬스터가 서로 전투를 하지 않는 문제 녹슬지 않는 실력 1 퀘스트에서 공격대 상태로 몬스터 처치 시 카운팅되지 않는 문제 베르아크 성채 비밀지역 2네임드 특정 스킬 사용 시, 간헐적으로 클라이언트 크래시가 발생하는 문제 베르아크 성채 비밀지역 전투 공간에서 비행 탈 것 탑승이 가능한 문제 엑소도르 퀘스트 중 일부 퀘스트에서 NPC가 중복 배치되는 문제 코어 폭파 퀘스트 진행 중, 쟈넬라 NPC와 대화하기 전 칼리가르 몬스터 처치 시 진행이 불가능한 문제 수집 효과 UI에서 카드 완성 시, 탭이 넘어가지 않는 문제 뼈아귀 괴물의 이펙트가 출력되지 않는 문제 차원문, 소환된 파르프 등 몬스터 처치 시 스폰되는 NPC가 파티 상태에서 스폰 확률이 비정상적으로 증가하는 문제 2019 썸머 이벤트 아이템 툴팁의 삭제 일자가 잘못 기재되어 있는 문제 로그아웃 한 캐릭터를 살펴보기 했을 시 출력되는 안내 메시지에 오타가 있는 문제   source : TERA 테라 | NEXON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019.07.23 patch notes (v86.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/translations/2019/v86-01/</guid>
      <description>1. Zone expansion  Expanded floating island “Exodor” zone  A new story quest is obtained from NPC 에키오르 라펠레이트 upon completing [Important] Bringing Down Exodor story quest Said NPC is located at Spring Valley Exodor consists of four regions :  Garden Ranch Viridian Wetland Verark Fortress      2. Dungeon  New : Vernark Fortress (5-man)  Instance Matching System can be accessed upon reaching level 69, and item level 458 Requires 385 Aventure Coins to enter, and is limited to 40 entries (80 for Elite) per week Teleportal is located on the upper floor of Verark Fortress, Exodor   Added Skill Advance XP reward to the following 12 dungeons  Dungeon :  Rakelith&amp;rsquo;s Manor (normal/hard) RK-9 Kennel (normal/hard) Velik&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary (normal/hard) Grotto of Lost Souls (normal/hard) Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (normal/hard) Forsaken Island Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum     Ghillieglade  Changed starting location to the front of the bridge   Red Refuge  Added a dungeon-specific weapon design  Argog Weapon  Can be obtained as weapon skin box, or by combining Refined Metal (가공된 광물) and Argog&amp;rsquo;s Toenail obtained upon defeating Argog       Ace dungeon  Changed level appropriately, and adjusted reward accordingly  Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Trial : ilvl 431 Akasha&amp;rsquo;s Trial : ilvl 412 to ilvl 439 Baracos&amp;rsquo; Trial : ilvl 412 to ilvl 446   Adjusted to increased Golden Talent and Silver Talent Added to apply a movement speed buff through all Ace dungeons Increased elevator speed in Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Trial   Celestial Arena  Changed total stage count (from 7 to 5) Changed monster HP, and revised to move to the next stage faster upon defeating all monsters Adjusted to increase Golden Talent/Daric/Plate and Silver Talent/Daric/Plate reward Changed item level appropriately (from 412 to 439) Significantly increased audience cheer buff   Adjusted to increase the enchanting material reward of the following dungeons :  Ravenous Gorge Channelworks Velik&amp;rsquo;s Hold Thaumetal Refinery Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Keep    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019년 07월 23일 업데이트 안내 (v86.01)</title>
      <link>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seraphinush-gaming.com/posts/patch-notes/raw/2019/v86-01/</guid>
      <description>1. 지역 확장  공중섬 &amp;lsquo;엑소도르&amp;rsquo; 지역이 확장됩니다.  &amp;lsquo;[중요] 격추 시도&amp;rsquo; 퀘스트 완료 및 68레벨 달성 시, &amp;lsquo;에키오르 라펠레이트&amp;rsquo; NPC를 통해 &amp;lsquo;엑소도르로 가는 길&amp;rsquo; 미션 퀘스트를 수주하여 진입할 수 있습니다. 에키오르 라펠레이트 NPC는 바라카니아 구릉지&amp;gt;바라카니아 경제인 연합에 위치합니다. &amp;lsquo;엑소도르&#39;는 아래 4가지 지역으로 구성되어 있습니다.  로가쉬의 장원 엑소도르의 대농장 비리디안 습지대 베르아크 성채      2. 던전  신규: 베르아크 성채 비밀지역 (5인)  69레벨, 장비레벨 458 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>