<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v61 on mysterium</title>
    <link>/mysterium/tags/v61/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v61 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/mysterium/tags/v61/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2017.08.03 patch notes (v61.02.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-02-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Decreased difficulty of Alpha Cyrux Research Facility - Decreased damage of certain skills for each boss - Increased stun duration of 1st boss after tackling tree - Decreased penalty/damage of explosive goblins during 3rd boss Developer comment (paraphrased; point form) - Too many players were trying to take advantage of the market by obtaining tradeable items from Token/Mark of Change and eventually trading gold for real money so they changed items to be untradeable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 08월 03일 업데이트 안내 (v61.02.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-02-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 알파 사이럭스 연구 기지 난이도가 하향됩니다. - 각 네임드가 사용하는 일부 스킬의 데미지가 하향됩니다. - 1네임드가 나무에 머리를 박았을 때 걸리는 스턴의 지속 시간이 늘어납니다. - 3네임드 전투 시 등장하는 고블린이 자폭할 때 주는 패널티가 감소합니다. § 개발자 코멘트 &#39;변화의 잔재&#39;는 수호자님들이 기존 장비 성장 구조에서 획득한 아이템의 가치를 보존해드리기 위한 시스템이며, 부차적으로는 구 장비를 마저 강화/제작하길 원하는 수호자님들이 어려움을 겪지 않도록 보조해드리기 위하여 도입하였습니다. 그러나 아래와 같은 상황이 확인되어 대응을 진행하게 되었습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017.07.27 patch notes (v61.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - New dungeon : Hangar RK-9 - ilvl required : 439 - Portal location : Spring Valley - Items obtainable : High-tier encahnting box, Dark mind-control device, Arch Devan artisan tool, etc. - New dungeon : Alpha Cyrux Research Facility (hard mode) - ilvl required : 439 - Portal location : Savage Reach - Items obtainable : High-tier encahnting box, Unknown liquid metal, Blood-soaked metal, etc. ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 07월 27일 업데이트 안내 (v61.02)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 신규: RK-9 격납고 - 상위 던전인 RK-9 격납고가 추가됩니다. - 장비 레벨 439 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 바라카니아 &amp;gt; 바라카니아 경제인 연합 &amp;gt; 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다. - 상급 강화 재료 상자, 어둠이 깃든 정신 지배 장치, 아크데바 장인의 강화 도구 등을 획득할 수 있습니다. - 신규: 알파 사이럭스 연구 기지 - 상위 던전인 알파 사이럭스 연구 기지가 추가됩니다. - 장비 레벨 439 달성 시 파티매칭을 통해 입장할 수 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017.07.20 patch notes (v61.01.02) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-01-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Dungeon - Sky Cruiser Endeavor - Decreased the HP of mobs for 1st boss - Significantly decreased the HP of 2nd and 3rd boss - Nightmare Lilith&#39;s Keep - Significantly decreased the HP of 1st, 2nd, and 3rd boss - Harrowhold - Reoponed 20-man raid Harrowhold - Teleportal is located at Velika Outskirts - Harrowhold does not support IMS - Harrowhold proceeds through 4 phases, rewarding loot per phase - (same conditions apply to looting) Reward change comment - Despite our intention for unskilled new and returning players to be self-sufficient through solo contents, it seems as though players were forced to harvest enchanting materials from multiple characters for one character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 07월 20일 업데이트 안내 (v61.01.02)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-01-02/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 던전 - 엘카라스 호 - 1네임드 일반 몬스터의 HP가 하향 조정됩니다. - 2~3네임드의 HP가 대폭 하향 조정됩니다. - 악녀 릴리스의 성 - 1~3네임드의 HP가 대폭 하향 조정됩니다. - 파괴된 신계의 관문 - 20인 공격대 던전인 파괴된 신계의 관문이 재오픈 됩니다. - 벨리카 근교에 위치한 차원의 마법석을 통해 입장하실 수 있습니다. - 파괴된 신계의 관문은 서버간 파티매칭을 지원하지 않습니다. - 파괴된 신계의 관문은 총 4단계에 걸쳐 진행되며, 각 단계 클리어 시 보상이 지급됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 07월 14일 업데이트 안내 (v61.01.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-01-01/</guid>
      <description>### [버그수정] - 아이템 - 영구제 아이템을 특정 경로로 획득 시 소실되는 문제 - 소실된 아이템에 대해서는 07/20(목) 점검 시 재지급 해드릴 예정입니다. - 던전 - 릴리스의 성 3네임드의 HP가 비정상적으로 낮은 문제 - 사이럭스 연구 기지 1네임드와 전투 중 소환되는 나무를, 패턴 무시 후 처치할 수 있는 문제 - 사이럭스 연구 기지 1네임드와 전투 중 소환되는 나무가 간헐적으로 이동하는 문제 - 장비 성장 시스템 - 명품,각성화 되지 않은 일반 매혹/냉혈 장비 10강 이상에서 승계 시 9강화 이상을 보존해 주지 않는 문제 – [고객센터] 로 문의 접수 해주시면, 도와드리겠습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017.07.13 patch notes (v61.01) | K TERA</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/translations/2017/v61-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. Gear progression system - Changed enchantment method of all gear to material enchanting method - Enchanting will proceed not using Feedstock/Alkahest but a different material depending on gear - Removed same gear enchanting system - Added gear upgrade system - UI can be displayed by pressing Shift + T - Fully enchanted gear can be upgraded to +0 enchantment gear of the next tier - Upgrading will proceed by consuming specified material as it is with enchanting - Gear rolls, etching, crystal/dyads, dual option reset upon upgrading - Accessories can also be upgraded - Added gear proficiency system - Proficiency can be obtained through Vanguard Initiative quests - Higher the proficiency, higher the chance of success for enchanting and upgrading - While you can obtain more than the maximum proficiency, the amount of proficiency actually consumed upon enchanting/upgrading is less than the cap, and the chance of success is reinforced up to its max - Changed rerollable system - Can freely select desired options for the first time upon upgrading gear/accessory - Spellbind, Master Enigmatic Scroll/Intricate Identification Scroll and related items are no longer usable - Semi-Enigmatic Scrolls are now used to change all gear rolls - Amount of SES consumed varies depending on the type of options selected - Semi-Enigmatic Scrolls are required to change dual options - Exist dismantling function is removed, and exchanged with a revamped dismantling function - Can be used in the same way as before through the &#39;dismantle&#39; icon through inventory - New enchanting materials can be obtained dismantling old enchanting materials - Removed masterworking system - Removed awakening system - Old gear can still use old enchanting materials to enchant - Old enchanting materials can no longer be obtained from boxes (Premiere Box) - New enchanting materials now replace old enchanting materials from existing boxes (Premiere Box) ### 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017년 07월 13일 업데이트 안내 (v61.01)</title>
      <link>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mysterium/posts/patch-notes/raw/2017/v61-01/</guid>
      <description>### 1. 장비 성장 시스템 - 모든 장비의 강화 방식을 재료 강화 방식으로 변경됩니다. - 강화석/강화제를 통해 강화하는 것이 아닌 장비 종류에 따라 재료를 소모하여 강화를 진행하게 됩니다. - 동일 장비 강화 시스템이 삭제됩니다. - 장비 승급 시스템이 추가됩니다. - Shift+T 버튼 단축키로 호출이 가능합니다. - 최대 강화된 장비를 다음 위상의 +0 강화 장비로 승급할 수 있습니다. - 강화와 같이 승급을 위한 특정 재료를 소모하여 진행하게 됩니다. - 장비 승급 시 옵션, 각인서, 크리스탈/아티팩트, 듀얼 옵션이 초기화됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>