<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v106 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v106/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v106 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/tags/v106/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.05.20 patch notes (v106.02.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Event  Changed Undying Warlord and Tyrant cosmetic items received from event, including ones already received, to no longer be able to dismantle  **3.*8 Services  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.     아이템명 가격(블루) 판매 시작일 판매 종료일     [랜덤] 반짝반짝 황금빛 코이노보리 상자 55 2021-05-18 00:00 2021-06-09 점검 전   [랜덤] 흩날리며 타오르는 꽃의 유카타 상자 40 2021-05-18 00:00 2021-06-09 점검 전   [랜덤] 돌아온 태양신 발더의 무기 상자(10+1) 400 2021-05-21 00:00 2021-06-02 점검 전   [랜덤] 돌아온 태양신 발더의 무기 상자 40 2021-05-21 00:00 2021-06-02 점검 전    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where select box items with time duration could be duplicated Fixed issue where Multi-Nostrum added on Monthly Pass was displayed in PC Bang benefits  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.05.12 patch notes (v106.02) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Item  Changed item properties of superior Halidom / Relic  Cannot be stored in storage -&amp;gt; can be stored in storage Bind of pickup -&amp;gt; bind on equip    3. TERA Pass  Revised to update TERA Pass UI upon using TERA Pass item while UI is open  4. Services  테라샵에서 아래의 아이템이 판매됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.05.06 patch notes (v106.01.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  Proceeded with structural stabilization work to minimization server instability  2. Non-migrated account data deletion  2021년 4월 30일까지 이관하지 않은 계정의 데이터를 삭제 처리하는 작업을 진행합니다.  2021년 4월 30일까지 이관하지 않은 계정 정보는 모두 삭제되며 계정 정보 복구가 불가합니다. 2021년 4월 30일까지 이관하지 않은 계정 정보는 추가 이관 또는 수동 이관 지원이 불가합니다. 2021년 5월 6일 정기점검 이후 미이관 계정에 포함된 캐릭터 이름은 재사용할 수 있으며, 게임 내 컨텐츠에 삭제된 캐릭터 이름이 등록되어 있을 경우 “다른 차원의 수호자”로 표기됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021.04.28 patch notes (v106.01) | TERA KR</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2021/v106-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Battleground  Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold  Tanks  Adjusted to increase damage Adjusted to increase HP Adjusted to increase movement speed   Sieges  Adjusted to increase damage Adjusted to increase HP   Platform-based sieges  Increased damage range to reach Outer Gates Adjusted to increase damage to Gates Adjusted to decrease HP   Ships  Adjusted to increase HP   Fraywind Canyon  Adjusted to decrease maximum number of healers from 5 to 3   Added skill effect to equalized gear distribution Brooch  Revised to be able to register in a skill slot Added skill to disable abnormalities (3 minute cooldown)      2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>