<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018 on mysterium</title>
    <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018 on mysterium</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 patch summary</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/summary/</guid>
      <description>January   v68.01
 New dungeon : Red Refuge New dungeon : Red Refuge (hard) New equipment : Mask New accessory : Onset Mask, Infinity Mask Class balance (Berserker, Priest, Lancer) New open world : Essence of Life (Island of Dawn)    v68.01.01
  v69.01
 New dungeon : Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss New dungeon : Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) New feature : Leaderboard New gear : Heroic Oath New battleground : Gridiron Class balance (Valkyrie) Account : Max character slot expansion (19 -&amp;gt; 20)    v69.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.27 patch notes | TERA KR (v80.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v80-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v80-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Achievement  Added first level 70 achievement for each class  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where XP gained from goblin thieves was higher than intended Fixed issue where XP bar UI did not display up to two decimal places 월간 패스 일일 T-cat 주머니 쿨타임이 게임 미접속 시 적용되지 않는 문제  (*월간 패스 T-cat 주머니 쿨타임 오류 보상은 확정 시 안내드릴 예정입니다.)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.22 patch notes | TERA KR (v80.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v80-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v80-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Balance  Adjusted to increase XP on ilvl 412-456 dungeon bosses  Changed XP ranges differently per dungeon   Decreased XP required to level up between level 66-70  Developer comment - First off we increased XP earned through dungeons by 3 times through this maintenance. - The XP gain has been adjusted using difficulty and clear time as basis, and therefore each each dungeon provides a different amount of XP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.20 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.05.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-05-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-05-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Level cap expansion  Increased level cap to level 70 Added new story quest Break of Nightmare  Can progress post-Awakening   Adjusted required XP for levels 58 to 65 Adjusted XP rewarded from monsters level 58 and above, quest, and Vanguard Request New : Skill Advancement system  Players can now use Skill Advancement and Option Unlock Skill Advancement  Players can use Skill Advancement upon reaching levels 66, 68, 70 Skill Advancement requires Skill Advancement Scroll I, II, III and gold to improve skills   Option Unlock  Players can unlock options upon reaching levels 67, 69 Each (unlockable) skill has 3 options, and requires Skill Optimization Scroll I, II and gold to unlock   Options can be selected / changed out of combat  Skill Advancement Scroll, Skill Optimization Scroll can be changed :         Item Material Amount Result Amount     Skill Advancement Scroll I Skill Advancement Scroll I 7 Skill Advancement Scroll III 1   Skill Optimization Scroll I Skill Optimization Scroll I 3 Skill Advancement Scroll III 1   Skill Advancement Scroll II Skill Advancement Scroll II 7 Skill Advancement Scroll III 1   Skill Optimization Scroll II Skill Optimization Scroll II 3 Skill Advancement Scroll III 1     Achievement  Started achievement season 10 Added 1 level-related achievement  Level 70   Added 11 Skill Advancement-related achievements  Accessed Skill Optimization Optimized 2 Skills Optimized 4 Skills Optimized 6 Skills Advanced a Skill Advanced a skill 30 times Advanced a skill 60 times Advanced a skill 90 times Advanced a skill 120 times Advanced a skill 150 times Advanced a skill 180 times   Added Talent-related achievements  Achievement : Stagnant Water  Spent 500 EP       Credit Faction  Added 3 new Reputation Factions  Anti-Amber Operations I Anti-Amber Operations II Anti-Amber Operations III      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.13 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.05.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-05-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-05-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Balance (added)  Slayer  Changed to reset cooldown of Overhand Strike to 0 upon using In Cold Blood    2. Wintera Snowfield  Applies equalized gear in this battleground Changed round specific system message  3. Miscellaneous  Changed Travel Journal limit to 10 locations  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where deactivating Noctenium Infusion in dungeons did not work properly Fixed issue where Valkyrie&amp;rsquo;s Godsfall skill did not receive chain effect from Gungnir&amp;rsquo;s Bite Fixed issue where during Reaper&amp;rsquo;s Shadow Reaping, Grim Strike&amp;rsquo;s Glyph of Persistence&amp;rsquo;s system message did not display the skill&amp;rsquo;s name in its message Fixed issue where Wintera Snowfield description did not include win condition upon timeout to be dependent on number of team players remaining Fixed issue where Slayer&amp;rsquo;s Startling Kick - Empowered Speed talent did not display its activation requirement properly Fixed issue where Reaper&amp;rsquo;s Death Spiral - Empowered Speed talent did not display its activation requirement properly  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.12.06 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.05)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-05/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Wintera Snowfield  Added a shrinking snowstorm area  Snowstorm area induces 5,000 damage per second   Changed to single round instance  Winning condition is to defeat all enemy players   Added relevant Vanguard Request  Vanguard Request  It&amp;rsquo;s Time for Wintera Snowfield!  Gold: 100 talentXP: 1215 itemXP: 1650     Optional  It&amp;rsquo;s Time for Wintera Snowfield!  Gold: 100 talentXP: 1215       The following denotes win and loss rewards :  Win reward  40 Wintera Token 216,000 BC   Loss reward  20 Wintera Token 72,000 BC   Wintera Token Shop       Type Reward Token cost     Enchanting materials Archdevan Surfactant 400    Elemental Essence 1650    Veilthroch 3600    Otherworldly Shard 1100    Devil&amp;rsquo;s Claw 360    Dragon Skill 360   Consumables Fireworks Set 20    Dragon Firework 40    Green Wintera Scarf 100    Yellow Wintera Scarf 100    Blue Wintera Scarf 100    Red Wintera Scarf 100    [Event] Bravery Potion II 100    [Event] Lamb Bulgogi 200    [Event] Rejuvenation Elixir 300    EP Reset Potion 1000   Special [Event] Frost Mantle of Indifference 2000    [Event] Wintersilk Dress Box (14 days) 3000    Snowflake Firework (30 days) 4000    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.29 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.03.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-03-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. UI  Revised Monster HP Bar enrage information  Revised to display the amount of enrage time remaining    Bug fixes  Fixed issue where cancelling Slayer&amp;rsquo;s Whirlwind with Overhand Strike had discrepancies in cancelling time due at different skill levels Fixed issue where Valkyries could not iframe debuff-type skills Fixed issue where Reaper&amp;rsquo;s Retribution tooltip was insufficient to explain &amp;lsquo;cannot use Retribution against projectiles in PvP&amp;rsquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.22 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.03)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-03/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Balance  Mystic  Thrall of Life  Revised to increase speed of summoner recognition  Changed to use area of effect cleanse and healing skill immediately after summoning regardless of the distance between thrall and summoner Slightly increased casting speed of area of effect cleanse and area of effect heal used after being summoned Changed the maximum distance from summoner before attempting to move towards the summoner from 5m to 20m        Developer comment - 소환 직후 시전자와 생명의 정령의 거리가 멀어질 경우, 스킬을 사용하지 않고 시전자만 따라다니던 문제를 수정하여 스킬의 활용성을 개선하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.15 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Shadow Sanguinary (hard)  Gear requirement : ilvl 446 Teleportal location : Highwatch Outskirts Potential reward : Onset Mask, top-tier enchanting material, transparent accessories (mask, back), etc. Added appropriate Guild Quest   Shadow Sanguinary  Gear requirement : ilvl 439 Teleportal location : Highwatch Outskirts Potential reward, high-tier enchanting material, transparent accessories, etc. Added appropriate Guild Quest   Velik&amp;rsquo;s Sanctuary (hard)  Gear requirement : ilvl 453 Teleportal location : Velika Potential require : Infinity Mask, top-tier enchanting material, crafting additive I, transparent accessories, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.08 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Reward  Added rewards to Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard)  Slightly increased the drop amount of Scavenged Supplies upon defeating Nightmare Antaroth Added Dragon Skull to loot table    Developer comment - 공허한 안타로스의 심연 보상효율이 다른 453던전에 비해 부족한 것으로 판단되어 보상을 추가하였습니다.  Added new &amp;lsquo;Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Mask&amp;rsquo; to replace &amp;lsquo;Transcendent Mask&amp;rsquo; in Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum  Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Mask  Upper tier item that has one static line and 3 random static lines (can have the same stat)     Fixed field / dungeon item drop during level progression  Decreased gold rate rate while increasing drop amount Removed gold drop from dungeons Decreased crystal drop rate in field/dungeon    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.11.01 patch notes | TERA KR (v79.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v79-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Balance  Changed all class&amp;rsquo; base Endurance to 80, class-specific stats, and defense stats on gear Berserker  Lethal Strike  Increased skill damage by 15% Decreased PvP skill damage by 30% Decreased the additional damage received as player&amp;rsquo;s HP decreases Increased MP cost from 0 to 300   Thunder Strike  Adjusted Popori&amp;rsquo;s hit point relative to the hit point of other race   Combo Attack  Adjusted all race&amp;rsquo;s hit point relative to race Elin&amp;rsquo;s hit point   Leaping Strike  Fixed issue where Leaping Strike could cancel Cyclone   Cyclone  Adjusted to apply stagger to other players without pulling them in if overcharged   Triumphant Shout  Changed immunity effect duration from 6 seconds to 5 seconds   Fearsome Shout  Changed to be removable by cleanse   Unleash  Changed to be able to cancel with Regression/Plague of Exhaustion      Developer comment - 광전사의 경우 던전 일반 파티에서의 효율에 비해 필사의 일격을 활용하는 파티의 구성원일 경우 효율이 매우 높은 문제를 확인하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.25 patch notes | TERA KR (v78.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  New : Training Ground  Can be accessed in Highwatch Can fight against a specified BAM to measure DPS and freely practice without entry limit    2. Security update  Updated security program  3. Elin Gunner / Brawler  Can now use Race Change Voucher to race Elin  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where Dark Harvest allowed Reapers to clip through walls Fixed issue where using Heart Thrust did not display skill name in system message Fixed issue where Cultist&amp;rsquo;s Weapon Chest was rendered as weed in Cultist&amp;rsquo;s Refuge  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.18 patch notes | TERA KR (v78.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Adjusted balance of Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum  Decreased damage of 2nd phase Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Fury Swipes during enrage Added Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest as reward  Spawns at 2nd phase area after completing 1st phase Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Treasure Chest contains the following :  Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Amplifier Coin can be exchanged for Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Handwear Amplifier or Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Footwear Amplifier  Drop table (chance to drop) :  Supreme Metal Springy Draco Limb Weight Pendulum Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Amplifier Token Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Handwear Amplifier Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Footwear Amplifier           성장 구간 던전에서 클래스 상관 없이 매칭 수락 팝업창이 매칭 30초뒤 팝업되도록 변경됩니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.11 patch notes | TERA KR (v78.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Temporarily closed Dreadspire, Harrowhold  Removed Dreadspire from Leaderboard    2. Item  Brooch promotion  Marrow Brooch can now be promoted to Dracoloth Brooch Quatrefoil Brooch can now be promoted to Powerful Goddess&amp;rsquo;s Brooch Cost for promotion [for both brooch] is the following :    | Item XP | 1 attempt material | 1 attempt amount | Gold | | 158994 | Silver Talent | 85 | 9114 | || Scavenged Supplies | 39 || || Devil&amp;rsquo;s Claws | 8 || || Dragon Skull | 8 || || Diamond | 3 ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.10.04 patch notes | TERA KR (v78.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v78-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Quest  Added new quest at Highwatch to be received from Marmundam  Can receive at ilvl 439, and can complete once per day per character Reward :       Item Amount     Liquid Metal 6   Hypnotic Device 4   Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools 3   Copper Clasp 2   Pansophic Ash 1   Archdevan Formula 4   Carved Ornament 2   Scavenged Supplies 1    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.09.20 patch notes | TERA KR (v77.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v77-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v77-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Balance (added Developer comment)  Slayer  Added chains to use [Whirlwind], [Heart Thrust], and [Knockdown Strike] after Savage Strike Changed chance to proc Aggression talent level 1 to level 20 from [22-34%] to [22-60%]    Developer comment - 무사의 경우 괴력 특성의 발동 확률이 낮아 관련 특성을 최대 단계로 올려도 효과를 제대로 받기 어려운 문제가 있었습니다. 따라서, 괴력 발동 확률을 상향 조정하여 특성 효과를 보다 잘 활용할 수 있도록 하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.09.13 patch notes | TERA KR (v77.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v77-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v77-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Fishing  Added Fishing guide quest [Fishing] Let&#39;s Go Fishing  Quest can be found in Highwatch via NPC Waining Added Vanguard Request &amp;lsquo;Fishing! So much fun!&amp;rsquo; with the following is reward :  500 gold 50 Vanguard Initiative credit 500 Item XP 20 Angler Token 5 Red Angleworm 1 Gathered Materials Box         Material from Gathered Materials Box     Harmony Grass   Cobseed   Veridia Root   Mushroom Cap   Moongourd Pulp   Apple   Plain Stone   Cobala Ore   Shadmetal Ore   Xermetal Ore   Normetal Ore   Galborne Ore   Achromic Essence   Crimson Essence Crystal   Earth Essence Crystal   Azure Essence Crystal   Opal Essence Crystal   Obsidian Essence Crystal       Fishing is done by using Bait with Fishing Rod near Fisheries  Before attempting to fish, bait must be activated by using Bait 1 Bait is consumed if there is a bite while fishing Fishing spots can be found via Worldmap UI  Muricai Fishery Cutthroat Harbor Fishery Lake of Tears Fishery Vexatus Swamp Fishery Celsian Lake Fishery Seren&amp;rsquo;s Lake Fishery   Fishing does not consume Production Point If there is no action for 3 minutes upon a bite, game will automatically switch to automated mode and fish until all bait is used or inventory is full There are four (Old, Xermetal, Ash Sapling, Fairywing) types of fishing rod, and all types excluding old fishing rod can be promoted to tier 8   42 different types of fish can be caught, and it can be either cooked or delivered  Fish are graded from tier 0 to tier 10 and by size, and large fish can only be caught manually Delivery  Fish can be delivered to an NPC located in cities and fishing spots Demand list changes every day at 6am Fish can only be delivered a limited amount of times, and resets at 6am        2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.09.06 patch notes | TERA KR (v76.03.03)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03-03/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  서버 안정화 작업이 진행되었습니다.  2. DB hardware exchange  DB 장비교체로 점검 시간이 다소 길어진 점 양해 부탁드립니다.  Developer comment - 리리 제멋대로의 선물 오류 원인 파악이 완료되어 차주 정기점검 시 수정될 예정입니다. 불편을 끼쳐 드려 죄송합니다. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.30 patch notes | TERA KR (v76.03.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Server stabilization  서버 렉 현상 완화를 위한 안정화 작업이 진행되었습니다.  Bug fixes  Fixed issue where character boss event quest item was not usable Fixed issue where option to see monters on radar UI would automatically uncheck Fixed issue where certain new/returning player event items would have different item type than described  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.23 patch notes | TERA KR (v76.03.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Bamarama  Changed round times  Changed time per round to 180 seconds Changed Gold Ticket round from once every 10 minutes to once every 5 minutes Changed Diamond Ticket round from every 50 minute of the hour to every 25 and 55 minute of the hour   Changed Gold Ticket and Diamond Ticket to cannot trade status, and changed sale price  Golden Ticket : 90 silver to 1 gold, Diamond Ticket : 9 gold to 10 gold   Changed betting time and betting limit  Time  Changed betting time to 90 seconds   Golden Ticket  Changed round frequency from 10 minutes to 5 minutes, and changed maximum betting limit from 30k tickets to 100k tickets   Diamond Ticket  Changed round frequency from 60 minutes to 30 minutes, and changed maximum betting limit from 10k tickets to 30k tickets     Applied tariff upon winning  From 0% to 10%   Place a Trade Broker (beside banker) Changed Bamarama BAM HP and enrage duration by half, and changed minimum HP required to use ultimate [from below 30%] to below 40%  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.16 patch notes | TERA KR (v76.03)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-03/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill / balance  Brawler  Never Retreat (new passive)  Acquired at level 65 Increase frontal skill damage by 7% and aggro by 15%   Jackhammer  Changed max endurance debuff stack from 8 to 3 Changed endurance debuff effect from 1.5% to 4.0%     Berserker  Unleashed: Beast Fury  Decrease damage received by 50% while casting     Valkyrie  Leaping Slash  Recover 10 Ragnarok Point upon successful 2nd hit   Half-moon Slice  Decreased Ragnarok Point recovered from 16 to 15 upon successful hit   Leaping Slash, Shining Crescent, Half-moon Slice  Now displays Ragnarok Point recovered in tooltip     Warrior  Enhanced Defensive Stance (new passive)  Acquired at level 65 Increase frontal skill damage by 8% while in Defensive Stance     Sorcerer  Elemental Cores  Increase skill damage by 4% upon obtaining a core     Archer  Gust Arrow  Slightly increased total skill damage Slightly increased casting speed   Find Weakness  Added an effect to the skill      Developer comment - 광풍살의 후폭풍 효과가 의도와는 다르게 2회 중복 적용되어 과도한 위력을 발휘하던 문제를 수정하였으며, 스킬의 감소된 위력 및 위상을 감안하여, 광풍살 스킬의 위력 및 차징 속도를 소폭 증가 시켰습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-08-09 patch notes | TERA KR (v76.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum  Removed ilvl access restriction Adjusted Vanguard Request ilvl requirement from 457 to 456 Can now use IMS upon reaching ilvl 456 Adjusted drop rate of Supreme Metal, Sacred Mallet    2. Gear  Changed Heroic Oath enchanting cost for +2 -&amp;gt; +3  Weapon       Item Amount (before) Amount (after)     Gold 109,447 91,206   Golden Plate 382 153   Silver Plate 96 38   Supreme Metal 395 237   Weight Pendulum 29 29   Sacred Mallet 9 20   Diamond 9 0       Armor       Item Amount (before) Amount (after)     Gold 65,668 54,723   Golden Plate 229 92   Silver Plate 57 23   Supreme Metal 237 142   Weight Pendulum 17 17   Sacred Mallet 5 12   Diamond 6 0       Gloves, boots       Item Amount (before) Amount (after)     Gold 43,779 36,383   Golden Plate 153 61   Silver Plate 38 15   Supreme Metal 158 95   Weight Pendulum 11 11   Sacred Mallet 3 7   Diamond 4 0    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.08.02 patch notes | TERA KR (v76.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  New : Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum  Requires ilvl 457 to use IMS Located at Frymount Drop table includes Sacred Mallet, Springy Draco Limb, Weight Pendulum, Supreme Metal, Amplifier II, Transcendent Mask, auto-pot pet, Superior Etchings, and Meownya Innerwear (all 5 types) Added Bahaar&amp;rsquo;s Sanctum to Leaderboard  Added Replica Statue as Leaderboard reward      Replica standards  Previous season rank 1 party   No replica is installed for the first season, and existing replicas are removed when seasons change Only the rank 1 party will have their replica installed  Replica look saved as right before server maintenance   Replica look will reflect the look right before server maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.26 patch notes | TERA KR (v76.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v76-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Elin Brawler  Added class [Brawler] to class Elin  Cannot use Race Change Voucher    2. Character limit  Expanded character limi from 20 slots to 21 slots  Can receive Additional Character Slot from Elin Brawler event page    3. Battleground reward  Fixed tool tip on enchanting material that can be received from Battleground  4. Skill and balance  Valkyrie  Added 11% additional damage to boss monsters Changed armor option [Shining Crescent] Increase critical damage by 8% to Increase all skill damage by 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.19 patch notes | TERA KR (v75.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v75-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v75-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  New : Grotto of Lost Souls (hard)  Requires ilvl 455 to use IMS (1 entry, 2 with VIP) Located at Dragonfall Drop table includes Supreme Metal, Dragons Bow, Weight Pendulum, Accessory Amplifier I/II, Transcendent Mask, and Meownya Innerwear (all 5 types)   New : Grotto of Lost Souls  Requires ilvl 453 to use IMS (1 entry, 2 with VIP) Located at Dragonfall Drop table includes Elemental Essence, Pansophic Ash, Brooch etchings I/II, Accessory Amplifier I, Infinity Mask, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.13 patch notes | TERA KR (v75.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v75-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v75-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill  Revert chain skill to the state before 07.12  Developer comment - 자동으로 설정된 이어지는 스킬과 직접 설정한 이어지는 스킬을 동시에 이용하는 수호자님의 불편을 고려하여 기존의 방식대로 되돌렸습니다.  Gunner  Rolling Reload  Changed skill cooldown to 4 seconds after using just 1 time, to be able to use 2 times   Dashing Reload  Changed skill cooldown to 4 seconds after using just 1 time, to be able to use 2 times      Bug fixes  Skill  Sorcerer : Fixed issue where Fusion skill did not immediately go on cooldown Fixed issue where charging skills would go off earlier than expected Ninja : Fixed issue where using Leaves on the Wind as a chain skill in between Boomerang Shuriken occasionally crashed client Gunner : Fixed issue where [Blast] related glyphs did not take effect on additional missiles from [Modular Weapon System]-applied [Detonate] Fixed issue where hit from behind buff of Apex passive skills did not specify on monsters   UI  Fixed issue where Champion laurel did not display on party UI Fixed issue where whisper alert setting would alert as undefined Fixed issue where adjusting font size on chat UI would apply to all tabs (not fixed) Fixed issue where adjusting shortcuts did not work properly Fixed issue where skill or items did not register on item slot after immediately removing skill or item off the skill slot by drag and drop Fixed issue where chain skills did not work upon registering in the right extended skill slot Fixed issue where shortcut settings before 07.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.12 patch notes | TERA KR (v75.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v75-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v75-01/</guid>
      <description>Apex and skill udpate 1. Class Awakening  Added Apex Skills to 6 classes : Archer, Ninja, Gunner, Reaper, Valkyrie, Sorcerer  Mission quest can be proceeded upon reaching ilvl 439 and acquire [Apex Skills].   Adjusted recommended glyph setup and chain skills for all Class Awakening part. 1 classes except Mystic  2. Skill and balance adjustments  Added new skills and changed a few existing skills appropriate to the Class Awakening update Sorcerer  [Apex Skill] Elemental Cores (active)  Imbues elements to existing offensive skills, and elements divide into Flame, Frost, and Lightning Depending on the combination of collected elements, skills enabled by [Fusion] changes Normally you are allowed to fuse 2 elements, but during [Mana Boost] you can fuse up to 3 elements   [Apex Skill] Ice Lances (active)  Throws frost projectiles forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.28 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Elin Gunner  Can now create Elin Gunner  Cannot use Race Change Voucher to create an Elin Gunner    2. Balance  Slightly adjusted balancing of all classes except reaper throughout level progression  Bug fixes  Leaderboard  Fixed issue where ranking titles were not collected from players   Island of Dawn  Fixed issue where caiman thieves did not spawn    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.21 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Item  Added clear face cosmetic  This item equipped in the face style slot hides the expressed appearance of masks Randomly drops from level 65 party dungeons Sells for 8,000 T-cat in the T-cat merchant   Added clear back cosmetic  to level 65 dungeons and Tikat This item equipped in the back style slot hides the expressed appearance of weapons Randomly drops from level 65 party dungeons Sells for 8,000 T-cat in the T-cat merchant    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.14 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Summer festival (TERA KR exclusive)  07/12(목)까지 여름 축제가 오픈되며, 여름 축제 홍보용 NPC가 배치됩니다.  여름 축제 NPC 배치 장소  대도시 내부-벨리카, 알레만시아, 카이아도르 축제장소-태양의 정원, 뱀의 섬      2. Guardian Legion mission  Decreased HP of the initial two dragons for Superior GLM Adjusted Superior GLM time from 15:30 minutes to 18:30 minutes  3. Dreadspire  Adjusted 5th floor and 10th floor reward  Adjusted to increase gold reward  5th floor : 22,000 gold to 30,000 gold 10th floor : 22,000 gold to 50,000 gold   Removed the following rewards  Carved Ornament Copper Clasp Otherwordly SHard Pansophic Ash   Added combat consumables  Bravery Potion, Superior Noctenium Elixir, Fed: Health Potion, Fed: Rejuvenation Potion      4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.06.07 patch notes | TERA KR (v73.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Shadow Sanguinary (hard)  Requires ilvl 446 Teleportal located at Highwatch Outskirts Drop table includes Onset Mask, and other top-tier enchanting materials   Shadow Sanguinary  Requires ilvl 439 Teleportal located at Highwatch Outskirts Drop table includes Golden Talent, Silver Talent, and other high-tier enchanting materials    2. Item  Added new accessories  Ethereal Necklace Ethereal Earring Ethereal Ring Ethereal Circlet Heroic Oath Belt   Added items required to promote to new accessories  (Following items can be acquired from Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard), RK-9 Kennel (hard), and Ruinous Manor (hard)) Worn crate Devil&amp;rsquo;s Claw Dragon Skull   Added Talent Reset Potion to Specialty Merchants at each town (TERA KR exclusive)  Price : 2,000 gold    Bug fixes  UI  Fixed issue where simply selecting the existing rerollable options in a different order displayed a different Semi Enigmatic Scroll cost than the actual cost    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.31 patch notes | TERA KR (v73.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Battleground  Added Bellicarium credits to rewards and enchanting material box  Revised reward       Battleground Bellicarium Credit win reward Bellicarium Credit lose reward Win reward Lose reward     Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold 90,000 30,000 Enchanting material boxes x 7 Enchanting material boxes x 4   Fraywind Canyon 90,000 30,000 Enchanting material boxes x 8 Enchanting material boxes x 5   Champions&amp;rsquo; Skyring (solo) 9,000 3,000 Golden Talent x 7 Silver Talent x 3   Champions&amp;rsquo; Skyring (team) 4,500 1,500 Golden Talent x 7 Silver Talent x 3       Changed reward from Vanguard request from 1x Champion&amp;rsquo;s Enchanting Chest to 2x Champion&amp;rsquo;s Enchanting Chest Increased Bellicarium credit cap to 2,000,000 credits Added the following items to the Bellicarium credit merchant  Bellicarium credit merchant :         Item Point cost     Liquid Metal 3,000   Hypnotic Device 6,000   Archdevan Surfactant 30,000   Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools 9,600   Copper Clasp 18,000   Pansophic Ash 30,000   Elemental Essence 600,000   Archdevan Formula 6,000   Carved Ornament 12,000   Otherworldly Shard 200,000   Veilthroch 1,500,000   Ruby 10,000       One of the following items can be rewarded from the (new) enchanting material box :       Item Min Max     Golden Talents 35 35   Liquid Metal 1 1   Hypnotic Device 1 1   Archdevan Surfactant 1 1   Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools 1 1   Copper Clasp 1 1   Pansophic Ash 1 1   Elemental Essence 1 1   Silver Talents 35 35   Archdevan Formula 1 1   Carved Ornament 1 1   Otherworldly Shard 1 1   Veilthroch 1 1   Infinity Mask 1 1       Removed Killing Spree and its credit merchant    Developer comment - 승리의 인도자 평판 포인트를 통해 전장 보상을 추가 지급하게 되면서 더 이상 사용하지 않는 광기의 학살자 평판 포인트와 관련 상점을 삭제하게 되었습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.24 patch notes | TERA KR (v73.01.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Style shop (TERA KR exclusive)  발키온 정찰대 포인트로 구매 가능한 외형 아이템이 추가되었습니다.  새로운 외형으로 &amp;lsquo;무자비한 무기&amp;rsquo; 시리즈를 판매합니다.  해당 아이템은 6월 21일 정기점검 전까지 구입하실 수 있습니다.      2. Event item removal (TERA KR exclusive)  슈퍼위크 럭키 이벤트 아이템인 [이벤트] 잔칫상, 정제된 녹테늄 강화탄[전설], [이벤트] 용맹의 물약II 가 기간종료로 삭제됩니다.  Bug fixes  Dungeon  Broken Prison, 3rd boss : Fixed issue where portals did not get destroyed occasionally Dreadspire, 8th floor : Fixed issue where 2 aggro marks were designated Kalivan&amp;rsquo;s Challenge : Fixed issue where defeating 1st boss did not open path to 2nd boss   UI  Fixed issue where certain profile elements were empty occasionally TERA KR event exclusive   Skill  Lancer : Fixed issue where Adrenaline Rush talent effect to increase skill damage by 5% did not apply    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.18 patch notes | TERA KR (v73.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update Bug fixes  Skill  Fixed issue where shield-type skills absorbed a static amount of damage   Item  붉은 에메랄드 큐브 툴팁 획득 리스트에 희귀 스킬교본:블루/옐로우 리리가 누락된 문제 수정 (* 희귀 스킬교본: 피닉스,본드래곤 누락 문제 또한 차후 점검을 통해 수정할 예정입니다.)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.17 patch notes | TERA KR (v73.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v73-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill and balance adjustment  Priest  Mana Infusion  Decreased total casting time by 2 seconds, and increased casting speed by 10% Increased MP regeneration from 100 to 500 MP per second Decreased duration from 20 seconds to 10 seconds Increased cooldown from 10 seconds to 20 seconds Changed to maintain abnormality even after using attack skills or getting hit     Slayer  Energy Rush  Changed skill to apply as increase 25% crit chance as it is written in the skill tooltip rather than increase 25% crit factor     Reaper  Shadow Reaping  Changed cooldown from 120 seconds to 90 seconds   Enhanced Shadow Reaping  Changed attacks peed increase from 5% to 4%     Berserker  Thunder Strike  Decreased PVP damage by 5%      2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.10 patch notes | TERA KR (v72.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Event item removal  Removed Manglemire event related items  2. Guardian Legion mission additional reward  Distributed additional rewards that were not distributed to players properly  Distributed via parcel    Bug fixes  UI  Fixed issue where Lancer&amp;rsquo;s perfect block UI would display longer than the reflected damage splash Fixed issue where items distributed through events could not be registered on a skill slot   Dungeon  Demon&amp;rsquo;s Wheel, 1st boss : Fixed issue where aoe attacks would explode immediately when boss is defeated    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.05.03 patch notes | TERA KR (v72.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Demon&amp;rsquo;s Wheel  5 man dungeon reopen Teleportal : Alementheia Outskirts ilvl required : 439  Loot table includes Dyad Niveot Structure, [Event] Afro, [Event] Lamb Bulgogi    2. Civil Unrest  Changed so that only guild members with authority can place Guild Tower  3. Gridiron  Changed operating hours (TERA KR exclusive)  Changed rank rewards  Medal         Rank Amount     1st 9   2-3rd 7   4-7th 6   8-10th 5       Medal shop       Item Medal needed     Health Potion 2   Bravery Potion II 4   Rare Noctenium Refiner 14   Gridiron golden talent box 6   Rare innerwear exchange voucher 240   Dragonscale 10   Niveot Structure 120   Smart Niveot Structure 800    Developer comment - 지하의 격전장 참여인원을 10:10으로 변경한 이후에도 원활한 매칭이 이뤄지지 않아 이용시간을 좁혀 지하의 격전장을 이용하시는 수호자 분들이 제한된 시간이나마 대기 시간 없이 전장을 즐기실 수 있도록 운영시간을 조절하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.26 patch notes | TERA KR (v72.01.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Adjusted balance on Dreadspire  Adjusted to decrease HP of each monster Decreased the frequency of patterns for 3rd floor Dakuryon Decreased the stack debuff difficulty of 6th floor Krakatox   Closed Manglemire Disabled usage of Chocolates (consumables) in ranking contents. entering dungeons with the buffs will removes the consumables. the following dungeons are affected :  Dreadspire Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard) Pit of Petrax    Developer comment - 이벤트성으로 지급된 소모품 아이템의 효과가 순위 경쟁에 영향을 끼칠 만큼 높은 성능을 지니고 있고, 해당 아이템의 유무에 따라 순위가 갈리는 현상을 방지하고자 하였습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.20 patch notes | TERA KR (v72.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update Bug fixes  Flying Guardian Legion mission  Fixed issue regarding server instability and reopen mission   Skill  Fixed issue where certain shield-type skills were able to absorb more damage than it should   Item  Fixed issue where mid-tier Island of Dawn enchanting box had missing possible items in its tool tip   Dungeon  Fixed issue in Ruinous Manor where 3rd boss dropped Dyad Niveot Structure Fixed the drops of the following dungeons :  Red Refuge  Adjusted to decrease drop amount of Archdevan Formula   Island of Dawn  Adjusted to increase drop amount of Golden Talents to maximum in mid-tier Island of Dawn enchanting boxes   Rk-9 Kennel (hard)  Removed Enchanting Crate from reward   Sky Cruiser Endeavor  Adjusted to increase drop amount of Hypnotic Device       Event (TERA KR exclusive)  하늘고래 날탈 쿠폰으로 지급되는 일부 비행 탈 것의 지상 속도 성능 280인 문제    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.19 patch notes | TERA KR (v72.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v72-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Guardian Legion mission  Added flying Guardian Legion missions Rhapsody of Wind and Fire and Recon Eradication Mission  Can only be taken by level 65 players, and can participate in the same way as existing Guardian Legion missions  World map &amp;gt; Guardian Legion mode toggle &amp;gt; Track mission &amp;gt; Enter mission   As the mission partakes in the air, you can only carry out the mission with a flying mount You can gain Guardian Legion points in the same way as existing Guardian Legion missions, and with enough points you can earn Guardian Legion gem box, item XP, and Guardian Legion credits Successfully clearing flying Guardian Legion missions can reward either 1-3x Mark of Flight or a Superior Etching Box as [additional reward]  Additional reward ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.12 patch notes | TERA KR (v71.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v71-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v71-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. PVP  Disabled Outlaw content Existing skill is turned off, and Infamy reset to 0  Developer comment - 의도치 않은 악용이 지속 발생하고 있으며, 사용성 개선이 필요하다고 판단하여 일시적으로 무법자 컨텐츠를 중단하게 되었습니다. 추후 개선된 모습으로 업데이트 될 예정입니다. Bug fixes  Dreadspire  Fixed issue where player&amp;rsquo;s death location was different per player Fixed issue on 3rd floor where projectiles from Demokrons one shot players   Skill  Fixed issue where Baraka Priest&amp;rsquo;s Zenobia&amp;rsquo;s Vortex IX skill casting speed was different compared to other races Fixed issue where Warrior&amp;rsquo;s Blade Frenzy tooltip did not have cooldown information Fixed issue where using Lancer&amp;rsquo;s Stand Fast increased based attack speed stat in Profile UI Fixed issue where Ninja&amp;rsquo;s Jagged Path tooltip information of distance was different from actual distance traversed Fixed issue where Reaper&amp;rsquo;s Soul Reversal talent did not apply to large monsters (Added) 광전사 피의 보복 패시브 효과가 힐/정화를 받을 때도 적용이 되던 문제 (Added) 사제 수호자의 성역 탈출 특성이 찬란한 섬광에 의한 본인 피격에도 적용되던 문제    Developer comment - 사제/광전사의 이번 오류 수정으로, 기존 상황에서 플레이 하셨던 수호자님께는 적지 않은 변화가 생겼다는 점을 인지하고 있습니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.04.05 patch notes | TERA KR (v71.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v71-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v71-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Dreadspire  Added Veilthroch to 5th floor reward Increased item drop rate by 2 times excluding gold by changing Joy of Partying to apply   Pit of Petrax  Changed Petrax to not enrage regardless of aggro unless damage is dealt Changed timer condition to upon hitting monster    2. Leaderboard  Due to rankings made with a bug, Pit of Petrax rankings has been reset Changed ranking conditions for Dreadspire  From clearing 4th floor -&amp;gt; to 1st floor    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03.29 patch notes | TERA KR (v71.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v71-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v71-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  New dungeon : Dreadspire  10 floor 5-man dungeon There is no ilvl requirement, and 1 entry (2 for VIP) per day upon reaching level 65 Dungeon teleportal is located at Tempest Reach The following items are rewarded per floor :       5F 10F 1 ~ 5F 6 ~ 10F     Elemental Essence Veilthroch Dreadspire Helmet Dreadspire Armor   Copper Clasp Copper Clasp &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;   Pansophic Ash Pansophic Ash &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;   Archdevan Formula Archdevan Formula &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;   Carved Ornament Carved Ornament &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;   Otherworldy Shard Otherworldy Shard &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;   Gold reward Gold reward &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;       Added Dreadspire to Leaderboard   Reopen Manglemire  5-man dungeon reopen Requires ilvl 439 to use IMS Dungeon teleportal is located at Pora Elinu Can receive rewards of ilvl 439 dungeons   Ace Dungeon  Changed to spawn teleportal to Highwatch upon clear   Pit of Petrax  Added one of the following to be static drops upon clear  Prime Battle Solution Bravery Potion Raw Moonlight Fruit (restores 100 production points) Complete Crystalbind (1 hour) Goldfinger Token Dragonscale   Adjusted to lower Archdevan Archer damage Adjusted timer requirement  Start requirement  (From) Petrax recognizing user by aggro -&amp;gt; (to) approaching a certain distance to Petrax; displays a message of the combat and starts the timer   Pause requirement  Death during combat with Petrax; timer does not reset even though aggro has been reset     Removed Petrax HP recovery mechanic    2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03.22 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.04.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-04-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-04-01/</guid>
      <description>Update Bug fixes  Services  Fixed issue where Restyle Hat on cloud-type cosmetics crashed client    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03-15 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.04)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-04/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Battleground  Adjusted rewards for Corsairs&#39; Stronghold, Fraywind Canyon  Win reward  Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold - Champion&amp;rsquo;s Enchanting Chest x5 -&amp;gt; x7 Fraywind Canyon - Champion&amp;rsquo;s Enchanting Chest x6 -&amp;gt; x8   Lose reward  Corsairs&amp;rsquo; Stronghold - Champion&amp;rsquo;s Enchanting Chest x1 -&amp;gt; x4 Fraywind Canyon - Champion&amp;rsquo;s Enchanting Chest x1 -&amp;gt; x5     Added the following items to Champion&#39;s Enchanting Chest :  Last Element, Infinity Mask   Changed Corsairs&#39; Stronghold cooldown  Changed from 15 minutes -&amp;gt; 10 minutes    Bug fixes  Skill  Lancer : Fixed issue where nearby PC emotes were cancelled upon holding shield Mystic : Talent comment Priest : Fixed issue where two of Backstep, Fiery Escape skills were displayed in the Chain Skill UI Berserker : Fixed issue where maximum viewing distance would decrease upon dying during Berserk status Priest : Fixed issue where Salvation (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.03.08 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.03.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-03-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Battleground  Kumas Royale  Changed kick vote rate  Changed from 100% yes votes to 80% yes votes excluding player to be kicked   Adjusted lose reward  Adjusted from 1 Kumas Royale Receipt to 3 Kumas Royale Receipts      2. Item/quest item deletion  TERA KR exclusive TERA KR exclusive  Bug fixes  Services  Fixed issue where game would crash when equipping and unequipping hat accesssory repeatedly   Dungeon  Fixed issue in Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss where resetting instance did not teleport players out of the instance    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.28 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.03)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-03/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill and balance  Valkyrie  Balder&amp;rsquo;s Tears  Added Ragnarok Point Recovery effect to prevent decay, while recovering 67 points per second Added Ragnarok Point Recovery effect immediately ends upon end of Balder&amp;rsquo;s Tears, or entering combat   Ragnarok point  Changed to not reset upon death Changed Gjallar Horn and Max Ragnarok effects from ending upon death Changed effect duration of Max Ragnarok which prevents decay upon 1000 Ragnarok points from 60 seconds to 40 seconds Changed base decay rate to 50 points per second   Gunner  Talent : Burst Fire - [Force] (x% chance to apply y power which stacks up to 5 times)  Changed Talent effect duration from 5 seconds to 12 seconds   Command : Recall  Decreased cooldown at each skill level by 10 seconds   Bombardment  Decreased Arcane Energy cost from 1500 to 1000 Increased skill damage by 20%   Burst Fire  Increased skill damage by 15% Increased Arcane Energy cost from 70 to 75   Mana Missiles  Increased skill damage by 8%   Scattershot  Increased skill damage by 10%   Energy shot (HB shot)  Increased skill damage by 10%     Slayer  Piercing Lunge (Awakened skill)  Changed to immediately cancel any previous skill motion Changed all attacks to be considered from behind after the 2nd hit (from 5 seconds) to 4 seconds     Priest  Divine Charge  Changed crit power increase description in the tooltip     Mystic  Thrall Augmentation  Changed crit power increase description in the tooltip     Sorcerer  Arcane Pulse  Decreased charging time by 20% (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.22 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.02.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon server stabilization  Proceeded with stabilization update to reduce player lag issues  2. Proxy block  Proceeded with security update to block Proxy usage  Bug fixes  Dungeon  Fixed issue where player location did not sync with the server during certain dungeon mechanics   Quest  Fixed issue where The Traitor of Acarum quest NPC stated the wrong location Fixed issue where Frymount NPCs Eurice and Kenela did not exist Fixed issue where Reaper quest could not proceed by using Double Shear II   Services  Fixed issue where Elin&amp;rsquo;s upswept hairstyle did not display properly to certain classes   Skill  Lancer : Fixed issue where Adrenaline Rush tooltip stated skill damage increase Gunner : Fixed issue where blast was shot not out of Arcannon but elsewhere Brawler : Fixed issue where using Divine Wrath glyphed with Energetic glyph fully filled rage gauge    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.08 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Quest  Revised &amp;lsquo;Tragedy and Triumph&amp;rsquo; story quest at Ex Prima to respawn experiment cage while progressing the quest  Bug fixes  Party  Fixed issue where vote UI for kicking offline players did not display after entering dungeon/battleground   Dungeon  Fixed issue in Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (nm/hm) where players could not re-enter when defeating final boss and wiping simultaneously   Skill  Fixed issue where summoning shadow as Baraka Warrior did not summon shadow   Item  11/23(목) 점검 이후 접속 시 소지하고 있던 마도공학회 엘리트 유니폼이 삭제되었던 문제 (오늘 중 우편으로 복구해드릴 예정입니다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.02.01 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.02)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-02/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Battleground  Adjusted point scale for Gridiron  Increased Warrior damage point scale Increased Lancer technique point scale Increased Ninja damage point scale Increased Valkyrie damage point scale Decreased Sorcerer damage point scale Decreased Archer damage point scale Decrased Priest technique point scale    2. Dungeon  Pit of Petrax  Revised Petrax HP per class Reset dungeon rankings accordingly   Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard)  Increased movement speed of 3rd boss after 5 minute time attack   Significantly decreased item, gold, exp earned from monsters for those higher than a certain level limit from the following dungeon  Ebon Tower Kelsaik&amp;rsquo;s Nest Labyrinth of Terror Sabex Armory Macellarius Catacombs   Sabex Armory, Macellarius Catacombs  Significantly decreased gold drop amount    3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.25 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Skill and balance  Lancer  Adrenaline Rush  Removed additional 5% damage to monsters effect     Warrior  Blade Waltz  Fixed issue where this skill could not cancel post animation of Torrent of Blows and Battle Cry     Berserker  Crush  Decreased skill damage by 25%   Smash  Decreased skill damage by 25%   Decimate  Decreased skill damage by 25%     Slayer  Colossus Blade  Changed cooldown from 5 minutes to 3 minutes   Piercing Lunge  Changed to definitely crit upon hit Increased skill damage by 30%     Sorcerer  Meteor Strike  Increased base crit chance by 10% Changed MP cost from 800 to 750   Void Pulse  Increased base crit chance by 10% Changed MP cost from 600 to 550   Lightning Strike  Changed MP cost from 300 to 250   Hailstorm  Changed MP cost from 900 to 800     Gunner  Mana Missile  Increased skill damage by 10%   Time Bomb  Increased skill damage by 10%   HB bomb  Increased base crit chance by 20%   Burst Fire  Increased base crit chance by 15%     Ninja  Burning Heart  Talent : Changed talent condition from upon critical hit to upon hit Changed cooldown reduction of Attunement from a maximum of 6s to 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.18 patch notes | TERA KR (v69.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v69-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  New dungeon : Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss  Requires ilvl : 446 Dungeon entrance : Velika Outskirts Reward : Emerald, Diamond, high/top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier accessory enchanting material, Onset Mask   New dungeon : Antaroth&amp;rsquo;s Abyss (hard)  Requires ilvl : 453 Dungeon entrance : Velika Outskirts Reward : Infinity Mask, rare/superior innerwear, Stormcry gear box, Emerald, Diamond, top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier accessory enchanting material   Pit of Petrax  Removed Pit of Petrax shield phases, and changed additional mobs to drop HP motes upon death Changed some of the other patterns (Added) Changed daily entry limit from 3 to 2 (additional 1 entry for VIP ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.11 patch notes | TERA KR (v68.01.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v68-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v68-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  Ruinous Manor (hard)  Increased respawn time  This change is made in order to prevent users from resetting after combat and preventing certain mechanics from initiating     Red Refuge, Red Refuge (hard)  Revised first boss&amp;rsquo; in/out pre-explosion effect Revised obstructions on path to first boss    2. Achievement season 8 start  Achievement season 8 which was delayed last week due to an error will now start  Bug fixes  Dungeon  Fixed issue where background music did not play in Red Refuge and Red Refuge (hard)   UI  Fixed issue where Guardian Mission UI displayed outside of Guardian Missions area    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.01.04 patch notes | TERA KR (v68.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v68-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v68-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Dungeon  New : Red Refuge  Required ilvl for IMS : ilvl 439 Teleportal is located in Feral Valley, Frontera Frostmetal gear box, Emerald, Diamond, high/top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier jewelry enchanting material can be obtained   New : Red Refuge (hard)  Required ilvl for IMS : ilvl 446 Teleportal is located in Feral Valley, Frontera Onset Mask, Stormcry gear box, Emerald, Diamond, High/top-tier gear enchanting material, high-tier jewelry enchanting material can be obtained   Lilith&amp;rsquo;s Keep (hard)  Increased drop rate of Liquid Metal Decreased drop rate of Carved Ornament Copper Clasp will no longer drop   Sky Cruiser Endeavor, Ruinous Manor, RK-9 Kennel  Increased drop rate of Hypnotic Device Decreased drop rate of Archdevan Formula Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools will no longer drop   Broken Prison  Increased drop rate of Liquid Metal Decreased drop rate of Carved Ornament, Archdevant Surfactant Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools will no longer drop   Thaumetal Refinery (hard)  Increased drop rate of Liquid Metal Decreased drop rate of Carved Ornament Copper Clasp will no longer drop Decreased damaged of certain skills for all three bosses Increased cooldown of certain skills for all three bosses   RK-9 Kennel (hard)  Increased drop rate of Carved Ornament, Otherworldly Shard, Copper Clasp Liquid Metal, Hypnotic Device, Archdevan Surfactant, Archdevan Formula, Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools will no longer drop Decreased drop rate of Emerald, Diamond, Elemental Essence Decreased drop rate of jewelry etchings   Ruinous Manor (hard)  Increased drop rate of Archdevan Formula, Otherworldly Shard, Artisan&amp;rsquo;s Tools Carved Ornament, Hypnotic Device, Copper Clasp, Archdevan Surfactant, Liquid Metal, Soul Fragment will no longer drop Decreased drop rate of Elemental Essence Decreased drop rate of jewelry etchings    Developer comment - In accordance to adding new dungeons without retiring old dungeons, rewards for existing dungeons have been adjusted with the addition of new dungeons (Red Refuge, Red Refuge (hard)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018.07.05 patch notes | TERA KR (v74.02.01)</title>
      <link>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tera-mysterium.com/en/patch/2018/v74-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Update 1. Level progression reward UI revision  Revised to receive all accumulated rewards at once  *이미 보상 UI가 4개를 초과하여 보상을 받지 못하신 수호자님께 오늘 중 보상을 지급해드릴 예정이었으나, 대상자 추출에 문제가 있어 07/12(목)으로 지급일이 연기되었습니다. 안내드린 일정을 지키지 못해 죄송합니다.    Bug fixes  Skill  Fixed issue where Brawlers could endlessly maintain Rhymthmic Blows buff by repeating Punch, Counter, and Rhythmic Blows   Item  Fixed issue where passive effects on gear occasionally did not work    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>